Chapter 797: Inter-Star Field Stargate

The Central Galaxy was many Star Fields from the Shattered Star Ring. There were also many desolate universe belts in between. The distance was extremely far. Back then, even though EsGod's subordinates had taken an extremely fast high-grade spaceship, it had still taken them years to cross this distance in hyperdrive. Without hyperdrive, it would probably have taken billions of years.

The first stop of the fleet was the Inter-Star Field Stargate Station that the Crimson Dynasty had built in the Shattered Star Ring.

Inter-Star Field Stargates could tremendously reduce the traveling time. It was the one and only way to safely and quickly travel between Star Fields. This did not include natural wormholes.

The further the distance reduced by the stargate, the more difficult it would be for the coordinates to be accurate, and it would be easy to deviate from the target. An Inter-Star Field Stargate was a technology barrier; even Star Cluster civilizations could not build them. Civilizations stronger than Star Cluster civilizations had this technology, but the three Universal Civilizations had made a rule to forbid any other civilization except them from building Inter-Star Field Stargates. Therefore, all the Inter-Star Field Stargates used to travel between the Star Fields came from the three civilizations. They were divided into military and citizen use.

Han Xiao and the others planned to borrow the military path, which was quicker and more convenient. As a high-level ally of the dynasty, of course, he had the right to.

"I have notified the troops at the stargate station," Zoel said in the communicator. "Once you identify yourself, they will let you pass and help you activate the military stargate. When you arrive at the Constellation Corridor, the dynasty's troops would be waiting there for you."

The Central Galaxy was the general name of the mother Star Fields of the three civilizations. They formed the central area of the universe. These three Star Fields were the Federation of Light's Abyss of Stars, the Arcane Church's Silver Arm, and the Crimson Dynasty's Constellation Corridor.

The Crimson Dynasty's military stargate in the Shattered Star Ring was located in a Star Cluster at the edge. Leaving from the Black Star Army, it would take about more than half a month to reach even with the stargates of the Star Cluster civilizations along the way and hyperdrive.

Han Xiao stayed within the long-distance fleet and communicated with Teny and the other dynasty elites on the way. With his identity and position, as well as the fact that they would meet each other every day given they were on the same ship, most people became familiar with Han Xiao.

Only Teny maintained an indifferent attitude—he was naturally suspicious, and keeping his alert up was a habit.

However, Han Xiao knew his personality rather well. If he used his personality to get close to him, it would have the opposite effect and make him even more cautious. Furthermore, as a Beyond Grade A, he would not lower his pride and fawn over a dynasty colonel. Therefore, Han Xiao treated all equally and did not look for Teny to speak privately.

According to Teny's personality, Han Xiao decided to stay put and wait. As Teny was also a Mechanic, he would likely go to him and ask for a lesson. After all, they were both on the dynasty's side; getting to know Han Xiao was the best way to learn. Although Han Xiao did not know where Teny's alertness came from, it did not seem like there was a need for him to give up an opportunity like this.

About ten days after setting off, Teny finally knocked on his door.

...

"You want to learn about my machinery technology?"

Inside the room, Han Xiao told Phillip to control the domestic robots to send two calming light green vegetable drinks onto the table. He looked at Teny and his deputy, Corbus, who sat opposite him.

Teny nodded slowly and did not touch the drink on the table. "Not really learn. I just want to exchange some knowledge with you."

As he had a request to make on this trip, he would not give an unfriendly face. He let go of a part of his caution and used a sincere attitude.

To him, this was nothing to be ashamed of. No matter what he would achieve in the future, for now, he was just a dynasty colonel. His position and identity were miles away from Han Xiao.

Han Xiao was delighted within but did not show it at all. He tapped the table and said, despite knowing the answer, "I only know you're a Mechanic, but I have never heard about what branch you focus on."

"Pure Mechanic, Armed Branch. I crossed the Grade A barrier two years ago and became a Calamity Grade," Teny said.

"Hmm, although I'm not of the Armed Branch, I can still teach you some experience." Han Xiao smiled.

"That's exactly my request." Teny nodded.

Every Beyond Grade A Mechanics had a specialty. Some had special styles; some had unique technology. With Teny's current level, he rarely had the chance to come into contact with any Beyond Grade As. Since Black Star was there, he did not want to give up on the opportunity to learn things from him.

Back when he knew that he was going there, he had already thought of this. After observing Han Xiao for a few days, he had finally decided to make a move.

Han Xiao chatted with him about technology for many hours, and Teny felt he had benefitted a lot from it.

"Let's end here for today." Han Xiao stopped and smiled. He then deliberately pointed at his temple and said, "I just transmitted some theory information into your communicator. Some is my experience; some are theories I've collected. Take a look."

Teny heard and nodded. "Thank you."

"You're welcome." Han Xiao waved his hand, suppressed his grin, and acted casual. "There's nothing much to do on the way anyway. If you have anything you want to ask, you can come to me again."

"Okay." Teny squeezed out a smile and gave an even better attitude. After all, he now owed Han Xiao a little.

Han Xiao knew to not continue and expressed his intention of sending the guests away. Teny bowed and left the room. His footsteps were much lighter.

After watching Teny leave, only then did Han Xiao started to shake his head and laugh with satisfaction. With this opportunity, their relationship would have chance to grow. Teny's Favorability was close to 'Friendly'.

With this identity of mine, making friends with high-class people is much easier than before.

If it were a player who wanted to get close to Teny, they would have almost no way to do so. For him, however, it was different. Teny had yet to achieve what he achieved in his previous life, so his position now was higher than Teny's. Furthermore, he was the dynasty's ally. With so many factors, even though Teny seemed cautious, he still came right to Han Xiao's doorstep.

With Han Xiao's current position and identity, farming character Favorability was much easier for him compared to the players.

...

In the next ten or so days, Teny went to consult Han Xiao every two days. Their relationship gradually improved, and they slowly turned into friends. This future marshal of the dynasty was treating himself as the student when he was with Han Xiao.

Of course, due to identity reasons, it was impossible for him to really become Han Xiao's student. However, Beyond Grade As had zero obligation to teach their experience to anyone. Han Xiao being so generous was doing him quite a huge favor. Despite being suspicious, Teny was not someone that could not differentiate the good from the bad. With this in his mind, of course, he would not distance himself from Han Xiao.

Also, every time Teny came, he would bring Corbus along. Han Xiao had some knowledge about this person as well—he was very loyal to Teny, and Teny treated his subordinates well, which gave this guy quite a lot of extra benefits.

Han Xiao felt that he could do something about Corbus. Like chasing a girl, bribing her best friend was a shortcut. Of course, he could not bribe Teny's loyal subordinates, but if he did a great favor for Corbus, Teny might have even more gratitude for him given how Teny had taken care of Corbus.

More than half a month passed. The fleet finally arrived at the dynasty's military stargate station at the Shattered Star Ring.

In the dark universe, a hexagonal stargate hovered. Thick space energy flew inside the gate, forming a deep blue vortex. Around it was the dynasty's heavy universe fortresses with garrisoned troops. Unlike the citizen-use station, no spaceship could enter or leave the stargate there—this was only for the dynasty's troops to use.

As the fleet approached, this stargate expanded in their sights. When getting close, the edges of this stargate seemed to extend to the end of one's sights. It was enormous and marvelous.

"Warning! Warning! Psionic Annihilation Beam aim lock detected!"

The artificial intelligence on the main ship that Han Xiao was in alerted them. The people were not surprised. They knew that they would be locked on by the guarding troops as soon as they entered a certain distance around the military stargate.

The artificial intelligence received a message from the guarding troops. "Stop advancing, report your identity."

"Black Star." Han Xiao validated his identity.

After a while, he finally received a confirmation message of his identity. The guarding troops removed the annihilation beam's aim lock and signaled for the fleet to advance.

This time, the main fleet received a communication request from the guarding troops. After picking up, a person that seemed to be the commander appeared on the screen and said with an expressionless face, "Your Excellency Black Star, Envoy Zoel has told us to set your course in advance. This stargate teleportation will be in direct mode.

"The target is Crimson Ring Star Zone 8, the dynasty's territory. There will be a team of troops there sent by the mother planet to receive you. They will open a flight path and bring you guys for hyperjump. Only then will you be able to pass through the Psionic Belt outside the mother planet and arrive on the dynasty's mother planet."

Han Xiao nodded.

All the Universal Civilizations had powerful weapons to prepare for the day if one of them went mad and used super-long range Primordial Psionic Energy cannons to instantly shatter their mother planet. Therefore, all the Universal Civilizations' mother planets were equipped with all kinds of top-notch defensive measures.

Then, this commander looked at Teny, who was on the side, squeezing out what looked like a smile from his seemingly paralyzed face. "Teny, it's been a long time."

"It's you." Teny's expression was a little odd. "Why are you here guarding the stargate?"

"This is an order from above." This commander shook his head. A hint of bitterness appeared in his eyes but was immediately suppressed.

This command and Teny were graduates from the same year of the dynasty's 'Journey' high-level military school. They knew each other, and both of their results were outstanding. They were supposed to have bright futures, but Teny did not expect him to be sent to guard the stargate.

Guarding the stargate was not a good job, especially military stargates. There was close to zero chance of achieving something remarkable, and they would be held responsible if anything went wrong. However, to keep the stargates safe, elite troops had to be stationed there. Therefore, those stationed at the stargates were either sent there randomly or unlucky ones who were marginalized during faction conflicts. No one would ask to be stationed there.

Teny understood that this friend of his had clearly suffered due to faction conflicts. He shook his head with resignation. "All the best then. Anyway, you'll be sent away in a few years. Take it as an opportunity to train your soldiers."

The transfer period of the stargate guarding troops was not long, usually around six to ten years. The dynasty would also not waste elite troops on stargates all the time.

After chatting for a little, this commander finally ended the communication. This time, the fleet was about to enter the stargate as well.

An extremely strong attraction force came from the other side of the stargate, wanting to drag all of them in like a black hole.

The fleet entered the stargate, and the world outside the porthole became bright.

The inside of the stargate path was filled with violent space energy but was restricted by the stargate's technology, creating a stable path.

The spaceship almost felt stationary. The people inside could not feel the speed of the spaceship's advance at all, as if the fleet had stopped moving in the stargate.

However, in an instant, the ship trembled. The space energy around disappeared, and the scenery outside the porthole became the black universe filled with diamond-like star lights once again.

The stargate that had previously been in front of them was now behind the fleet.

The fortresses around were stationed differently as well. The troops stationed there were more than ten times larger in quantity compared to the previous one.

A special fleet waited before them. The appearance of the spaceship was special. It seemed to be a very uncommon spaceship model.

Beep beep!

This time, every quantum network device received an area announcement made by this special fleet.

"Welcome to the Central Galaxy, Your Excellency Black Star."

Chapter 798: Dynasty Mother Planet

"Welcome to the Central Galaxy, Your Excellency Black Star."

I'm here, at the center of the universe...

As the area announcement sounded, this strange-looking fleet slowly advanced. The fleet's main ship received a communication request. An officer wearing the dynasty's high-level army uniform appeared on the screen. He had a small mustache and looked highly intelligent.

"I'm the commander of the dynasty mother planet's Guard Team 17, here on orders to welcome the dynasty's ally."

Han Xiao's brows rose as he sized him up. This commander was not someone famous, but Han Xiao was somewhat familiar with him. In his previous life, when the players traveled to the dynasty's mother planet, they had to go through many inspections before the mother planet's guard team brought them through. These people were like the gatekeepers, so the players were familiar with all of them.

"Thanks," Han Xiao said.

"Please follow me."

Then, the guard team turned around and headed to the mother planet. The fleet followed behind.

Ames suddenly turned and asked Han Xiao, "This is your first time here at the Central Galaxy, right?"

"Hmm." Han Xiao did not deny it. He knew the Central Galaxy like the back of his hand, but on paper, this was his first time there.

"Then let me tell you about it..." Ames shook her head. She used to occasionally visit the Central Galaxy to sightsee while also searching for Aesop, so she was quite familiar with it. Since Black Star had never gone before, she felt that she had to help Han Xiao know more about the situation here.

Listening to Ames talking about the Central Galaxy, Han Xiao felt a little strange, as if he was a farmer entering a big city for the first time.

"Unlike the other Star Fields, here in the Central Galaxy, the three civilizations rule over all the Star System and the Star Cluster civilizations," Aesop added while Ames was speaking. "In the other Star Fields, the various civilizations are on different sides, while here they're all on one side. The security here is the safest in all the Star Fields. Other than some brutes that are on EsGod's level, there are close to no galactic pirates or wanderers here. They are eliminated as soon as they're discovered by the three civilizations."

Han Xiao nodded. The three civilizations ruled over the Central Galaxy. This was their headquarters and was basically under their complete control. Maintaining the law was equivalent to maintaining their own ruling, so they were not going to allow any disruption.

The two fleets left the stargate station and stopped.

The commander of the mother planet guard team said, "Please wait a moment. I will now open a path for everyone and bring you guys to the mother planet.

Then, the mother planet guard team's battleships shot out blue and green beams, which formed a dot far away. A blue and green ring gradually expanded from it and turned into a teleportation gate-looking path. The inside of the gate was bright green.

"This path is for you guys to safely pass through the Psionic Seal Ring of the mother planet. Your spaceships will receive a coating once you enter the path, so you won't be obliterated by the Psionic Seal Ring," the mother planet guard team commander explained.

The Psionic Seal Ring was like layers of shielding covering the mother planet, protecting it against all kinds of Planetary Obliteration attacks.

This was not just a regular shield. It covered around half of the entire Crimson Ring Star System. Only universal civilizations could build something this grand.

The coating was one of the advanced application methods of energy. Different coatings were like different passwords, and the wrong coatings would not be allowed into the various Psionic Seal Rings. It was like a security pass and a key.

As the fleet entered the light green gate, a thick, colorful coating covered all the spaceships. The guard team followed behind, and the gate closed after them.

The guard team led the way ahead. The two fleets turned into streams of light and advanced following the safe path.

On the ship, Teny started to chat casually with Han Xiao about his mother planet.

"The Psionic Seal Ring was built during the exploration era war. Back then, it was to protect against the Planetary Obliteration attacks from the other civilizations. The cosmic space inside the ring can be considered a completely sealed new world. During the war, the scientists adjusted the physical constants inside, all for the sake of safety. When the time of peace came, these altered physical constants became a form of contamination. It took quite a lot of effort to fix them and make the sealed world that the mother planet was in return to a normal cosmic space..."

"The three civilizations' technology is so much more advanced than before." Aesop caressed his beard as he spoke. "With the concentration of resources, talents, and technology, their development speed far exceeds those beyond Star Cluster civilizations. The gap between them is growing constantly. I wonder what can even shake your rule nowadays."

Han Xiao scratched his nose and did not say anything.

This time, the two fleets passed by an area. Through the porthole, Han Xiao could see a cluster of dark blue light faraway.

Seeing Han Xiao look over, Teny explained, "That's a cluster of Primordial Psionic Energy. If we get close, we will be assimilated and devoured. That's one of the defense measures of the Psionic Seal Ring."

After flying in hyperdrive for two days, the spaceship trembled suddenly and finally left the Psionic Seal Ring. In their sights, a sesame-sized dark red planet appeared.

"That's the dynasty's capital, the Crimson Ring Star Group. Planet Crimson Ring is the main planet. There are sixteen satellites and sixty large government life stations around it, as well as many space bases. The total population is 470 billion," Corbus said with pride.

Han Xiao tutted and said, "The house price there must be very high."

"That's right... but your focus is a little odd." Corbus' lips twitched. I was talking about how marvelous the mother planet is, and you asked me if the house price there is high? Are we even talking about that‽

As the fleet moved closer, they started to see the details of the Crimson Ring Star Group.

Planet Crimson Ring was extremely large. The people of the Crimson Dynasty had artificially modified the size of their mother ship. The sixteen smaller satellites orbited around it. These natural satellites had been moved there by the dynasty using their technology to offset the gravitational pull so the mother planet's habitable area would be enlarged. The planet's surface was filled with buildings.

There were also many large life stations and space fortresses around.

"The capital of a universal civilization, it is indeed marvelous to look at," Ames complimented softly. This was her first time there at the capital of the Crimson Dynasty, and it was thanks to Han Xiao.

"When I was still one of the Ancient Ones, I did come once before, but I did not have as grand an entrance as you." Aesop sighed. "I wonder if the national pillars of the Crimson Dynasty still remember me. I only met them once."

Following the orders, the fleet parked at a space port. The members of the Black Star Army remained in the ships while Han Xiao and the others took the spaceship prepared by the Crimson Dynasty toward Planet Crimson Ring.

He deliberately decided not to bring the players. The players possessed too many uncertainties, so things might get out of hand if they caused any trouble there. Furthermore, if he took the Shattered Star Ring players there, he might not be able to take them back.

As they approached Planet Crimson Ring, the buildings on the surface became gradually clearer. The Crimson Dynasty was known to be strict, hardworking, and pragmatic. Compared to the Federation of Light and the Arcane Church, the cultural aspect of the dynasty was not as advanced. Their architectural aesthetic was focused on sharpness, bulkiness, and symmetry. The main colors used were red, black, and metallic gray.

Hu!

The spaceship slowly landed outside a huge city. The sunlight from the artificial Fixed Star coated the upright buildings with a layer of gold. This was the main city of the dynasty's mother planet, Tarunamir Palace, the power center of the entire dynasty.

A group of receptionists were waiting at the docks. They approached and said, "Your Excellency Black Star, we're responsible for welcoming you. Please follow me to Tarunamir Palace's Dynasty Reception Center to rest for a day. The dynasty's leader will personally meet you tomorrow."

"Okay." Han Xiao had no objection. He then looked at Teny and the group of the dynasty elites and said, "What about you guys?"

Teny shook his head. "We have to report to the army."

Han Xiao nodded before casually summoning a set of Beyond Grade A orange-grade hovering guards to give to Teny.

"For you to protect yourself, I don't know when we will meet next. Keep in contact."

Teny was stunned for a moment. He accepted the set of machinery and gave Han Xiao a deep look. "Okay."

Han Xiao did not forget about the other elite officers and gave them some machinery too, showing friendliness. Mechanical weapons built by a Beyond Grade A were quite valuable to Calamity Grade Mechanics, and Han Xiao had a ton of them.

Han Xiao watched as Teny and the others left.

If not because they had gone to accept the modification, Han Xiao would not have had the chance to have close contact with them. He wondered if he would have chances like this to gain Favorability again in the future.

After the dynasty elites left, the group only consisted of Han Xiao, Ames, Aesop, Hila, and the Black Star Guards. They followed the receptionists through the military security zone and entered Tarunamir Palace.

The moment Han Xiao stepped into the city, suddenly, seven enormous waves of energy erupted and soared into the sky.

Boom!

"Hmm?"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and stopped his footsteps.

These seven sources of energy were all Beyond Grade A!

The seven waves only lasted for an instant before they were withdrawn. There seemed to be no provocative intention, just to showcase their own existence.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. Seven Beyond Grade As... They should be the ones belonging to the dynasty itself and the allies that the dynasty had gathered.

He thought about it. This did not look like a provocation, more like a Beyond Grade A style greeting to the newcomer.

"Your Excellency Black Star, to welcome your alliance, the dynasty has gathered the National Pillars under its command," the receptionist said at a suitable moment. "Other than those who are held back by business or are too far away, all the Beyond Grade As who are free have come. There is a total of seven of them.

"After you meet with the dynasty's leader tomorrow, we will arrange for the various National Pillars to meet with you too."

"National Pillars, these guys have quite a nice title." Han Xiao smiled casually.

"What are you talking about?" The receptionist chuckled. "You, too, are now a National Pillar of our Crimson Dynasty."

"That newcomer is here."

In a certain room inside Tarunamir Palace, a few people with various appearances sat on the sofa and looked in Han Xiao's direction with interest.

"Didn't respond."

"Looks like it's his first time seeing so many Beyond Grade As together, so he doesn't know the rules."

"It's only normal since he's from the Shattered Star Ring."

"Hmm? The woman beside him is a Beyond Grade A, too."

"The Dragon Emperor, Ames, I know her."

"The old man beside looks familiar too... Hey, that guy seems to be one of you guys, the Ancient Ones in the past. The one that knows prophecy."

"It is him. I remember."

"Hehe, this new ally seems quite interesting."

"The Evolution Cube is in his hands. Don't be excessive tomorrow. I still want to borrow it."

Chapter 799: 'Dynasty Ruler' Urranrell and 'Dark Lord' Clotti

The interior reception center of Tarunamir Palace had multiple independent villas.

Han Xiao and the others followed the receptionist into one of them. This would be the temporary accommodation for them.

After settling down, Han Xiao locked himself in his room and pondered about the next day.

"I will be meeting the dynasty's leader and those Beyond Grade As tomorrow. I wonder what the dynasty's leader will talk to me about... Hmm, other than the customary welcome of me being a new ally, the dynasty's leader might request to use the Evolution Cube here on a large scale, as well as invite me to some events...

"As for those Beyond Grade As, they will take me into their circle as an ally. Since we're all on the same side, we will have to help each other..."

He knew the Beyond Grade A members list of the dynasty very clearly, and he knew some of their personalities and likings. However, at this moment, he did not know who the seven who had come were.

"Many of the Beyond Grade As of universal civilizations are seniors who have lived a very long time. They have a ton of talents, abilities, energy, and are very strong..."

He felt that his meeting with the Beyond Grade As tomorrow would most likely not be just a simple meeting.

Beyond Grade As were all individuals with extreme power; strength was their fundamentals. When a newcomer joined their circle, some people might want to test him. If he was weak, even if he would still be accepted into the circle, he would be marginalized—only the strong would be respected.

The three strongest individuals were at the top among the Beyond Grade A allies of the dynasty. Han Xiao wondered how many of them were in attendance this time.

"Although I'm not weak, I'm just barely over the Beyond Grade A doorstep, and some of my attributes are not high enough. The Heber Stellar Furnace Cultivation is already halfway done, which gave me close to 10,000 energy... as for the machinery aspect, it's also more complete..."

Lately, other than dealing with the army's matters, Han Xiao had spent a lot of time building machinery and had stocked up quite a lot of inventory.

Through all the Cutting-Edge Knowledges he obtained, Han Xiao had fused many new machinery blueprints. Other than adding new units into the mechanical army, he also built many other high-level machines that could be used for multiple purposes. He had been increasing his strength through the Mechanic way.

Han Xiao's eyes lit up suddenly.

"Since I know some information about these Beyond Grade As... maybe I can make use of that tomorrow."

...

After sleeping for the night, in the early morning the next day, one dynasty emissary came to Han Xiao's doorstep.

Hila opened the door. The emissary was standing outside with a respectful expression.

"Greetings, the Dynasty Ruler has invited His Excellency Black Star to a meeting."

"Let's go." Han Xiao walked out of his room and nodded.

Hila and the others wanted to follow, but Han Xiao waved his hands and told them to stay. Seeing this, the emissary, who was about to stop them, swallowed the words he wanted to say.

Flying was not allowed above Tarunamir Palace, so the two of them boarded the long-awaited land carrier and drove toward the city center.

The city center was the office area for the people at the highest positions in the dynasty. It was a marvelous and enormous palace.

The closer they got to the center, the tighter the security was. The areas were covered with all kinds of mechanical detection devices and teams of dynasty elite patrols. With just a brief feel, Han Xiao could sense the presence of more than ten Calamity Grades, and that was just from one direction. The defense of the dynasty's capital was extremely powerful.

Not only did universal civilizations control the Central Galaxy—they also controlled some other Star Fields to a certain extent. They had rich talents and resources, as well as all kinds of high-level Super schools to raise talents within. Their ratio of Calamity Grades far exceeded anywhere else in Galaxy. With those factors, the universal civilizations had plenty of powerful members.

The carrier stopped outside the palace, and Han Xiao followed the emissary inside. They passed by checkpoint after checkpoint before boarding the hovering lift inside to the top floor. This entire floor was the office of the dynasty's leader.

After passing by the guard and secretary area, the emissary pushed a door open and gestured for him to enter.

Han Xiao nodded and walked right in. The room entered his sights.

This was a wide office. The room was rectangular, the walls were deep red, and there were floor-to-ceiling windows on every wall.

The floor was covered in a red carpet, and at the edge was a green potted plant. It looked like it was carefully looked after and was giving off a calming aroma. A filled bookshelf stood against one side of the wall, and on the other side was a white stone circular coffee table and a red sofa used to seat guests. There was no furniture in the middle of the room. A huge chandelier hung from the ceiling. Further in, there was an office desk, and a person sat behind it. Another person stood beside the desk.

With just one look, Han Xiao recognized the dynasty's leader who was sitting down.

Her long and white hair was coiled up. The dignified vibe and her serious eyes could make people ignore her looks.

Urranrell Shin Rybet, the Crimson Dynasty's ruler!

Yes, the dynasty's current leader was a woman!

The Crimson Dynasty only admired the strong; sex was not a factor.

The succession of the dynasty's leader had nothing to do with the bloodline. During the term of the previous leader, the training for the candidates for the next leader would have already started. There was more than one candidate. They were all top-notch elites that the upper echelons and the various factions selected through negotiations.

The emissary closed the door from outside.

"Black Star, I'm the Crimson Dynasty Ruler, Urranrell. Please, take a seat." Urranrell stood up, approached him, and reached out her hand.

The man behind her followed tightly after. His sharp eyes were fixed on Han Xiao as if no movement could deceive his eyes.

"Hi." Han Xiao shook her hand. The two of them then sat opposite each other on the guest sofa, while the man behind Urranrell still stood behind her.

"This is Clotti, the captain of the Dynasty Ruler Personal Guards." Urranrell introduced the man behind her.

Clotti raised his head a little with an expressionless face as a greeting.

Han Xiao looked calm, but he had a lot of thoughts in mind.

In his previous life, the leaders of universal civilizations changed quite a number of times throughout the versions. Urranrell was the Crimson Dynasty Ruler during one stage. During her term, to the players, the most famous achievement she made was the battle and the development of the Flickering World. She obtained a new Star Field for the dynasty.

The players in his previous life did not know much about this Dynasty Ruler. That was because, during her reign, the main stage of the players were the Flickering World and their own Star Fields. They had yet to have much contact with the upper echelons of universal civilizations. To them, the leaders of universal civilizations were just a few lines of words in the background introduction.

Now, however, Urranrell was right before his eyes. This woman was one of the three most powerful people in the entire universe. It could even be said that they ruled the universe. What she represented had completely overshadowed her appearance or sex.

Clotti, who was behind her, was her bodyguard, a senior Beyond Grade A nurtured by the dynasty. He was an Esper, and his ability was the control of dark energy and dark matter. Among his nicknames were 'Dark Emperor', 'Lord of Dark Matter', and 'Cosmic Distorter'.

This person was one of the three strongest Beyond Grade As in the dynasty!

"Firstly, on behalf of the Crimson Dynasty, we welcome you as an ally." Urranrell cut to the chase and stared at Han Xiao's eyes.

"This is my honor," Han Xiao replied.

"For the initial stages of the Flickering World exploration, the dynasty needs Heber and your power," Urranrell said slowly. "According to our agreement, other than the resources the dynasty gives you as support, after everything is done, you will receive an area in the Flickering World..."

Han Xiao nodded. "I know."

"You're the dynasty's ally. As long as you make contributions to the dynasty, the dynasty will certainly not hold back on our resources," Urranrell said with a very serious tone. "The more tasks you're willing to take on, the more resources the dynasty will provide you. Sometimes, the dynasty might send out an announcement to dispatch the Beyond Grade As including you and carry out some missions. Of course, if you encounter difficulties, you can also request backup from the Beyond Grade As of the dynasty. Remember, you're one of the dynasty's National Pillars. At the same time, the dynasty has your back."

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and was quite satisfied. Duty and power were associated. By becoming the Crimson Dynasty's ally, he became their power, and they became his. The various Beyond Grade A allies were not just the dynasty's resources, but he had the right to borrow them as well.

"As for the Evolution Cube in your hands, you don't have to worry. By all means, we welcome you to hand it to us willingly, but even if you're not willing to, the dynasty will certainly not snatch it away from you. However, I have a request. The dynasty doesn't oppose you to use the Evolution Cube to negotiate with other organizations, but the evolution allocation for the dynasty must be unlimited. We will send people to the Black Star Army anytime for evolution."

"Of course." Han Xiao nodded. He limited allocations for the other civilizations, but he would not set a limit for his biggest ally, the Crimson Dynasty.

Furthermore, the Crimson Dynasty's population was way too high. There was no way they would make the outrageous request of having their entire race go through evolution. They would not do that even if they had the Evolution Cube themselves.

"Since you've come to the dynasty's mother planet, you might as well stay here for a few days and transform the teams on the mother planet," Urranrell said.

As expected, this is one of the main reasons you called me here, Han Xiao thought.

Compared to selecting elites and sending them to the Shattered Star Ring for evolution, it was clearly more convenient to call him over to the Crimson Dynasty.

Furthermore, the mother planet's troops could not casually be moved around, so summoning him there to use the Evolution Cube was the best solution. This way, the various factions also would not have to negotiate for allocations.

Chapter 800: Pressure

After the two of them talked about business for some time, Urranrell changed the topic. "One more thing. The dynasty is willing to help the Black Star Army build a division in the Central Galaxy to aid communication between both sides. I know you already planned to do this since you brought your portable base here. The dynasty supports this."

"That would be great." Han Xiao nodded.

"As for the details, I will let someone settle them with you," Urranrell said. "If you have any other requests, you can tell me now."

Han Xiao caressed his chin. "I hope to obtain the Ultimate Knowledge of the Mechanic class as soon as possible. I'm wondering if there are any chances."

Without changing her expression at all, Urranrell said, "The resource rewards of the dynasty are given to allies who've made contributions. If you want to obtain it as soon as possible, I suggest you help the dynasty do some things. I will have someone make a list of the matters that the dynasty requires aid with and notify you."

Then Urranrell stood up, extended her hand, and signaled the end of this meeting. Han Xiao did not continue to speak. He stood up as well and shook her hand before bidding farewell and leaving.

The emissary had been waiting outside the door. He guided him out of this palace.

After Han Xiao left, Urranrell leaned on the chair and said slowly with her eyes closed, "Crowell, when you guys meet him later, remember to keep the situation under control."

Clotti grunted in assent and left.

...

Han Xiao boarded the ground carrier. The driver did not head in the direction they had come from but toward another direction.

"Your Excellency Black Star, the National Pillars have been waiting. I'm taking you to meet them," the emissary explained.

Han Xiao did not reply and was still thinking of his meeting with Urranrell earlier.

The meeting was short. Urranrell had plenty of matters to deal with every day, so she would not have time to have a casual chat with him. Hence, everything they had talked about was business. The terms and agreements of the Flickering World partnership were mentioned. After the pioneering of the entire Star Field was complete, as the leading exploration team, he would receive one area that he would be able to develop freely. It was like land awarded by the government.

He would rule that area and own all kinds of rights to it as long as he paid taxes to the dynasty every once in a while.

This was one of the most important terms in their agreement, it would make the Black Star Army even stronger. This was also something very important to Han Xiao. As for the location and size of that area, it would depend on his achievements during the development of the Star Field.

The use of the Evolution Cube and creating a new division of the Black Star Army were his rights and duties as an ally of the dynasty. If he wanted to obtain Ultimate Knowledge personally, he would have to do some dynasty missions. With Urranrell having already spoken about this, he would not have to trigger them himself. The dynasty's men would make a mission list and give it to him, which was much more convenient.

Urranrell... Dynasty Ruler... doesn't show her emotions, not easy to read...

Through the conversation earlier, the image Urranrell gave to him was filled with prestige and the vibe of someone in a high position. Compared to an individual with flesh and blood, this Dynasty Ruler felt more like a symbol, making people ignore her personal traits. Han Xiao basically gave up on wanting to farm her Favorability.

The ruler represented the dynasty. Urranrell had most likely cut off all her personal desires, so she would not have any weaknesses, would be able to maintain rational at all times, and would never let her emotions take over. Her personal feelings would never affect her decisions.

To someone like this, farming Favorability was basically a high-cost, low-reward act, so Han Xiao did not want to waste his efforts.

Comparatively, it would be easier to bond with the Beyond Grade As.

Very soon, the carrier stopped before a villa. This was not a villa in the reception center but the residential area of the internal members.

Clotti stood in front of the door with an expressionless face. He nodded and said, "Black Star, follow me. Everyone's waiting."

Han Xiao walked out of the car and looked at Clotti with a strange expression.

The two of them had just met back at Urranrell's place not long ago. He had traveled there by carrier, while this guy had sprinted over so that he could be waiting for him in advance. Although Beyond Grade As' speed would be much quicker than land carriers, visualizing that image in his mind still felt quite comical.

They opened the door and entered.

As soon as they entered the house, the eyes of six different Beyond Grade As all looked over and stared at Han Xiao with curiosity.

Clotti looked for a seat and sat down, leaving Han Xiao standing alone.

Han Xiao scanned around. He was not unfamiliar with all six of them. They were all known Beyond Grade A allies of the Crimson Dynasty. There was even a member of the Ancient Ones.

However, among the three strongest people in the dynasty, only Clotti was present.

The seven people there all had different looks in their eyes. Some were filled with anticipation, some were cold, and some were curious. These Beyond Grade As all had different dynasty factions behind them, so their personal stand was not the same.

"So, you're Black Star from the Shattered Star Ring?" One of them sized Han Xiao up. When his eyes looked past the Evolution Cube, a tint of hostility seemed to have flashed for an instant.

"Who else did you think I was?" Han Xiao raised his brows and did not respond politely. Everyone there was a Beyond Grade A; he did not plan to keep a low profile. He would only be respected if he showed his strength.

"Of the four... oh, five Beyond Grade As in the Shattered Star Ring, both you and Heber have joined the Crimson Dynasty. Which one of you is stronger?" someone beside asked with curiosity.

"If you're so curious, why don't you try it out yourself?" Han Xiao shrugged. He did not want to be questioned while standing up, so he found a random seat and sat down.

These Beyond Grade A had no idea that although this was their first meeting, Han Xiao knew about them quite well and had a very clear idea of the situation in this room.

Among the seven people, Clotti was above all and looked calm and cold. He represented the ruler's confidant faction, so he only watched but did not interfere. Another Beyond Grade A who was close to the dynasty military's Youngsters Faction looked very interested in him and seemed to have the intention of wooing him. The other five more or less wanted to test him.

Seeing how Han Xiao did not take any steps back at all, they exchanged glances and saw a little bit of surprise in each others' eyes.

In the past, the newcomers came with the intention of making friends with them. These newcomers thought that everyone would be talking calmly and politely, while the older members would make this meeting into somewhat of a review and questioning section. They would keep asking provocative questions and watch the new Beyond Grade A suppress their anger and answer every question. Most people there had experienced this and left a dark history. Therefore, this became a tradition in accepting the newcomers.

If someone could not take it, they would speak with fists to determine their position in the future.

If it was a previously renowned neutral Beyond Grade A becoming an ally, only then would they give the newcomer face and restrain themselves.

Of course, Black Star, who had just become a Beyond Grade A, was not on that list.

However, this was only the start, and they had yet to even start the real provocation, but Black Star had already retaliated. It was clear that this newcomer was not planning to follow their plan.

It's probably because Heber shared his experience with him...

In their eyes, it looked like Han Xiao knew about their tradition, and Heber, who also left a dark history there, was from the Shattered Star Ring. Therefore, it was most likely that Black Star knew about this from him and did not want to let their plan succeed by speaking in this manner.

"Not going to happen..."

They secretly exchanged looks and made a plan.

"Hehe." The person who spoke first said coldly, "Black Star, I don't think you've realized what your position is."

"Oh? Mr. Star Slasher, what do you mean?" Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

Viru, a Beyond Grade A Pugilist of the War Soldier Branch. Among his nicknames were 'Star Slasher' and 'Fixed Star Splitter'. He came from the Primeval Star River, now an ally of the dynasty, and was operating tens of thousands of galactical Pugilist dojos in the Central Galaxy.

"This is the center of the universe, the Central Galaxy. Do you think this is the Shattered Star Ring that only has five Beyond Grade As? How dare you speak to us that manner..."

Boom!

Before he finished his sentence, Viru suddenly released his energy, which slashed the villa in two. The thick aura and his cold stare pressed onto Han Xiao. As if he was furious, he said word by word, "A newbie who has just entered the Beyond Grade A stage, who gave you the right to be this arrogant in front of us‽"

"Tsk." Expressionless, Clotti waved his hands and told the patrols who rushed there not to get close. Viru restrained his energy and did not let it spread out. Clotti did not stop Viru's action.

Other than the Beyond Grade A close to the Youngsters Faction who was shaking his head and did not speak, the others all had unfriendly expressions on their faces and stared at Han Xiao, pressuring him.

Even if Heber had told him the rules earlier, they did not believe that Black Star would not be afraid of offending all of them at once.

If Black Star continued to not step back, they did not mind teaching him a lesson. As for if that would anger Black Star... they all had Beyond Grade A organizations, so it did not matter.

The few of them secretly looked at Han Xiao's expression, hoping to find a tint of panic or fear on his face.

The sharp and aggressive aura was like a knife in Han Xiao's face. He narrowed his eyes and suddenly chuckled. "Alright, let's make things easier. We're all Beyond Grade As. If we have any conflicts, we can settle it by fighting."

Then, before everyone could respond, Han Xiao pointed at Viru. "You and I will fight, how about that?"

The others were surprised and even more interested.

This newcomer is deliberately issuing a challenge? How confident. Doesn't he know we're all seniors who've fought a very long time for the dynasty?

They initially wanted to bring sparring up to provoke Black Star into fighting, but they did not expect this guy to propose it first.

"Okay." Viru's expression looked irritated.

He had already showcased his energy, yet Black Star still wanted to challenge him. Did Black Star think that he had a chance of winning?

Viru would not allow his position to be threatened.

Han Xiao was calm. He had already guessed that only strength would earn him respect in the Beyond Grade A allies circle, so he had mentally prepared to fight long ago.

In order to befriend Beyond Grade As, he first had to show strength worth befriending.

This time, Clotti spoke slowly.

"Go fight outside the Psionic Seal Ring. Don't fight near the mother planet."

...

"Your Excellency, Black Star's meeting with the National Pillars was not pleasant. He challenged His Excellency Star Slasher to a spar. Clotti and the other National Pillar have gone along as well."

Hearing the report from the internal communicator, Urranrell said, "Clotti will take care of this. You guys don't have to worry about it."

"Understood."

"Hmm... go and notify Black Star's friends."

Then, Urranrell hung up the communicator and shook her head.

She did not like the tradition of bullying the newcomer between the Beyond Grade A allies, but she also did not want to force these Beyond Grade As to do anything unless absolutely necessary.

However, the private relationship between the dynasty's allies being bad might not be a bad thing. It would not affect their partnerships with the dynasty, and profit was the priority.

...

"What? He's fighting with those allies?"

After hearing what the emissary came to their doorsteps to say, Hila and the various guards' expressions changed drastically.

This time, Aesop spoke and comforted them. "Don't worry, it's just a test of strength between Beyond Grade As. Sparring is very normal. I've seen them do it before."

Sadly, not many people took what he said in.

"Let's go take a look." Ames did not say much and stepped out of the door.

Chapter 801: Spar

Outside the Psionic Seal Ring, Han Xiao and Viru floated in the cosmic space. A spaceship was looking there from not very far away.

The spaceship carried Clotti and the other Beyond Grade As, as well as Ames, Aesop, and the rest who had arrived later.

"It's been a long time, Aesop," that Ancient Ones member greeted with a fake smile.

"Ravenlaude, you're still alive," Aesop replied.

"Ever since you were kicked out of the Ancient Ones, I have yet to hear from you. So, it turns out you went to the most rural area, the Shattered Star Ring. Why, you couldn't make a living in any other Star Fields?" Ravenlaude said with a mocking tone.

"You've lived so long that your memories are failing you. Why do I remember that I left the Ancient Ones?" Aesop gave him a faint glance.

Among the Ancient Ones, Aesop did not have a good relationship with this person.

Back when Aesop left the Ancient Ones, other than because he did not want this title to prevent him from looking for trouble, it was also because he did not have a good relationship with some of the other members. As a powerful Oracle, he did not like to use his ability for unrelated people. When the times he rejected them started to pile up, it became the source of their conflict.

Ames did not know anyone, so she stood at the side and watched alone.

This was a chance to observe Black Star's strength. Other than Clotti, who was not very interested, everyone else was focused and looked forward to the two of them to start the fight.

They knew how strong Viru was; his combat capability had been tested countless times through battle. Therefore, the only question was—how long could Black Star hold on?

They had heard that Black Star had the 'Indestructible Body' nickname and that the toughness of his physical body seemed to be on par with the Tyrant's. They wondered if he would be able to stop Viru's sky splitting blade.

Han Xiao activated his mechanical suit. The helmet covered his face and hid his expression. Then, he opened the secondary dimension gate. The mechanical army swarmed out and filled the battlefield instantly.

Quite a lot, but in front of me, these are all minions. Viru snorted in his mind. His muscle violently expanded, and a light blue flame burned on the surface of his body.

A surging flame concentrated on his palm and kept extending, forming a hundreds-of-meters-long blue energy sword so dense that it almost looked like it had a physical form.

Pugilists had different branches. The War Soldier Branch focused on fighting with blades, but it was different from being a Mechanical Pugilist. Mechanical Pugilists completely relied on weapons to fight and used Mechanical Force to enhance their weapons, while Pugilists only used weapons to better their own skills. Their damage source was still their own Pugilist flame.

With a deep breath, the flames gushed into the hundreds of meters long blade. Viru slashed multiple times consecutively. Blue blades of light shot out and created empty areas within the formation of the mechanical army. The power of those blades of light dropped as they destroyed mechanical soldiers, from completely shattering the first ones to only heavily damaging the ones after.

Han Xiao immediately activated various bonus abilities and controlled his mechanical army to join him in the battle.

Viru was surrounded by tons of mechanical soldiers. His sword danced so quickly that it formed a sphere. Blades of light continuously shot out from it and destroyed the formation of the mechanical soldiers, causing tremendous damage. It was as if a tornado had appeared in the cosmic space.

As the combat information kept refreshing, Han Xiao tutted in his mind. This guy's damage is indeed high. Maybe even Heber is weaker in this respect.

Compared to Heber's heavy and firm offense, Viru mainly focused on swiftness and sharpness. His area attacks were not bad, and his individual target damage was even more horrifying. Earlier, when colossal defense-focused Giant Soldier turned its shield to full capacity in an attempt to stop Viru's attack, Viru still easily slashed it in two without stopping.

Nonetheless, Han Xiao did not randomly pick this opponent. Viru's attack damage was indeed high, but he was inferior compared to Heber in one aspect... his tankiness!

Although this guy was also a Pugilist and had a ton of damage reduction talents, he did not have a very essential core tanky talent... he was not immune to True Damage!

Viru had a fifty-percent True Damage reduction talent, which was way weaker than True Damage Immunity. True Damage was still much more terrifying than normal damage even when halved!

When comparing Heber and Viru, Han Xiao could only fight head-on with the former, but for the latter, he just so happened to be the type of enemy Han Xiao indirectly countered!

The blades of light shot out in all directions. The mechanical army formation took quite a lot of damage, so the mechanical army dealt with it by spreading and attacking from further distances.

Under the focus fire of psionic cannons, Viru's blade formed a complete sphere. He used a certain ability, turning the blades of light around him into a special kind of shield, blocking most of the psionic attacks. The explosions were blocked by the sphere of light.

However, the mechanical army was too large, and their attacks were too concentrated. Viru's defense could not stop all of them. Occasionally, psionic attacks would pass through the blade shield and land on his body, shaking his protective energy flames.

Feeling the obliteration of the cells in his body, the look in Viru's eyes changed.

So powerful... prolonged battles are not suitable for me. I need to attack his physical body.

Having realized that, Viru's energy flame vibrated. The shield around his body expanded and turned into an impact wave, blowing away the mechanical soldiers around him.

Then, he held his sword backhand. His entire body turned into a blue phantom and charged toward Han Xiao, leaving countless afterimages behind. When he reached the frontline of the mechanical army, he turned from holding his sword backhand to front hand, striking forward. It was like all the afterimages were concentrated on this attack.

Star Slasher Style Technique—Blade Shadow!

Thousands of blades of light erupted at the same time and spread outward in all directions, instantly shattering the formation of the mechanical army in one direction and penetrating many layers of defenses. The shattered mechanical parts splashed everywhere.

Han Xiao immediately clenched his fist. Blue-gold Mechanical Force shot out from the Void Dimension, grabbing all the parts like a lightning net and connecting them together.

[Waste Modification]!

[Advanced Machinery Construction]!

The shattered parts became mechanical soldiers again.

However, in just this short instant, Viru disappeared. As if he had teleported, he passed through the layers of defenses and appeared right in front of Han Xiao. The sword in his hand returned to normal size from hundreds of meters long. With the more concentrated Pugilist energy sword in his hand, he slashed right down!

"It's not my first time fighting a Mechanic," Viru said with an expressionless face. It was not a secret that Mechanics had the Waste Modification ability. Being very experienced, he knew that a Mechanic would definitely use it. Using that opportunity, he used a special mobility ability and instantly got close to Han Xiao. He was a Pugilist focused on speed, so he had more ways of closing the distance than Heber.

Swoosh!

The blade slashed right through Han Xiao's body without any resistance, as if it had cut him in half. However, Viru did not feel like he had slashed through anything. His expression changed instantly.

The halved 'Han Xiao' suddenly disappeared. His real body was little more than ten meters away.

Earlier, Han Xiao had used some kind of illusion device and misguided Viru's senses. Deceiving a Beyond Grade A Pugilist who could lock the target with his energy was very difficult, but this special illusion device was one of the high-level machines that Han Xiao had built that could be used in Beyond Grade A battles. It could create an illusion that perfectly simulated even his own energy presence, and it had a quite long cooldown.

Having missed one attack, Viru's movement did not stop. He turned and attacked another time, quicker and swifter. His blade extended and slashed onto Han Xiao's chest like a whip.

Star Slasher Style Technique—Whip Slash!

This attack was initially targeted at Han Xiao's chest, but Viru changed its direction and targeted Han Xiao's head.

However, Han Xiao's response shocked him—he did not dodge at all and went toward it directly.

The blade cut Han Xiao's mechanical suit right open, slashing across his forehead. Blood gushed down from his head.

Viru was shocked. Before he could withdraw his blade, he saw Han Xiao grab onto his arm like he was completely unharmed and punched right onto his chest.

Boom!

The vibration echoed in Viru's body. Tons of cells were destroyed and quickly born through Viru's energy. As the process repeated, he felt a strong pain in his body.

[Machinery Apostilization] and [Mechanical Force—Emperor's Power] gave Han Xiao a lot of attributes, so his attacks were much stronger.

Then, Han Xiao's bloody wound recovered right under Viru's nose. The nanoparticles of the mechanical suit fixed the broken part as well.

This recovery speed... Viru's pupils constricted.

This time, the mechanical army behind Viru turned their barrels and fired at the two of them.

Just as Viru was about to back away, two enhanced Oathkeepers appeared beside Han Xiao and held him back.

With a swing of his blade, he slashed an Oathkeeper's body but met a tremendous force of resistance. He could not cut it in half with one slash. The blue-gold Mechanical Force flashed inside the wounds of these two Oathkeepers.

These two Oathkeepers were elite mechanical soldiers that had received bonuses from the [Emperor's Gift]. Even Beyond Grade As would not be able to destroy them in just one attack.

Unable to break the Oathkeepers into pieces in one slash, Viru reacted quickly and hastily blew them away with an energy impact wave. However, he was attacked by the Oathkeepers at the same time. Psionic cannon shots landed on his chest, and his movement paused for an instant again.

The psionic cannon fired from behind him. Chains of shots landed on his back. Viru was not willing to give up on the opportunity of being able to attack Han Xiao at such a close distance, so he released a defensive shield behind him that barely blocked the focus fire for an instant before attacking Han Xiao violently.

The battlefield left its original area and kept shifting.

The two of them fought at close range. Viru's blade slashed through Han Xiao's body time after time, cutting away parts of his mechanical suit and his flesh again and again. However, he recovered at a visible speed, and his wounds healed in seconds.

The longer Viru fought, the more shocked he was. He had heard about Han Xiao's 'Indestructible Body' nickname, but he had never expected it to be so powerful.

Since some time ago, Clotti, who was watching from afar, had stopped being uninterested. He was now focusing on their battle with a serious look on his face.

Han Xiao's recovery speed shocked even him.

He had never seen any Mechanic with a physique so strong that it could match up to even a Pugilist.

"A newbie who has just advanced shouldn't have such combat capability," one of them said with shock. He voiced the thought that was in everyone's mind.

Han Xiao used [Repel - Thorns] and [Void Dimension Jump] consecutively to guard against his opponent's attacks. The two of them fought at close range for a short period of time before the enormous mechanical army finally held Viru back again. Han Xiao finally got out of the close-range battle.

After taking Viru's chain of powerful attacks, Han Xiao was close to unharmed. At least the others could not see what damage he had taken on the surface.

Han Xiao patted his chest and opened his arms.

Before Viru could respond, the mechanical army's attacks became stronger. With the help of all kinds of traps, Viru temporarily became passive.

At this time, many enormous mechanical barrels appeared behind Han Xiao. Psionic energy started to concentrate and gave off a powerful energy reaction.

Planetary Obliteration Cannon!

The expression on Viru's face changed drastically.

Come on, using this kind of war level weapon has exceeded the context of sparring!

Suddenly, from the mechanical army around Viru, hundreds of electromagnetic chains dashed out and tied onto Viru from all directions.

Viru tried to escape, but to his shock, he realized that he could not escape from it in an instant. It was as if these chains were tentacles. They could direct his strength away.

Extreme Electromagnetic Locked Catcher, single target control type mechanical trap. This was equipment that Han Xiao had built with the Cutting-Edge Knowledge [Activation Theory]. It could temporarily control even Beyond Grade As and was considered as a high-level machine. It hid within the mechanical army and activated at a crucial moment, capturing Viru right away.

The next moment, the teams of mechanical soldiers fired on Viru, and psionic attacks rained like a thunderstorm!

The light illuminated Viru's drastically changed expression. Flames all over his body immediately erupted, turning into blades of flames, and quickly spun around his body, forming a layer of shield-like defenses.

Blade Control—Energy Barrier!

The sphere of light expanded. Han Xiao fired the Secondary Sky Planetary Obliteration Cannons that had completed their energy charge. Enormous dark-blue beams of light gushed out and headed right to Viru.

When the beams were only halfway through, clusters of dark energy suddenly appeared on the attack route and clashed with the psionic energy beams. The two forms of energy caused chains of explosions, continuously expanding in the cosmic space.

On the other side, dozens of dark energy barriers stopped the focus fire of the army and gave Viru time to breathe.

Viru hastily escaped from the trap, activated some kind of mobility ability, turned into a stream of blue light, and escaped the battlefield. He hovered at the side with a pale face, looking like he was more than slightly injured.

If it were Heber, these attacks would just have been tickles. However, Viru's health had been reduced quite a lot by the True Damage attacks.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and made the mechanical army stop attacking before looking at the spaceship.

Clotti was standing behind the porthole and had one hand raised. He was the one who had controlled the dark energy and interfered with their battle earlier.

"The spar has ended," Clotti said in the communication channel. "This shall be... considered a draw."

Draw?

The others had different looks on their faces.

They knew exactly that this was just a way of saying it so Viru would not be humiliated. Just from the situation earlier, Han Xiao had won undoubtedly. Han Xiao had showcased his combat strength.

With his powerful recovery ability and enormous mechanical army, as well as his oddly powerful attacks, a Mechanic like him had close to no weaknesses. They were shocked, and they put away the slight underestimation they had for Han Xiao because of him being a newcomer and his Shattered Star Ring origin.

Han Xiao had earned their respect with his strength.

Viru's expression was not looking good. As the one that had been challenged, he had initially been completely confident. However, he had instead become the target for the newcomer to showcase his strength. He felt very embarrassed and displeased.

However, the opponent had gained the upper hand with valid ways, so he had nothing to say and could only feel unhappy inside.

Hearing what Clotti said, Han Xiao did not deny it and withdrew his mechanical army.

The result did not matter. As long as the goal of showcasing his strength was achieved, it was enough for him.

Furthermore, if Viru had gone all out, his explosive power would only have been higher than Heber's. It would not be easy for Han Xiao to deal with even with his powerful recovery speed.

One reason he had gotten the upper hand in the spar was because of the combat style counter; another was the nature of the battle. It looked like he had completely overwhelmed Viru, but if it had been a real battle, Viru might not have made the same mistakes.

I have to become stronger.

Among Beyond Grade As, he was very strong in long-duration battles, but his raw strength was not high enough.

He had accumulated a large sum of EXP. When the EXP penalty was over, he would be able to level up again.

He estimated that only then would he be able to obtain a higher position among the Beyond Grade As.

He returned to the spaceship and walked into the cabin. The others approached him.

Han Xiao noticed that there was no longer inspection in their eyes, and now there was some respect. Han Xiao nodded in his mind.

Through this spar, his strength had been recognized. Now, he had officially been accepted into this circle.

Viru walked in after Han Xiao. With a long face, he turned around and said with a deep voice, "If there's a chance in the future, we have to spar again."

"Then I guess there won't be any chances." Han Xiao raised his brows. With no benefits, why would I fight you? It's not like I'm a battle maniac.

Speaking of which, it seemed like most Pugilists were battle maniacs...

Chapter 802: Eat and Sleep Before Fighting EsGod

The spaceship returned to the mother planet. On it, the few Beyond Grade A allies no longer put on any airs. It seemed that they had genuinely accepted Han Xiao as a comrade, formally introducing themselves.

Han Xiao had long known the names of all the people and was merely going through the formalities. Some of them were related to the dynasty, some were characters who had influential power in the Central Galaxy, but only two of them were big names throughout a few Star Fields.

They came from the Sea of Star Spirits and the Primeval Star River respectively. The latter was a Beyond Grade A who leaned toward militaristic Beyond Grade As. Thus, within this crew, his attitude was the most favorable.

This guy was not that old, and his name was Beyoni. He had the nickname of 'Incineration' due to his Esper Ability, Original Source of Fire. He was able to ignite all types of things from a microscopic level, even if they seemed non-flammable at first glance. This was not limited to matter, as he could even burn energy. The most famous story was that a wandering planet had once been ignited by him, and all the trees, dirt, and metal were burned, turning it into a scorched planet.

Sometime ago, Han Xiao had spent some time with the elites of the dynasty, and the eyewitnesses had told him how he had taken care of Teny. This was interpreted as a sign of goodwill for the dynasty, as Teny was considered one of the core figures even though he had not actually entered the upper echelons, or else he would not be given the chance to undergo the evolution process.

Thus, because of factional reasons, Beyoni intended to make friends, and Han Xiao would naturally not reject. The two of them talked for quite a bit.

Other than him, another person that Han Xiao felt he needed to be careful of was Ravenlaude from the Ancient Ones. He was neither cold nor warm toward Han Xiao, and thus, he did not purposely associate himself with the other party.

The Ancient Ones were a loose alliance whose members were all strange people. Some of them were Beyond Grade A Supers—some possessed special abilities. Their common point was that they all had a long life span and lived far longer than other creatures. In Galaxy, the Ancient Ones were one of the most well-known organizations, with members from the three Universal Civilizations also within.

For example, on the side of the Crimson Dynasty, there were two members of the Ancient Ones. One was naturally Ravenlaude, and the other was one of the three strongest National Pillars.

The Federation of Light as well as the Arcane Church also had a few people inside the Ancient Ones. One of them would be the leader of the Mechanic Empire, Manison. While their empire was considered as one of their strongest allies, they possessed high independence. After all, he was the head of the entire Mechanic Empire. With so much power in his hands, it naturally turned into a faction of its own.

The Ancient Ones represented a huge pool of resources and connections. It was a pity that Han Xiao himself had not yet reached the required age, or else he would have given it a try.

Because of the previous spar, Han Xiao had obtained a certain level of respect. As the crowd returned to the mother planet, a discussion began on the spaceship. Since everyone had already acknowledged Han Xiao, so he was able to mix in with the rest.

A few of them required borrowing the Evolution Cube to use, but Han Xiao did not agree immediately. For the Beyond Grade As, this was like adding wings to a tiger. There was no free lunch in this world, and while Clotti had a direct relationship with the dynasty and was thus able to enjoy such a privilege, the same could not be said of the other allies. Without any benefits, Han Xiao would not allow them to improve their capabilities. After all, they had no relationship.

Hearing that Han Xiao wanted some benefits in exchange, the group had differing thoughts and did not immediately express their stand.

The majority originally thought that Black Star would be more pliable the first time they met and immediately take out the Evolution Cube to please them. However, Black Star turned out to be more difficult to deal with, so their plan went awry, and they could only wait till a later time to use the cube. As great figures themselves, they could not display any form of desperation.

After bidding goodbye to the group, Han Xiao and Ames returned to their residence. Seeing the duo return, Hila and the rest felt reassured.

This also counts as my official appearance within the circle of advanced combatants in the advanced civilizations. I'm now stepping onto the stage of the Central Galaxy, Han Xiao thought to himself. This was something long within his plans.

Having more friends would mean getting things done was easier. By befriending this group, he would also be able to utilize some of their connections. Of course, he would appear the same in the eyes of the others, and this was using each other's networks to one's benefit.

There were also disadvantages, however. They would be treated as chips on the table of the dynasty by the other organizations and would attract the attention of the greater organization. The hostility and strength of their opponents would naturally be higher in the future.

There was no way around it. To obtain so many resources from the dynasty, it would be a pipe dream to think that there were no conditions attached to it.

The Central Galaxy is controlled by the three Universal Civilizations, and its organizations do not have the freedom to develop and are not suitable for major operations. It is still necessary for them to look outward to the Shattered Star Ring and Flickering World for development. For this area... I'll just leave a contact point. After this is done, it would be better for me to stay away from this area unless necessary.

If one wished to increase their standing within the Central Galaxy, it need not be done within the area. The best way was always to be able to run an area properly. If one's value increased, it would be simple to obtain a rise in standing.

The same night, Clotti shared the information of Han Xiao's spar with Viru with Urranrell and gave his opinion about Han Xiao at the same time.

Even in the late night, Urranrell's office was still fully lit. She stared at Clotti and asked solemnly, "What do you think about the chances of Black Star being able to raise to a higher level in the future?"

"There is a possibility." Clotti simply phrased it as such.

The pioneers had already broken into this stage more than tens of thousands of years ago. After researching for so long, they had also started to give a proper classification to the tiers for the Beyond Grade A realm. With Black Star's current age and his lack of an apparent weakness in his fighting style, there was definitely room for growth in the future. Most might not be able to keep up with his pace.

Clotti was not stingy with the evaluation of Han Xiao. In his long lifetime, he had seen countless Beyond Grade As. Some of them had exhausted all their potential breaking through from the Calamity Grade, destined to stay at their current level forever. Some of them could continue to grow even after, and those were the geniuses among geniuses. In his eyes, Black Star belonged to the latter group.

However, he had already seen far too many of them, such that he no longer liked to communicate and meet with new people. Moreover, Clotti was directly related to the dynasty, and with his position, he need not butter up anyone. Thus, he did not show much attention toward Han Xiao.

After all, not every Beyond Grade A was like our Great Mechanic Han, who liked to have support and nurturing.

Urranrell leaned back on her chair, a thoughtful expression on her face.

"Since that's the case, it would be more useful for him to stay on the fringes of the Star Fields. His current mentality is geared toward developing the Flickering World, but after that, he might come over to the Central Galaxy to develop... However, there is sufficient manpower here, and we do not need him."

The three Universal Civilizations would occasionally have friction within the Central Galaxy, but because it was their base camp, they would never escalate into an all-out war. Thus, there was no need for so many Beyond Grade As to hold helm in the dynasty. They just needed a sufficient number for deterrence, and too many would instead waste their resources. It would be better to send the Beyond Grade As into other Star Fields to expand the control of the dynasty. This was the meaning behind the phrase National Pillars.

However, since the Central Galaxy was the heart of the Universe, countless people wished to have the right to speak there. To Urranrell, the number of allies they had there was too saturated, and she did not like to have so many people relying on the name of the dynasty to develop their organizations in this place.

Since Black Star had brought over his portable mobile fortress, it meant that he wanted to establish a branch there. To give face to her allies, Urranrell was willing to provide some help, but she was planning to secretly limit the expansion speed of the Black Star Army in the Central Galaxy. This was to stop him from coming over to the Central Galaxy, instead retaining his thoughts toward the development in Shattered Star Ring or Flickering World.

Urranrell believed in Clotti's judgement. Since he mentioned that Black Star had the possibility of advancing into the next tier, he would definitely not be wrong. As such, Black Star would be an important chess piece for them...

Since he was an important chess piece, he naturally needed to be placed at the proper position to display the best effects.

The news of Black Star being officially received by the Dynasty Ruler was spread throughout the channels of the dynasty. Based on what Han Xiao knew, they would not hide something like this and would rather announce that they had new chips.

His name now formally entered the sight of all the major organizations in the Central Galaxy. Han Xiao had no foundation in the Central Galaxy, however, and was unable to understand the responses of these organizations.

Over the next few days, the Dynasty arranged for the mother planet's garrisoned troops to undergo the transformation of the Evolution Cube, and Han Xiao focused on cooperating with them.

It took several days to finally complete the evolution of all the dynasty's garrisoned troops.

During this time, the Black Star Army did not idle. With the help of the dynasty, they used a small piece of land in the dynasty to create a simple office, only leaving a small group of staff for a long term stay for easy communication. Before they left, they had assessed this group of people and picked only those that were willing to stay in the Central Galaxy.

As for the mobile satellite bases of the Black Star Army, the dynasty would naturally not allow them to settle next to the mother planet, so they gave Han Xiao a star map, allowing him to choose a spot in the territory of the dynasty to set up the sub-base.

There was no need to hesitate in choosing since Han Xiao had long drawn up a draft.

Since it was meant to dig out more leeks to farm, the location of the subbase naturally would be the main activity area of the players.

Due to some matters, Han Xiao chose to temporarily stay behind on the mother planet. He commanded his troops to leave without him. Because of the stability and high security within the dynasty, his army did not require him to open the base there.

The reason he had chosen to stay behind, other than to accompany Ames and the rest sightseeing, was because he was planning to obtain some Ultimate Knowledge.

Urranrell had sent the list of tasks organized by her people over to Han Xiao, and after choosing, he had finally selected a mission.

The general miscellaneous tasks were not enough, and only the trickier ones would entitle them to obtain Ultimate Knowledge. What Han Xiao chose was a task that required a Beyond Grade A to participate... the clearance of the remnant Fallen Ark forces!

In other words, fighting EsGod!

The three star fields of the Central Galaxy were separated by a desolate universe belt, which was sensitive and difficult to manage. As a result, bandits and outlaws who dared not remain in the three Star Fields had poured into the border belt, forming a piece of polluted land.

This desolate universe belt occupied a large area. During the initial periods of the war, the three Universal Civilizations had fought their brains out on their doorsteps, and their battlefield had turned into this desolate universe belt. Countless planets had turned into barren wastelands because of their attacks.

A large number of outlaws hid themselves within, making them difficult to locate. With the border area connected to the desolate universe belt of the Central Galaxy, the connection between the two made it impossible for them to be eradicated.

This sensitive ground was not easily governed. Besides, the three Universal Civilizations had stargates connecting to each other, so most people would not even choose to travel along the desolate universe belt. Thus, its impact on the security of the Central Galaxy was not too huge.

EsGod's team usually hid within the seams of the borders along the desolate universe belt. Their presence had always been a secret, and only recently did they suddenly reveal their tracks, being caught by the dynasty's surveillance.

With the notoriety of EsGod, the three Universal Civilizations had long treated this job as ordinary, as though their daily tasks would be to eat, sleep, and fight with EsGod, thus the name 'Routine Clearance'.

Han Xiao still had a grudge to settle with EsGod. While EsGod had made him an offer, Han Xiao would not regard EsGod as an ally or friend. Since he was based inside the Lawful Faction currently, he had to draw a line between himself and this sort of notorious outlaw.

Speaking of which, it had always been EsGod that looked for him to create trouble. This was the first time that he was paying back his dues.

If it was not for the opportunity given by the dynasty, he would not have been able to do so. Having a backer was truly awesome.

However, he was a little anxious toward the strange abilities of EsGod, so he did not move solo, instead inviting a few Beyond Grade A allies of his for this operation.

Clotti had a position and thus refused without even thinking. The rest of them also made excuses, as they did not wish to provoke EsGod. Only one person agreed to his invite.

"When do we set off?"

The communicator showed Beyoni's horn-covered head, the volcanic texture for skin, and the fluttering around him of agile fire snakes. He was no human but rather an Esper of the Pyre Tribe.

"Tomorrow. I've already informed the people in the dynasty, and they will send us over." Han Xiao stroked his chin.

He had settled everything on the dynasty's mother planet, and there was nothing left for him to do. The next step would be to complete the two plans that he had in the Central Galaxy.

The first was to obtain the Ultimate Knowledge, and the second was to develop his leeks. The latter only needed the brand of the Black Star Army and did not require him to be there in person.

"It will be dangerous with just the two of us. EsGod's fleet is too large, and he himself is dangerous." Beyoni shook his head.

"We don't just have two Beyond Grade As here."

He glanced at Ames to the side. Upon knowing of this matter, Ames had automatically volunteered, as though she was worried about being left out, and more people would always be welcome.

Seeing him look over, Ames gave a light smile, as though she was raring to go.

Chapter 803: No Coincidence

An ordinary dynasty spaceship leisurely left Planet Crimson Ring, and within it, Han Xiao stood at the porthole, looking out at the shrinking dynasty mother planet, his expression passive.

Having accepted this routine clearing task and notified the dynasty, they had specially arranged an escort spaceship to see them off. The entire process was settled that day, with no delay. Thus, the three of them, together with Hila and the others, boarded the dynasty's spaceship and set off to the garrison base located at the border to participate in the removal of the Fallen Ark forces.

"This time, I really came in a hurry and left in a hurry." Han Xiao's eyes looked at the gradually shrinking mother planet as he mused.

He had only stayed on the mother planet for a few days, not even close to the time he had spent on the road. He did not wait long, leaving the moment he finished his activities there, swift and decisive.

This trip allowed him to meet with the Dynasty Ruler as well as the National Pillars of the dynasty to deepen his ties, expanding his network in the dynasty. His image within the dynasty was now clearer, and with the Crimson Dynasty's well wishes, he would also become one of the backbones of the dynasty in the future.

"The dynasty's troops have finished organizing themselves and are just waiting for a Beyond Grade A Super to take the fort. Through the stargate, we will converge with them in another four to five days."

Beyoni walked over from the side as he spoke, spitting out little fire seeds.

The Crimson Ring Star System was the center of the dynasty, and they were moving to the edge of the Star Field. Needing only four to five days was not because of the short distance but because the transportation of the Central Galaxy was much better compared to that of the Shattered Star Ring. This was because the three Universal Civilizations had planted a multitude of stargates within the Central Galaxy to form a quick transport channel. If they converted this to time taken in the Shattered Star Ring, the journey might have taken longer than a month.

"Before this, did you participate in any related activities?" Han Xiao suddenly asked.

"Oh, I've only taken part in the encirclement and suppression of the Fallen Ark twice. This is the third time for me. Those Beyond Grade As who reside in the Central Galaxy have participated in such actions," Beyoni noted.

This is really eat-sleep-fight, and that bunch of allies who made excuses saying they did not wish to provoke EsGod did so only because they did not wish to group up with me... Han Xiao's mouth curled up.

"Then, had EsGod practically fought with all the Beyond Grade A people in the three Civilizations?"

"You could say so. However, the majority of times we only came into contact with the doppelganger of EsGod. Only during large operations will we come across his true body. However, people on Clotti's level would be in charge of such operations because the true body of EsGod is far too strong. I've heard that more than two Beyond Grade As have already fallen at his hands. We only have so many Beyond Grade As, so this can be considered a terrific result."

Beyoni shook his head.

Because of his deliberate attempt to foster ties, Han Xiao's relationship toward him was closer than to the rest of the allies.

Hearing his words, Han Xiao nodded to express his understanding, his eyes flashing.

The capability of EsGod was well known, but to the three Civilizations, if they gritted their teeth, they would be able to get rid of this threat. There was no need for them to endure EsGod for so long. There had to be something more hidden.

"This time, there are three Beyond Grade A Supers holding the fort, so even if we're unlucky and encounter his true body, we can still retreat without losses," Beyoni said.

Unlucky? Heh, there's an eighty percent chance we'll meet with his true body this time.

Han Xiao smirked to himself. EsGod revealing some tracks the moment he entered the dynasty's mother planet was no coincidence.

Upon thinking about the contents of when EsGod had contacted him, it was likely because of this reason. However, he had still chosen to participate in this cleaning operation.

Putting those thoughts aside, he opened the interface to look. The cleaning operation missions were placed within, with great rewards.

_____________________

Dynasty Battle Operation: Fallen Ark (Repeatable)

Mission Introduction: The Fallen Ark, the paradise of the thugs in the Universe are evil and notorious, is constantly besieged by the three Universal Civilizations. Today, the Crimson Dynasty has discovered the whereabouts of one of the Fallen Ark's groups, and you decided to participate in this battle and contribute your strength.

Reminder: This is a faction series mission. You can complete the below requirements during this mission.

Elite Soldier: A cumulative kill count of over 2,000 enemies. Reward: 3,800,000 Experience, +20 Crimson Dynasty Contribution Points.

Fierce General: A cumulative kill count of over 200 Supers at least at Grade C. Reward: 8,100,000 Experience, +30 Crimson Dynasty Contribution Points.

Street Cleaner: A cumulative kill of over 10,000 enemies. Reward: 13,350,000 Experience, +50 the Crimson Dynasty Contribution Points.

...

Beheader: Kill the Fleet Commander. Reward: 120,000,000 Experience, +220 the Crimson Dynasty Contribution Points.

Face Off Against EsGod (I): Deplete a cumulative total of 0.5% of EsGod's HP (either to the true body or its copies). Reward: 200,000,000 Experience, +350 Crimson Dynasty Contribution Points.

Face Off Against EsGod (II): Deplete a cumulative total of 5% of EsGod's HP (either to the true body or its copies). Reward: 1,500,000,000 Experience, +550 Crimson Dynasty Contribution Points.

Face Off Against EsGod (III): Deplete a cumulative total of 15% of EsGod's HP (either to the true body or its copies). Reward: 6,500,000,000 Experience, +900 Crimson Dynasty Contribution Points.

Face Off Against EsGod (IV): Succeed in joining forces with the Crimson Dynasty troops to eliminate a doppelganger of EsGod. Every 1% of contribution effort made in battle will reward: 250,000,000 Experience, +80 Crimson Dynasty Contribution Point, and an EsGod Character Summon Card.

_____________________

This was not a one-off opportunity. As long as there was another cleaning operation, this mission would appear once more.

The Crimson Dynasty was one of the top organizations in Galaxy, so the rewards were the standard of the middle to later versions, involving the Beyond Grade A level. The highest rewards were worth tens of billions of experience.

This time, the Fallen Ark fleet was discovered near the frontier of the dynasty, so it was the troops belonging to the dynasty that were deployed.

Han Xiao had accepted this task because he saw the ample reward.

This was so for the [Face Off Against EsGod] series reward. Ninety percent of the potential rewards came from those mission requirements. This meant that it would be challenging, and most players could only complete the basic requirements of killing the enemy troops, since it was almost impossible to cause damage to EsGod. Even if the mission requirements were for cumulative damage, it was just too difficult.

However, it was a different case for him. When he was only at the Calamity Grade, he had been beaten black and blue by EsGod, but right now, even if the true body of EsGod was present, he might not be able to defeat it, but it would not pose any trouble to him.

Players needed to obtain a total of twelve thousand Contribution Points from a Universal Civilization in order to exchange for Ultimate Knowledge. However, his current identity was now different from theirs, and he had a discount of fifty percent. Only six thousand points were needed for one Ultimate Knowledge.

The stronger the faction, the harder it would be to increase favorability. In order to obtain Ultimate Knowledge in the past, the players had almost burst their livers from working. This sort of cleaning operation was the most popular. Since Han Xiao did not wish to stay too long in the Central Galaxy, he prepared to take full advantage of this mission to rack up his favorability.

In the entire mission list given by the dynasty, only this mission temporarily met his requirements, and it was also the most convenient.

This was also an opportunity for him to separate himself from EsGod and send a signal to him.

Han Xiao suddenly remembered something and asked, "That's right. How is it living out in the Primeval Star River? What's your relationship with the Mechanic Empire?"

Beyoni had belonged to the Pyre Demon Tribe before he advanced to Beyond Grade A. Currently, he had kept his original appearance as part of the Pyre Demon Tribe. He led his clan within the Primeval Star River, and while they led a life like thieves, they could still be considered bigshots in the Primeval Star River.

The Mechanic Empire was situated in the Primeval Star River, so Beyoni would definitely recognize him.

"Manison? Why are you asking?" Beyoni was confused.

"After all, he's a Beyond Grade A from the Mechanic profession, so I've admired him for a long time." Han Xiao casually gave an excuse.

Beyoni did not suspect a thing. "We seldom come in contact, but his influence is deeply entrenched in the Primeval Star River, far more than mine. If you wish to visit him, I can help you, but he belongs to the Federation of Light, so it might not be a good idea to visit him in private."

"You're thinking too much. The Universal Civilizations will never restrict our private meetings."

"Oh, but I don't like to associate with people from other organizations." Beyoni shook his head.

Han Xiao smiled in return. While he was not prepared to completely offend the Mechanic Empire, Aroshia's issue made him pay more attention to it.

As for the visitation, he was not lying. He was genuinely interested in Manison's 'Indestructible Mechanic Empire'. However, this was not the time to pay a visit. The exploration of the Flickering World was imminent, and he did not have the time to run off to the Primeval Star River.

However, upon mentioning the Mechanic Empire, Han Xiao could not help but remember an old archenemy of his—Thousand Shadows.

This guy did not seem to have acted for several years. Han Xiao surmised that he had given up, but the [Prey] mission still hung on his interface without disappearing.

I should pay a visit to the Abyss of Stars at some point.

He had not forgotten how much trouble that guy had caused for him. Now that his wings were growing, it was time to settle old debts.

...

Amid the rifts around the border of the Central Galaxy, a huge fleet was slowly cruising. This was the branch fleet of the Fallen Ark.

In the main flagship was a palace. The ground was covered in energy transmission loops that were connected to the throne in the center. A doppelganger of EsGod sat on the throne, and the energy core of the spaceship constantly flowed through, sending energy to it, as though it was a battery pack charging EsGod up.

At this moment, the main consciousness of EsGod was descending upon this doppelganger.

"Not sure whom the Crimson Dynasty will employ this time for the Beyond Grade A Super that will hold the fort." EsGod was musing. "My intelligence stated that Black Star has recently appeared in the Crimson Dynasty. Will he come over to find me?"

He had learned about Black Star's trip to the Central Galaxy more than half a month ago. If Black Star wished to perform the trade with him, he would need an opportunity to get in contact, so EsGod had intentionally revealed some of his traces to the dynasty to create an opportunity for him.

He could not easily leave the Central Galaxy. Thus, if he wished to allow his true body to utilize the Evolution Cube, he could only invite Black Star to his door. In order to prevent any blackmailing or threats, Black Star would not search for him on his own, so he had to provide a plausible excuse.

"He should understand my intentions..."

After thinking about it for a while, EsGod shook his head.

He did not doubt Black Star's perception, but since Black Star had not contacted him. It was likely that he had not decided as to if he wished to perform the trade.

In this situation, EsGod felt that Han Xiao might not come in contact with him.

...

"Black Star has already set off. Beyoni will watch over him."

In Tarunamir Palace of the Dynasty Ruler, Clotti wore an unreadable expression as he read Urranrell the intelligence report.

Urranrell put down the documents in her hand, rubbing her eyes. "He chose to fight with EsGod, which is out of my expectations. In addition, the timing is a little too coincidental. He brought the Evolution Cube with him, and EsGod is also interested in that thing. We must take precautions."

Initially, it should not have been the concern of a Dynasty Ruler like her as to which mission Han Xiao had picked, but she felt something suspicious about this, so she could not help but start to pay attention.

To the dynasty, the matter of EsGod attempting to steal the Evolution Cube was no secret. Han Xiao had taken the Evolution Cube to fight with him and could be seeking revenge, but it could also be for other things. While Black Star appeared as a new ally, with the dynasty taking care of his every matter, it was also a form of surveillance on him.

Beyoni accepting Han Xiao's invite was partly because he had a good relationship with him and partly because of Clotti's request. In addition to providing protection, he also wished to monitor Han Xiao's movements.

One always needed to have their guard up toward others, and the dynasty was not willing to see any of their allies come into contact with EsGod.

"Black Star's information shows that he is good at cooperation, working along the borders of many different organizations. To have built up his foundation to where he is today, he is definitely not someone that is easily satisfied..." Urranrell opened her eyes wide, her gaze cold and indifferent. "I hope he will not be too arrogant and attempt the same thing, thinking that he can deceive the dynasty."

Chapter 804: Main Body

A couple of days later, in the desolate universe belt, the small spaceship with Han Xiao and the others on it approached a large Crimson Dynasty fleet. This fleet belonged to the dynasty's border defense army, the 36th Division. This was the team tasked to eliminate the Fallen Ark. They were waiting to rendezvous with the dynasty's Beyond Grade As.

After checking the various passes and confirming their identity, the small spaceship entered the fleet's formation and connected with the square Soldier Grade Heavy Main Ship that looked like a coffin.

Whoosh!

The path opened, and Han Xiao and the rest entered the main ship's cabin. Officers were there to welcome them.

"Your Excellency Black Star, Your Excellency Incineration, and Your Excellency Dragon Emperor. I'm Commander Murraky's deputy, here to welcome you guys," an officer said respectfully.

Although Ames was not the dynasty's ally, she was a neutral Beyond Grade A who had followed Han Xiao there, so the dynasty would not treat her badly.

Han Xiao nodded. The group followed this deputy. After walking for a while, they realized that they walked into the resting area, not the command room.

"Is the commander not meeting us?" Beyoni wondered.

The deputy smiled apologetically and said, "The commander means to let you guys rest first. He will take care of the strategy, so you guys don't have to worry."

Han Xiao raised his brow. "Doesn't he want to discuss it with us?"

"The commander is currently busy discussing with the staff. You guys will be notified once the strategy is complete. The enemy might escape any time. We can't stay on standby for too long. We will be departing and engaging the enemies very soon. Please rest well. We will need your strength then."

Han Xiao and Beyoni exchanged looks and both shook their heads. It was clear that this Commander Murraky was not willing to let them interfere with the strategy planning, not even discussing with them.

"Then we shall rest." This was the first time that Han Xiao had marched into battle with the dynasty's army. Seeing that Beyoni did not say anything, he did not oppose the arrangements.

Seeing that the three Beyond Grade As did not have any objections, the deputy looked relieved. He then told his subordinates to make sure that Han Xiao and the others were settled before bidding farewell. He headed right back to the command room.

It was quiet in the command room. The commander, Murraky, stood before the enormous star map and observed it with his hands behind his back. The staff sergeants around him were all silent.

The deputy approached and reported, "Commander, the three Beyond Grade As have settled down."

Without turning back, Murraky said, "Did they have any objections?"

"No."

"Hmm, good. I don't like people who object." Murraky nodded faintly. "Announce to the entire fleet that we will depart immediately."

He was responsible for this elimination. His troops waited for a very long time for the Beyond Grade As of the dynasty arrived, which Murraky was very displeased about. However, the Beyond Grade As' position was very high, and they were not soldiers of the dynasty, so there was nothing he could say.

He did not like those Beyond Grade As who did not directly belong to the dynasty. As the commander of the fleet, he looked at matters from a strategic point of view. In his eyes, despite those Beyond Grade As having very high positions, they were just powerful destructive tools on the battlefield without their National Pillar titles.

Murraky did not want those Beyond Grade As to share his commanding power. The dynasty had given those tools to him, so they were for him to use. Therefore, he did not think that there was a need to waste time discussing strategy with the Beyond Grade As.

No matter how high their position was outside, one fleet could only have one commander—the Beyond Grade As just had to follow and obey his orders.

He had told his deputy to meet the Beyond Grade As because he was too lazy to give them a perfunctory welcome. He did not even want to see those Beyond Grade As step into his command room.

Under Murraky's command, the fleet started moving. They turned into streams of light dashing across the desolate universe belt and headed in the enemies' direction.

...

Inside the cabin, Han Xiao, Ames, and Beyoni were casually chatting.

"The commander of this fleet doesn't seem to like us." Ames shook her head.

Beyoni neither agreed nor disagreed. "The dynasty's military takes discipline extremely seriously. The Beyond Grade As, however, usually don't obey orders unconditionally. The words of the commanders are usually not taken seriously at all, so there have always been some dynasty officers who don't like to let us Beyond Grade As interfere with the overall strategy."

After a pause, Beyoni then said unhappily, "Despite all that, this guy named Murraky is way too arrogant. He doesn't even want to come to welcome us personally and even told us to just wait for his orders. Does he think us National Pillars are his soldiers?"

If it were an outsider who dared to act so arrogantly in front of some Beyond Grade As, he would have been killed easily. However, this guy was a soldier of the dynasty, and they could not do anything to him, which Beyoni was very displeased about.

Han Xiao, however, did not mind it too much. He waved and said carelessly, "He's the commander, after all. It's understandable for him to want to uphold his authority. One army can't have two commanding voices. Although our positions are high, there's nothing wrong with him treating us like the others. If we're just allowed to casually make suggestions, he won't be able to deal with them easily. Therefore, he simply divided our tasks clearly from the start so that we don't interfere with his command."

Beyoni glanced at him. "You really don't think of yourself as a Beyond Grade A."

Han Xiao shrugged.

Some senior Beyond Grade As were used to being high and mighty, not allowing the slightest disrespect. His attitude was different; he did not have such unnecessary pride.

After all, Murraky was a professional commander, so he was not willing to be told what to do by amateurs. Nonetheless, Han Xiao also felt that Murraky was indeed arrogant.

No matter what, it would not be asking too much for him to at least respect the strongest bunch of people in the universe. Never mind if he did not want to woo them, did he need to act so disrespectfully? Did he think he was the dynasty's marshal?

Shaking his head, Han Xiao did not want to bother about it anymore. They would most likely meet EsGod's main body this time, so he needed to think.

EsGod deliberately attracted the dynasty's army. He definitely intends to test me.

EsGod had once proposed to do one thing for him unconditionally in exchange for the use of the Evolution Cube. Han Xiao had to admit that he was tempted, but after careful consideration, he realized that this was not a pit that he could jump into.

EsGod was not a kind person—the deal itself was already a trap. Given the fact that anything that had to do with EsGod was a sensitive topic, if he really agreed to the deal, he would have left a weakness for others to possibly exploit. Since EsGod could live in between the three civilizations right under their noses, Han Xiao absolutely did not believe that EsGod had no connections with the three civilizations. If he agreed to EsGod's request, EsGod might expose this to the dynasty.

After EsGod finished using the Evolution Cube, he could disobey the agreement anytime he wanted. After all, he had never been known for having integrity. The uncertainties were too severe. Even if EsGod does live up to the promise, he would have plenty of ways to force Han Xiao into the opposite side of the Lawful Factions. EsGod was not afraid to do bad things, so it would be way too easy for him to drag Han Xiao down.

Han Xiao had another worry—EsGod had stolen the Evolution Cube from Psyker, exposing the fact that he had information about the Evolutionary Civilization, and now Han Xiao could use the Evolution Cube too, so it would be very easy for people to assume that they might have some sort of connection. People had definitely started to suspect him long ago. The Crimson Dynasty did not question him about this, so it might be because they had secretly investigated him and decided to trust him. However, if EsGod really wanted to drag him down and did something, it would affect him.

He would not be able to delay this matter forever. EsGod would not be willing to keep waiting, so he would definitely act once his patience ran out. If he was not in the Central Galaxy at that time, it would be very difficult for him to prove his innocence.

Being an ally of the dynasty would give him long-term benefits, so why risk it? He had made up his mind and decided that some things had to be made clear. He was certainly not going to jump into this pit. Since EsGod would not let him go, he was going to make it crystal clear that EsGod was his enemy!

Some things might look tempting and delicious, but inside, they were poisonous!

...

"Your Excellency EsGod, we have detected that the Crimson Dynasty's fleet has appeared behind us. According to our current speed, they will catch up with us very soon. Should we accelerate and get rid of them, or turn around and fight?"

Inside the main ship of this Fallen Ark fleet, the EsGod doppelganger listened to the report from his subordinates and waved his hand.

"Turn around and engage."

The very reason he had ordered this fleet to loiter around the dynasty's border was to attract the dynasty's army. Of course, he was not going to flee.

The Fallen Ark consisted of tens of millions of spaceships, and there were still many hidden bases in the desolate universe belt making new spaceships. Using one fleet as bait was not significant to EsGod at all.

If Black Star did not come, EsGod planned to capture some Espers during this battle so that he would not return empty-handed.

The Fallen Ark fleet turned around and faced the direction the dynasty's fleet came from, preparing for battle. Not long after, the 36th Division Army of the Dynasty Border Guard Army appeared on their radar.

Although Fallen Ark was made up of undisciplined brutes, they were not powerless. They fired right away at the dynasty's army from far away, at the same time, turned the thrusters' performance to their maximum and charged right at the dynasty's troops.

The three civilizations and EsGod were old enemies, there was no need for any words when they met, the battle erupted instantly.

The two fleets quickly charged toward each other and penetrated into each other's formation.

Spaceships exploded in the cosmic space one after another, turning into colorful and bright fireworks, beautiful and cruel.

There was a desolate planet at the side of the battlefield, wreckages of the spaceships turned into meteors and crashed onto its surface, creating craters all over.

The Soldier Grade main ship of the 36th Division Army fired all its weapons. Dark red energy annihilation beams shot out nonstop and destroyed Fallen Ark's spaceships one after another.

Murraky looked at the 3D battlefield map, observing the entire battlefield. He stared at the enemy's main ship and said coldly, "Strike first, have those three Beyond Grade As engage at the same time and force EsGod out!"

The order sounded on the communication channel. Beyoni frowned and said with a deep voice, "All three attacking together? Won't that expose our full capability immediately?"

Murraky heard the reply in the channel and said with an indisputable tone, "My orders are not for you to question. Execute them!"

Alright, this guy really is stubborn... Han Xiao sighed with resignation.

Almost everything about the Crimson Dynasty was good except this. Their civilization was too powerful, so it gave some of its government members too big a sense of superiority and confidence.

A tint of dissatisfaction flashed through Beyoni's eyes. This was not the right time to argue, so he endured it, kept silent, and jumped out of the hatch right into the battlefield, heading toward the enemy main ship where EsGod was.

Ames was a little unhappy, too. She shook her head and was about to step into the battlefield. This time, Han Xiao suddenly stopped her and sighed.

"Sorry, I didn't know the commander would have such a trash personality and made you endure this with me."

Ames' footsteps stopped. She turned around and glanced at him. The tiny bit of unhappiness in her eyes disappeared, and she teased, "Am I a kid to you? Does it look like I need you to comfort me, hmm?"

Then, Ames flew onto the battlefield and headed to EsGod's location from another direction.

Smiling with resignation, Han Xiao followed right after.

As soon as the three of them entered the battle, the situation changed. Everywhere Beyoni passed, groups of enemy battleships started burning out of nowhere and were covered in flames of all kinds of colors. Even the highly heat resistant alloys were burning and turned into liquid. Entire ships melted and exploded.

Ames directly grabbed countless battleships with her force field and swept left and right, creating countless empty areas. Those battleships that got too close were instantly crushed by the force field's pressure.

These two were both good in AOE abilities. They were weapons of mass destruction on the battlefield!

Han Xiao did not even need to put in any effort. He was happy to slack off behind the two of them with his mechanical army, only casually finishing some enemies off to complete some missions.

The three of them approached the enemy's main ship. Inside the main ship, the EsGod doppelganger saw Han Xiao and was surprised.

"So, you've actually come..."

Hum!

The next moment, he disappeared and teleported right before the three of them. Without even looking at Ames and Beyoni at all, he stared right at Han Xiao and sent a private psychic voice message with a tone filled with anticipation.

"Black Star, you really do understand me well. Have you decided to make the deal with me?"

Bang!

Han Xiao fired with countless psionic cannons at the EsGod doppelganger without hesitation, slamming it onto the surface of the desolate planet.

The three of them followed right after and hovered in the sky of the desolate planet. Ames dragged the EsGod doppelganger who crashed into the ground up with her force field and compressed it into a twisting black shadow. She then pulled it right toward the three of them.

Beyoni raised his hands and aimed at the EsGod doppelganger. Suddenly, flames erupted from within the EsGod doppelganger's dark body.

Han Xiao activated [Gene Liberation], and the mechanical army fired at the EsGod doppelganger continuously.

Psh!

Dark blue beams penetrated the EsGod doppelganger time after time like a thunderstorm, followed the gravitational force of the desolate planet, and disappeared in the cosmic space.

Pa!

The EsGod doppelganger exploded into a black fog and slowly dissipated.

Even Psyker could easily eliminate two EsGod doppelgangers alone. One EsGod doppelganger with limited energy would only be completely thrashed in the face of three Beyond Grade As.

"Not bad." Murraky, who was in the main ship far away, nodded.

Now that the EsGod doppelganger had been eliminated, he just had to wipe out the enemy fleet.

Just as he was thinking that, a space energy vortex suddenly appeared where the EsGod doppelganger had been eliminated. An ordinary ugly man wearing a hood stepped out of it.

As soon as this person appeared, as if he had brought an immeasurable amount of pressure with him, the spacetime around him seemed to freeze for an instant.

At this moment, Murraky's expression changed drastically.

Beyoni's relaxed body tensed up instantly.

Ames frowned tightly.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

This was no longer a doppelganger but EsGod's main body!

The notorious brute feared by many Beyond Grade As!

EsGod stared coldly at Han Xiao and spoke slowly with a cold tone.

"I'm... very disappointed with your response.

"But... when rejecting me, you shouldn't have been so close to me."

Chapter 805: Overwhelming

EsGod's appearance made Murraky horrified. He had thought this was just a regular routine elimination; he had never expected EsGod's main body to appear there.

It was common knowledge in the Central Galaxy—If you meet EsGod's main body, it's best to escape immediately.

"You guys, lure EsGod away and buy us some time!"

Murraky ordered his fleet to ignore the damage incurred and keep attacking the Fallen Ark's fleet while decisively giving Han Xiao and the other orders.

EsGod's vicious name was deeply embedded in the Central Galaxy. Murraky was arrogant, but he knew that there was no way to kill EsGod with the manpower he had. His goal was just to eliminate the enemy fleet and reduce EsGod's power so that EsGod would be alone, and they could try to force him away. If he succeeded, it would be an amazing achievement!

Although EsGod was one of the strongest even among Beyond Grade As, there were three Beyond Grade As on his side at the very least. It was time to make use of them.

As the dynasty's troops started moving, the three Beyond Grade As including Han Xiao were confronting EsGod on the desolate planet. They completely ignored Murraky's words and focused all their attention on EsGod.

The atmosphere was almost solidifying, and the murderous intent in the air kept growing.

Beyoni did not dare to move his eyes away from EsGod, so he glanced at Han Xiao with shock from the corner of his eyes—he had heard what EsGod said.

What response? Does Black Star have a private contact with EsGod?

With the movements of Han Xiao's fingers, the mechanical army all aimed at EsGod but did not fire immediately. Han Xiao slowly said, "Did you really think I would agree to your terms and let you use the Evolution Cube? I'm now a member of the dynasty, so you and I will only be enemies, nothing else! I came this time to make that crystal clear. The Evolution Cube is right here. If you want it, come and get it!"

Han Xiao did not hide the fact that the two of them had communicated in the past and actively stated his stance.

EsGod narrowed his eyes and stared at Han Xiao's neck as if his sight could penetrate the mechanical suit and see the Evolution Cube.

Black Star knew that this was a signal he sent deliberately, yet he still dared to personally come here to reject him? He had even brought the Evolution Cube along to draw the line clearly. Was Black Star really not afraid of him snatching it, or was Black Star too confident in himself?

EsGod glanced at Han Xiao and the others and said coldly, "Has fighting me as three given you confidence?"

As soon as his sentence finished, EsGod moved. With a push of his hands, rainbow-like energy gushed out and turned into countless beams of light, shooting toward the three of them.

"Shield!"

With a quick flash of green light in Ames' eyes, a thick force field shrouded the three of them. The rainbow energy exploded over the force field and turned into fireworks. Its penetration power was very strong and even had a decomposing attribute. If not because Ames' force field had a continuous supply of energy from her, these attacks would not have been easy to defend against.

EsGod turned his palm, and suddenly, another force field appeared and pressed onto them.

"He has a type of force field Esper Ability, too." Ames was shocked and hastily sustained her own force field. The two force fields entered a stalemate for the moment, but they were surrounded by EsGod's force field.

Force Field Esper Abilities were quite common and did not have very high potential. Ames was the one and only person that had become a Beyond Grade A with it. However, the low-grade Esper Abilities that EsGod had absorbed would receive Beyond Grade A bonuses from him, so the two of them were on par for the time being.

Along with Han Xiao's thoughts, the mechanical army outside started attacking immediately. EsGod narrowed his eyes. Suddenly, the space around him solidified and seemed to crystalize. Countless psionic attacks were deflected. Some disappeared into the sky, and some landed on the ground, causing enormous explosions, but none managed to hit him!

"Pure energy reflection Esper Ability..." Han Xiao's expression changed.

At this moment, Beyoni released his Esper Ability from afar and ignited EsGod's body. Be it his flesh, bones, or the energy inside him, they all turned into fuel for the flames.

However, EsGod was unaffected. He inhaled deeply, and it was as if the flames on his body were absorbed by his skin. Beyoni's flames turned into pure energy and were devoured by his cells.

Before they could respond, half of EsGod's body suddenly turned into black fog. The black fog concentrated into a human shape beside him. As if his cells had split, a new doppelganger appeared.

Swoosh!

This doppelganger disappeared instantly, ignoring Ames' force field, and appeared before Beyoni, punching right onto his chest. With its [God Speed] Esper Ability, this doppelganger was extremely fast.

Beyoni's response was quick, too. Energy flew in his body. He raised his arms at the verge of danger and blocked the EsGod doppelganger's fist. However, the fist had no momentum or power. Instead, the moment it touched Beyoni, a strange energy entered into Beyoni's body.

"Wha..." Beyoni's expression changed drastically. At that instant, it was as if the Esper Ability in his body had disappeared. He could not even sense his energy anymore.

At this time, the EsGod doppelganger emitted a blinding light and expanded extremely quickly.

Hum!

A black mass of light appeared, quickly expanding like a black hole, and shrouded Beyoni. A part of the mechanical army around were devoured too and were all obliterated. The mechanical soldiers that were not in the center of the explosion were blown away by the shockwave, incurring various degrees of damage.

Boom!

The mass of light expanded and exploded, leaving an enormous crater on the ground.

A black sphere of fire hovered in midair. The flames around it dissipated, and Beyoni appeared from within.

His entire body was burnt black. His Esper Ability had been suppressed by some kind of Esper Ability of EsGod. When the doppelganger exploded, he could finally sense his Esper Ability at the last moment and ignited the energy around him, offsetting the approaching energy and canceling most of the explosion's power, creating an empty space around him. This was why he was not too heavily injured.

Not far away, a rippled appeared in midair, and Han Xiao walked out of it. He had avoided the explosion by entering the Void Dimension. On the other side, Ames walked out of the Void Dimension, too. Her method of avoiding the explosion was exactly the same as Han Xiao's.

After just a short fight, the faces of all three of them looked grave. They looked up and stared at EsGod, who did not even move.

"What a terrifying guy..."

Although expected, the extent of how powerful EsGod was still shocked Han Xiao. Rumors were one thing—facing EsGod himself was another. He had fought an EsGod doppelganger before, but his doppelganger and his main body were on completely different levels.

This being before him was someone who had spent countless years collecting Esper Abilities, a monster with who knew how many abilities!

This guy's main body was the true definition of 'EsGod'—the mighty God of Espers!

The potential of an Esper Ability determined its owner's Grade limit. Many unique Esper Abilities had a very low Grade limit, but when EsGod absorbed these Esper Abilities and used his own Beyond Grade A energy as their energy source, some abilities that would have never reached Beyond Grade A could now possess Beyond Grade A level of power. Even the simplest Esper Abilities would be extremely powerful in his hands, and some strange abilities would even have shocking effects!

For example, the ability that suppressed Beyoni was originally an ability that could silence someone else's Esper Ability, but that ability had a very low limit and could not even affect Calamity Grades. However, when EsGod used it with his own energy, despite it only being able to activate at close range, it became effective even against Beyond Grade As.

With so many Esper Abilities, he almost had no weaknesses. To him, there were only two restrictions—his own energy limit and the fact that he could not use too many Esper Abilities at the same time, as that would overload his genes.

He suppressed three enemies including Han Xiao alone and did not look pressured. In the entire universe, very few could match up to him in a direct battle!

"Luckily, I dragged Beyoni here. The situation would have been much worse if there were only two of us. Although three of us still can't beat him, at least we can barely stall him..."

With a heavy heart, Han Xiao reorganized his scattered mechanical army.

Compared to the other Beyond Grade As whom he had fought before, EsGod was the only one whose strength completely overwhelmed him!

"He does live up to his notorious name." Ames gasped for air. This was also her first time fighting EsGod, and she was shocked after experiencing EsGod's overwhelming strength.

EsGod glanced at the three of them and suddenly disappeared by teleportation.

"Sh*t."

Han Xiao hastily looked up and saw that EsGod had moved into the dynasty's army.

Murraky, who was commanding the fleet, had the same thought. When he saw EsGod appearing in the fleet, his expression changed dramatically.

The next moment, EsGod punched forward and shot out a crimson beam of light toward the main ship. It directly penetrated the main ship's high-level energy shield and created a huge hole on the ship, completely penetrating it from one side to the other. Armor plates scattered around.

"Warning! Warning! Ship damage 10.8%! Engine Three broken! Energy circuit damaged. Energy core output efficiency decreased by 18%. Repairing..."

The tremble of the ship made the people in the command room stagger and almost fall. When Murraky finally balanced himself, his face had turned pale.

"Quickly, retreat!"

As the main ship was attacked, the situation changed in an instant. If they were attacked by EsGod a few more times, he would be dead for sure. The tiny bit of will of not wanting to accept defeat so easily disappeared immediately, and he did not dare continue fighting.

However, the main ship was EsGod's target. He fired a chain of black-red beams of light.

Looking at the beams of light approaching from the porthole and hearing the alarm in the spaceship, it suddenly occurred to Murraky that in the face of such superior strength, he was powerless. The fleet he trusted so much could not help him at all; he was like a pig waiting to be butchered.

Despair appeared on his face.

The beam of light shot right into the main ship. The next moment, light expanded from within, and the main ship exploded into pieces.

Murraky's vision was filled with darkness. He had already closed his eyes and was waiting for his death. Suddenly, he felt that his entire body was covered by cold metal. He immediately opened his eyes and saw that the mass of light emitted from the main ship's explosion was getting further in his sights, while he was covered by a mechanical suit and was quickly getting away from the area of the explosion.

"I'm not dead!" Murraky's eyes were opened wide. Fear still lingered in his heart.

Buzz...

At this time, the tactical display lit up, and Han Xiao's face appeared.

"Still alive? Don't just freeze there. The fleet needs your command. Don't think about retreating. EsGod is indeed terrifyingly strong, but he won't be able to beat the three of us in a short time. This place is very near the dynasty's borders. The guard army of the border is able to reinforce us anytime, so he won't stay here for too long. As long as we hang on, we can force him away."

As the main ship exploded, Han Xiao had arrived and saved Murraky—he could not let this guy die. The fleet needed a commander.

Black Star? This guy saved me?

Murraky's expression changed. After hearing what Han Xiao said, he clenched his teeth and left the thought of retreating behind. He hastily opened the command channel and told the fleet to continue attacking. The mechanical suit on him protected him and helped him flee, so he would not die.

Han Xiao took the other two to surround EsGod again, fighting him with all their might. They finally barely pulled him away from the fleet.

The four of them fought intensely. EsGod did not show any sign of difficulty dealing with the attacks of all three of them, while the number of wounds on Han Xiao and the others kept increasing instead. The damage of the mechanical army gradually increased too. None of them could match EsGod alone, so they could only fight him together.

In the middle of the intense fight, Han Xiao suddenly received a psychic voice message from EsGod.

"I've always wondered, how do you know how to use the Evolution Cube?" EsGod said with a curious tone.

He did indeed wonder. The data of the Evolutionary Civilization was clearly in his hands. He had checked Han Xiao's history and knew that Han Xiao had never had any form of contact with the Evolutionary Civilization, so why did he know how to use the Evolution Cube?

Han Xiao blocked an energy shockwave with his psionic shield, clenched his teeth, and barely opened his mouth. "I... was lucky!"

"Luck? Do you think I'm easy to fool?" EsGod's face was filled with doubt.

The activation password of the Evolution Cube is extremely complicated. For you to get it from luck alone, the possibility is infinitely close to zero. You're not going to fool anyone.

There was only one possibility—the data of the Evolutionary Civilization had definitely leaked.

EsGod paused, dodged Ames' force field impact, and suddenly shook his head. "Never mind, what's important is the fact that you know how to use it. The reason doesn't matter. Maybe this has given you the confidence not to be afraid. Sadly, you underestimated me and overestimated yourself. Bringing the portable Evolution Cube right in front of me is the biggest mistake you've made."

Then, EsGod raised his hand. A cluster of blue light hovered above his palm. The next moment, it disappeared and turned into a familiar tiny silver cube.

Han Xiao trembled and hastily looked down. The Evolution Cube on his neck had disappeared, and he did not feel it at all!

Chapter 806: Clue

"A space swap Esper Ability?" Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

"You don't seem nervous at all." EsGod narrowed his eyes. Then, having suddenly realized something, he pressed down hard on the tiny silver cube and shattered it.

Silver alloy pieces scattered from his palm—there were no traces of any evolution energy at all.

EsGod's movement became stiff.

Han Xiao chuckled. "Did you think that I would really bring the Evolution Cube here to see you? Let me return your words back at you... you underestimated me."

This guy was not Psyker, who had possessed the Evolution Cube for many years, so he did not have the psychic detection to identify the real Evolution Cube.

EsGod stayed silent for a few seconds before shaking his head. "That's right. Since you've decided to reject me, how could you have really brought the real one here? I was misguided by you."

When his main body had just appeared, Han Xiao acted very tough and told him to come and get it if he wanted the Evolution Cube, making his attention focused on the 'Evolution Cube' on Han Xiao. Afterward, EsGod did not have the time to think too much during the battle, so he subconsciously thought that the tiny silver cube on Han Xiao's neck was the real deal.

He just said that he was not easy to fool, but then he was fooled right after... EsGod's expression was not looking too bright.

It was no secret that the Evolution Cube had become portable. As Psyker was always attempting to take it back, it was impossible to let anyone else carry the Evolution Cube. That was the misconception that Han Xiao had been building, so people would think that he carried the Evolution Cube with him at all times. Therefore, due to this preconception, EsGod had mistakenly assumed that knowing Han Xiao's location was equivalent to knowing the Evolution Cube's location and failed to think of the possibility that the Evolution Cube might not be with Han Xiao.

The data left by the Evolutionary Civilization consisted of a method to locate the Evolution Cube, but it was different from Psyker's psychic method. That method could only accurately locate the Evolution Cube within a certain range when used in combination with a special detection device.

The technology used in this device came from countless years ago and had certain flaws compared to the present. Furthermore, the data left by the Evolutionary Civilization was not complete, so the detector had limitations, mainly distance.

Back when EsGod stole the Evolution Cube, it was because he had a rough idea of where the Evolution Cube was since it was on Psyker's mother planet. He had only used the detector when he was nearby to obtain the accurate location of where the cube was on Psyker's mother planet. If he did not know where the Evolution Cube was at the start, the detector would not be able to find it across the wide Star Field either.

If not because EsGod did not have the wrong preconception and did not have the time to look at the device while fighting the three of them, he would have noticed that the Evolution Cube was not nearby.

Psyker's psychic energy was linked to the Evolution Cube. Although the location would be not very accurate when the distance was too great, he could still sense the Evolution Cube no matter how far it was. This was why Han Xiao always carried it around with him. However, this time, it was different coming to have contact with EsGod. Knowing that EsGod had a lot of tricks up his sleeve, Han Xiao was prepared. The Evolution Cube was not with him for the time being.

Some time ago when he departed from Planet Crimson Ring and spent a few days to reach the border, he had secretly sent a spaceship in another direction during the trip, not to the border but stealthily moving in the territory of the dynasty. The real Evolution Cube was there, and no one knew about this.

Psyker was far away. The further he was, the less accurate the location of the Evolution Cube would be to him. Psyker only knew that the Evolution Cube was somewhere in the Central Galaxy. Furthermore, not mentioning Psyker not knowing what was happening right then, even if he did know, a famous member of the Arcane Church would not be able to enter the dynasty's territory. Therefore, Han Xiao could temporarily ignore the threat from Psyker.

For safety purposes, he had dispatched another mechanical army on the stealth spaceship that had the true Evolution Cube on it.

With his [Quantum Infinite Distance Transmission Channel] ability, even if the army was very far from him, he could still transmit Mechanical Force over and let the mechanical army over there have Beyond Grade A level power!

Staying in one place and letting the Beyond Grade A level mechanical army carry out expeditions was the specialty of Beyond Grade A Mechanics.

When he was not even at the scene, how could the enemy close the distance on him‽

This was somewhat similar to EsGod's doppelgangers but even better. This was exactly the combat mode that Manison used—the enemies would not be able to even see his face when fighting him.

Han Xiao was currently not using this strategy because his army had yet to reach the Mechanic Empire's level. Furthermore, his tankiness was one of his strengths, so it would be a waste to not utilize it.

However, the mechanical army he sent on an 'expedition' could also completely thrash Calamity Grades, so they were more than enough to be guards of the Evolution Cube for the time being.

While these thoughts flashed through his mind, Han Xiao did not stop moving and controlling the mechanical army to focus fire on EsGod. Although EsGod's energy reflection shield could reflect most energy attacks, Han Xiao had plenty of ways to deal with that.

The mechanical army had a wide variety of attack methods, so one single Esper Ability could not possibly make him helpless. His mechanical army could even counter Metal Manipulation, so a mere energy reflection was no obstacle.

Furthermore, EsGod could not use too many abilities simultaneously and was not going to keep defending but not attacking. Also, there were two more Beyond Grade As beside Han Xiao.

The three of them could not defeat EsGod, but at the same time, EsGod could not easily defeat the three of them. The result of the battle could not be determined in a short time, and the two sides had entered a stalemate.

In the battlefield, Murraky, who had just escaped death, had no time to relax and ordered his fleet to keep attacking. Despite being arrogant, his professional capability was no fluke. After all, he could single-handedly command an entire border defense army.

Under his strategic orders, the dynasty's troops attacked violently and had the firm upper hand. Without the interference of Beyond Grade As, this Fallen Ark fleet was no match for him at all and was quickly falling apart.

While dealing with the attacks, EsGod glanced at the fleet battlefield and frowned. He could see that his fleet was going to be wiped out.

As he had just confirmed, the Evolution Cube was not with Han Xiao. Therefore, to EsGod, there was no need to continue fighting. This place was too close to the dynasty's border, and their reinforcements would reach very soon. Even he did not want to face tons of dynasty border guard armies. Even if he would eventually escape unharmed, he did not want to provoke the three civilizations too much.

If he killed too many the Crimson Dynasty men, the Crimson Dynasty might immediately gather a large army and march into the sensitive areas to pursue and eliminate the main Fallen Ark army. By then, it would be Clotti and the other two old dynasty b*stards he would have to face.

Although EsGod was not afraid of them himself, he would lose far more than just a fleet, so it was not worth it.

At this time, Han Xiao suddenly sent a psychic voice message and said with a deep voice, "You have a space swap Esper ability, so I'm guessing you never wanted to make a deal with me since the start, and this has always been a trap."

EsGod blocked Ames' force field then replied in a mocking tone.

"It's true I have no credibility nor reputation, but this time, you're wrong. I was indeed sincere. The Evolution Cube was the only hope to reach the higher territory in my eyes, but it isn't anymore. I have seen a wider world! To me, the Evolution Cube is no longer my final target, just a tool that I want and not an absolute necessity. If you're not willing to lend it to me, I really would not have done anything to you..."

A higher territory? Han Xiao wondered. EsGod was combining the clearly restricted Super High Risk Esper Abilities and taking in countless galactic wanted criminals to form the Fallen Ark. Everything he did was for stronger power—his motive was very straight forward.

"You want to be like the Primordial Ones, break through the limit of individual power and discover a new grade?" Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

"Hehe." EsGod neither agreed nor denied it. Then, he suddenly changed the topic and said, "Speaking of which, I have to thank you. You made me see a new hope and changed my goal."

"Thank me?" Han Xiao was confused.

"A few years ago, my doppelganger fought you in the Shattered Star Ring. It was toyed with by you and thrown into a wormhole," EsGod said with a mysterious tone. "Sadly, you did not follow me through the wormhole. You have absolutely no idea what you've missed."

Between the lines of his words, it was as if that event had turned out to be beneficial to him.

Han Xiao suddenly had a flash of insight and linked all the clues together. Shocked, he asked, "Was that why your people killed Harrofal?"

Back when the DarkStar leader returned to assassinate him, he had used an EsGod doppelganger. That was the first time he had come in contact with EsGod.

At that time, he had been no match for the EsGod doppelganger. He had used the wormhole environment around and worked together with a Mechanic who studied wormholes, Harrofal, leading the EsGod doppelganger into the wormhole and banishing it.

After that, EsGod had sent his subordinates to steal the Evolution Cube but killed Harrofal too. Han Xiao did not know the reason. This had happened a very long time ago, and he did not expect EsGod to bring it up. It seemed like there was something else to this.

"Harrofal?" EsGod paused, as if he finally remembered this name after thinking for some time. "Hmm, right, that's his name, that guy who tricked my doppelganger together with you at that time. I obtained the data of that wormhole tunnel from him."

Han Xiao was puzzled. EsGod said that he had seen the hope for the next stage. What did this guy see on the other side of the wormhole?

Did EsGod obtain the data for that particular wormhole tunnel so that he could locate the destination of that random teleportation and build a stable tunnel?

What did that wormhole lead to that was worthy of even EsGod putting in so much effort‽

Han Xiao was tempted to know, but EsGod had no interest in speaking about it. He suddenly teleported and escaped from the siege of the three of them, waving his hand. A teleportation gate appeared behind him.

From far away, EsGod's sights stabbed Han Xiao like knives. From EsGod's eyes, Han Xiao understood what he meant.

I'll let you go this time, but we will have plenty of chances in the future to play again. The days are still long!

Their gazes clashed.

Then, EsGod took a step back and disappeared without a trace together with the teleportation gate.

"He retreated..."

Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief. The mechanical army lost the target and stopped moving.

EsGod could not obtain the Evolution Cube this time, so he would most likely make more plans in the future. Han Xiao had no idea what methods EsGod would use in the future.

The two of them were now on completely opposite sides. However, this guy could not easily leave the Central Galaxy, so Han Xiao did not know when they would fight again.

Also, the wormhole that EsGod mentioned had piqued his curiosity.

Thinking of the strength that EsGod had showcased in this battle, Han Xiao felt a lot of pressure.

"He is the final boss of the Chaotic Evil Faction. I don't have enough strength to fight him yet..."

Han Xiao felt a sense of pressure—he needed to become stronger.

Chapter 807: EsGod Character Summon Card: Esper Silence

Though they kept their guard up a while longer, EsGod did not appear again.

"We forced him away?" Beyoni's voice sounded in the communication channel filled with doubt and disbelief.

Ames looked at the fleet battlefield afar that was completely one-sided, shook her head, and said, "Does he not even want his fleet anymore?"

"They're all wanted criminals. None are good," Han Xiao said slowly. "Across the entire universe, new criminals are born every second and every minute. Countless people have sought protection from him. EsGod basically has an endless supply of manpower. How much will he care about the lives of his subordinates? If he did care, he would not have used his subordinates as bait."

Without EsGod, this Fallen Ark fleet scattered and escaped in all directions. The dynasty's troops chased right after them. The three of them did not do anything about those escaping battleships and returned to one of the sub-ships. Chasing those fleeing enemies was the dynasty's troops' task.

As the main ship had been destroyed by EsGod, Murraky had moved to this sub-ship to re-establish his command. As soon as the three of them entered the spaceship, they immediately saw the few soldiers who had been waiting beside the hatch all along.

"Y-Your Excellencies, the commander has invited the three of you to the bridge." The soldier was a little nervous. All these soldiers on the spaceships witnessed the fight between the three of them and EsGod—they had a very clear idea of how strong these three were.

"So, now this guy's willing to let us go to the command room?" Han Xiao laughed and walked at the front. The soldier quickly caught up and led the way.

When the three of them entered the command room at the bridge, Murraky was staring at the strategic map and talking nonstop, giving out orders to maximize the results of the battle. As he turned around and saw Han Xiao and the others walk in, his face turned respectful, and he hastily went to the three of them.

"Your Excellency Black Star, you saved my life, thank you! I'm very sorry about what happened before!" Murraky's attitude was completely different from before, and he could not have been more respectful.

No matter how arrogant he was, he could not act that way to Black Star, who had saved his life.

Han Xiao looked at him with narrowed eyes and said indifferently, "You're the commander. You can be arrogant, you can act all high and mighty, and you can have all kinds of problems... but you can't forget your job. The battle has not ended, yet you left your commanding position and came to apologize to us? Putting it bluntly, no matter what attitude you have, it will never change the difference in position between you and us. Do you think we care about your apology?"

The command room became silent. The people around dared not make a sound.

Murraky shivered. His intention to apologize was sincere, but he never expected to receive such an uncompromising response. It was almost shameful. He could not help but feel somewhat wronged. However, with an awkward expression, he did not dare speak again and returned to his station to continue commanding the battle.

After Han Xiao finally left with an expressionless face, the people in the room finally dared to breathe freely.

The annoyance in Beyoni's heart disappeared immediately. He patted Han Xiao's shoulder and laughed. "Dynasty military officers like him don't know how to respect the strong. That'll teach him a lesson."

Han Xiao glanced at him and shook his head in his mind. It was not Murraky's attitude that he was unhappy about. If this was directed just toward him, he would have generously laughed it off. However, this did not just concern him. Ames was not an ally of the dynasty—she had helped him purely because she was kind enough to. Yet she was treated this way, so there was no way Han Xiao was just going to act as if nothing had happened.

Therefore, even though Murraky had gone to apologize sincerely, he still did not accept it at all and used the chance to teach him a lesson. Ames was not the dynasty's ally, so she had no place to speak. Only he could help her vent her anger. Even though Ames had never requested him to do so, Han Xiao still did it.

Ames looked at Han Xiao with an interested look on her face. "Yo, this is the first time I've seen you show off your Beyond Grade A identity. Kiddo, has arrogance finally caught up to you?"

Han Xiao glanced at her and raised his brows. "Don't tell me you didn't like it."

"Smart." Ames laughed and shook her head. She softly poked Han Xiao's cheek with her slender finger.

Han Xiao turned his head around with resignation, caught Ames' hand, and pressed it down. "Your words were more than sufficient."

They casually chatted about the battle earlier as they returned to the house. Han Xiao entered a room alone and closed the door after him. Now, he finally had the time to take a breather and recollect the battle earlier.

He had gained quite a lot from this test.

The goal on paper to take part in this elimination was to complete a mission and obtain Contribution Points, as well as to clarify his stand and draw an obvious line with EsGod.

One of the secret goals was to evaluate the combat capability of EsGod's main body.

The Great Mechanic Han had a very clear idea of his own capabilities and knew that he was no match for EsGod at the moment, which was why he had hidden the Evolution Cube in advance. However, he was at least at the Beyond Grade A level just like EsGod, so he would not be too afraid and knew that he could at least fight EsGod.

Since EsGod was his enemy, while he had help, he wanted to test EsGod's strength personally and feel their differences. This way, he would have a rough idea when facing EsGod in the future and would not be unprepared.

The test did give him a result—EsGod felt unfathomable, like a bottomless pit. Just seeing the tip of the iceberg had already given him a lot of pressure.

"Level, talents, and Ultimate Knowledges need to be obtained, and the mechanical army needs to be continuously expanded." Han Xiao was planning ahead.

A Beyond Grade A Mechanic's army could travel long distances without him having to be there. Other than his own abilities, he also had to increase the size and strength of his mechanical army. After he obtained the Ultimate Knowledge to activate [King's Mentor], he would be able to enhance his mechanical army even further and make use of the Beyond Grade A Mechanic combat style.

The most important goal he had this time was to plant a ward on that guy.

EsGod had multiple abilities, but he was not a Mage. Even though the chances were slim, he had to try it. With this attitude, Han Xiao had secretly thrown an Observer's Mark at EsGod during the battle. Sadly, EsGod had discovered it and shattered it instantly.

Han Xiao was not very regretful about this. It was a gamble to begin with. It would have been a great surprise if it worked, but he had been mentally prepared for it not to.

Ding.

At this time, the mission complete notification popped up on the interface.

"The battle has finally ended?"

He opened the interface and looked at the notifications.

[Dynasty Warfare: Fallen Ark (Repeatable)] Completed!

The targets you have completed are: [Elite Minions], [Brave Warrior], [Scavenger]... [Facing EsGod I], [Facing EsGod II, [Facing EsGod III], [Facing EsGod IV].

Mission Rating: Unbelievable

You have received Unbelievable Mission Rating reward: Bonus 9,000,000,000 EXP, 2 Random Rewards

"That's quite a lot of EXP." Han Xiao was delighted. All missions that involved Beyond Grade As had very rich rewards. It was the same back when he fought Heber.

The total EXP reward for this mission was close to thirty billion! It was plenty even at his level. It mainly came from the reward involving EsGod, which he could complete easily but was extremely difficult for the players.

Scanning through the notifications, Han Xiao smiled. He had made a huge fortune this time. The Contribution Points for the Crimson Dynasty had reached more than eight thousand, more than enough to exchange for an Ultimate Knowledge.

Han Xiao saved the two Random Rewards before looking at the EsGod Character Summon Card reward from the [Facing EsGod IV] mission.

Character Summon Card - EsGod: [Esper Ability—Esper Silence]—Through physical contact, suppress the Esper Genes of the target and forbid the target from using Esper Ability. Only effective against Espers. The Judgement success rate and the duration depends on the difference between the user and target in terms of Level, Energy Level, and Luck.

Minimum duration if effective: 0.25s

Usages: 0/2

"Esper Silence?" Han Xiao recalled that this was the Esper Ability that EsGod had used on Beyoni.

EsGod had many abilities, and the Character Summon Card could only draw one. Luckily, this Esper Ability was quite useful, thanks to him touching Feidin before the battle.

Han Xiao pondered. The ability of this Character Summon Card just so happened to counter EsGod, which was an unexpected surprise. However, the difference in the various attributes between him and EsGod was quite large, so it was almost impossible for the Judgement to succeed.

Maybe when his level caught up to EsGod, this Character Summon Card would be effective on him.

Han Xiao kept this Character Summon Card as a trump card.

"Now that I've drawn the line clearly with EsGod, the goal for this trip is achieved... I shall exchange for Ultimate Knowledge later on and rendezvous with the army, as well as make contact with the Constellation Corridor players."

One of the two goals he had for this Central Galaxy trip was now completed, and Han Xiao had already planned for what to do next.

"One more thing..."

He was rather concerned with the wormhole EsGod mentioned and wanted to know what EsGod was planning.

"When I return to the Shattered Star Ring, I have to find the time to visit Harrofal's civilization and see if I can get the data for that wormhole travel. I have to find out why EsGod was looking for that set of data..."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

He had an intuitive feeling that this was not simple. It might be a surprise...

In the other room, Beyoni opened his communicator and called Clotti's number.

The communication was picked up very soon.

Du...

"Clotti, the battle here has ended."

"How was it?" Clotti asked.

"We met EsGod's main body..." Beyoni described the whole thing.

Clotti nodded and said, "This means that EsGod did indeed contact Black Star before, but Black Star did not agree, hmm... There is the possibility that they're putting on a show. Anyhow, good work, I will report this to Her Excellency."

"It didn't look fake." Beyoni spoke for Han Xiao. "I feel that Black Star knew that the dynasty had some doubts about him, and this was to express his stand to gain the dynasty's trust. After all, he's a new Beyond Grade A ally of the dynasty. Even if there are doubts, it won't be publicized. It's impossible to interrogate someone like him, so he needed to do this."

Clotti did not comment about it. He was only responsible for reporting; the final judgment depended on Urranrell.

"By the way, Black Star asked me about the Mechanic Empire," Beyoni suddenly said.

"That's normal." Clotti shook his head.

After a few more words, Beyoni hung up the communication and exhaled flame sparkles from his mouth.

Not only was he close to the military's Youngsters Faction, but he was also a confidant of the Ruler. During this trip with Han Xiao, not only was he building a closer relationship with Han Xiao, but he was also secretly told by Urranrell to keep an eye on Black Star's actions.

In the Central Galaxy's desolate universe belt very far from the battlefield, another Fallen Ark fleet was hidden.

A space vortex shaped teleportation gate appeared above the fleet, and EsGod walked out of it.

The main ship opened its hatch and welcomed EsGod onboard.

As he returned to the main ship's hall, the people on standby there stood up and greeted him.

"Your Excellency EsGod!"

"Boss!"

EsGod ignored them and walked to his throne. He sat down and glanced over the people below him. "How's the research progress?"

"They're still matching the data with the coordinates. We don't know how long it will take to accurately locate the location in the data records. That set of data is too strange. It does not seem to be in the explored universe. Even if we have the data, without the matching coordinates on the star map, the workload is enormous."

"Results are the only thing I want. Confirm the location as soon as possible," EsGod said coldly. He then turned to look at his capable assistant beside him and said, "Help me to contact the Arcane Church's men."

"Oh? For what?"

This person licked his lips. His tongue was purple and covered in spikes, like a whip. A bright red mask was embedded into his face bone as if it was soldered into his face. The mask blocked the upper half of his face, not even showing his eyes. Only his mouth and chin could be seen. He was a being with an upright spine but not human, about 1.7 meters tall. His back was bent like an old man. His skin was thick, dark purple, and rough like sandpaper. He had two pairs of upper limbs and one pair of lower limbs. He looked emaciated, and his body was like a purple brunch of a dead tree. He had the EsGod-brand fashionable beggar hood on too. He emitted a sense of evil and creepiness from all over his body.

Fakisen, nicknamed the Purple Devil, one of the Beyond Grade A Seeds in the Central Galaxy many years ago. He was once a wanted criminal chased by universal civilizations, then he joined the Fallen Ark and had been an important officer under EsGod for around a hundred years.

"Tell the Arcane Church's men, didn't they want the data left by the Evolutionary Civilization? I can give it to them."

"On what terms?" Fakisen tilted his head.

"To work together and snatch the Evolution Cube. Tell them, if that succeeds, the Evolution Cube is theirs. I only need to use it a few times," EsGod said slowly.

In order not to make the same mistake, he decided to borrow Psyker's ability to locate the Evolution Cube. As he had slaughtered many Star Pupil Holy Race members before, Psyker would not work with him, so EsGod planned to directly negotiate with the Arcane Church in secret. As long as the Arcane Church made a decision, he would be able to discreetly borrow Psyker's ability.

The Arcane Church had an unusual passion for the Evolution Cube. Ever since EsGod stole the Evolution Cube from Psyker and made it known to the public that he possessed information about the Evolutionary Civilization, the Arcane Church had proposed many terms to him secretly in exchange for the Evolutionary Civilization's information.

According to EsGod's speculation, the Arcane Church's feverish admiration for the Gods was one of the main reasons they wanted the Evolution Cube. EsGod did not know the details of it.

Although EsGod knew that he was the common enemy of the three civilizations. Since he shared a common goal with the Arcane Church, it was not impossible for them to work together in secret. Furthermore, the target of negotiation was the mysterious Arcane Church, which had the most ambiguous stand among the three civilizations. Compared to the Federation of Light and the Crimson Dynasty, the Arcane Church was the least keen to kill him.

"We're going to make a deal with the Arcane Church? That's really risky. If there's a chance, they might eliminate you during the process," Fakisen said with a mocking tone.

"Hehe." EsGod smiled faintly and did not reply. He then said, "I'll leave this matter to you. I need to sleep for some time."

Pa!

Fakisen's tongue whipped in midair and created a sound that had the same meaning as humans snapping their fingers, expressing that he would get it done.

EsGod grunted and lowered his head. His face turned back to a vortex shaped black fog and entered his slumber.

Fakisen was used to this. The various Esper Abilities of EsGod all existed in his body in the form of Genetic Chains, which had a very heavy load on his body. Continuously switching between his various Esper Abilities would cause his cells to age very quickly. When EsGod absorbed Esper Abilities from others, he was basically using his life span in exchange for power.

EsGod's cell activity had already started to deteriorate, and his life span had entered the elderly stage. However, he also had Esper Abilities to suppress aging and temporarily return him to his youth, which had to be triggered through sleeping. This was the reason he often slept. Usually, after intense battles, EsGod always slept.

"Black Star..."

Fakisen licked his lips. He knew that EsGod had gone to negotiate with Black Star. It clearly did not go well, and EsGod had even gone back empty-handed, which was shocking to him.

After the battlefield was cleaned up, Murraky's army returned to the border army base together with Han Xiao and the others.

There were millions of border army bases across the dynasty's wide border line. The highest position in one base was colonel.

As this battle came to its end, Han Xiao and the others bade farewell to the colonel of the base and left.

Han Xiao and Beyoni said to meet again when they had the time before going their separate ways. Beyoni left alone, while Han Xiao took Ames and the others to head toward the location where the Black Star Army was going to build a new division.

While heading there, they took a detour, and Han Xiao retrieved the Evolution Cube and the other mechanical army. He felt much more assured when the Evolution Cube was on him.

As the portable base of the army had yet to arrive, they were not in a hurry, so Han Xiao slowed down the traveling time. This was the first time Hila and the others had gone to the Central Galaxy. They made stops here and there on the way, occasionally visiting the colonial planets of the Crimson Dynasty for sightseeing.

With Han Xiao's identity, their journey was smooth.

Han Xiao had been paying attention to the Constellation Corridor page on the player forums all along and looking at the players' reactions. Ever since more than half a month ago when he spread the word at the Shattered Star Ring that he was going to the Constellation Corridor, the players there had been in a state of excitement and anticipation. They could not wait for the Black Star Army to cross Star Fields and meet them.

The transportation in the Central Galaxy was very efficient. When Han Xiao was still on the way, the army's main team finally reached its destination and arrived before the players.

Han Xiao had yet to arrive personally, but he could clearly feel the enormous impact of his army crossing servers on the Constellation Corridor page on the forums.

The passion of the players exploded!

Chapter 808: Harvesting Wild Leeks

In Galaxy, Star Fields were like individual servers with different main storylines and events. The players all had different experiences, worked for different civilizations, met different characters, and saw different scenery.

While the events in the various Star Fields were different, the overall direction was the same.

In Version 1.0, the players were born on their respective novice planets and experienced events there. In Version 2.0, the players experienced upheavals on their novice planets. Then, under the guidance of different factions, the players officially stepped into the universe and started their adventure within the Star Systems. Now, in Version 3.0, the players' stage started to gradually expand to the Star Clusters they were in. At the same time, they began to understand and become involved in more matters across Galaxy.

The professional clubs of the various countries chose different Star Fields as their base so that obtaining resources would be easier, and their local players would be more willing to start their character there. The Constellation Corridor mainly consisted of Russian and Australian professional players, as well as some clubs from smaller countries. Of course, the players could start in any Star Field they wanted, so there were players from other countries in the Constellation Corridor too.

The players there had experienced the Sodrian Rebellion on their novice planet. This planet was originally a rural territory of a Star System civilization, but it was a self-ruled area due to its history. The ruler of the planet was involved in a certain sensitive matter and was punished by the Star System civilization. Sodrian's ruler was not willing to give in and rebelled.

In the mid to late stage of Version 2.0, the rebellion was resolved, and the Star System civilization regained Sodrian. The ruler led his fleet and escaped. The players entered the universe due to external factors. As they did not have guidance like the Shattered Star Ring players had, the players of the Constellation Corridor went many separate ways. Some were recruited by Star System civilizations, some escaped with Sodrian, and some traveled the universe. They were scattered around in various factions and civilizations in the Star Systems around, completely unlike those in the Shattered Star Ring.

In Version 3.0, as the Constellation Corridor was the Crimson Dynasty's base, almost every civilization there was ruled by the dynasty, and none dared cause any trouble. Therefore, it was very peaceful there, unlike the other Star Fields. A few months after the start of the version, when the secret war main storyline in the Shattered Star Ring ended, the players in the Constellation Corridor triggered the main storyline.

As there were many factions and not much trouble, the players there looked for fun themselves. PVP became a norm, and guild wars were very frequent. As both Russia and Australia saw this place as their base, the normal players on these two sides took each other as the opposing faction. It was very boisterous.

To make communication more convenient, the players would always have public areas. The biggest safe area recognized by the Constellation Corridor areas was a trading planet called Gilman. It was a prosperous stargate transit station. Many players set up stores and looked for teams there.

The location that the Black Star Army had chosen was exactly Planet Gilman.

Just like the usual days, on this day, many players went to Planet Gilman by galactic flights and queued at the space dock of the planet. The spaceship queue extended like a river. It was quite crowded.

The guild Power and Glory's vice president 'Vodka' was in one of the spaceships together with many guild members. This guild was the official guild of the most famous club in Russia. Its goal was to provide resources to the club's professional team, 'Glory'.

Vodka was doing missions with the rest in other civilizations and gathered some equipment. This visit to Planet Gilman was to rest and store this batch of equipment in the warehouse at the guild base on the planet.

A guild officer walked into the room and reported to Vodka. "The fleet captain sent a message saying that there were some problems with the identity inspection of a certain fleet in front of us, and it will take about ten minutes till it's our turn."

"Good work." Vodka nodded.

Like the others, Vodka was browsing the forums while waiting. Many Black Star Army related posts entered his sights. He shook his head and said, "The Black Star Army topic has been trending for half a month. I wonder if they really are going to open a new division here at the Constellation Corridor."

The others joined the conversation.

"We can't even make contact with the Crimson Dynasty now. Who knows if the Black Star Army is already here?"

"Even if they're indeed coming to start a division, we might not meet them. Who knows where they will appear?"

Currently, the players at the Constellation Corridor had yet to join the Crimson Dynasty, and Han Xiao had not taken any players with him. As no player witnessed the army, the players in the Constellation Corridor did not know the whereabouts of the Black Star Army.

As they were chatting, one of them casually glanced outside the porthole. His expression suddenly stiffened. Shocked, he stared right outside the window.

"What is that‽"

The others looked over and were shocked too.

A fleet was guarding an enormous portable satellite base out of the stargate from not far away and slowly approaching Planet Gilman. Not just Vodka and the players there, all the players and the galactic residents queueing at the dock saw this.

These spaceships were marked with the Black Star Army symbol, which the Constellation Corridor players recognized.

"Black Star Army‽"

"They're here‽"

The Black Star Army's satellite base slowly stopped outside Planet Gilman and communicated with the guard army of the planet.

Looking at this, Vodka was stunned. "Wow! Could it be that... the Black Star Army is going to build their division on Planet Gilman‽"

Realizing the possibility, the surrounding guild members' expressions changed drastically, and they were overjoyed.

Not long after, news of the army's arrival spread across the entire Planet Gilman.

Very soon, the negotiation between the army and Planet Gilman's authorities was complete. Due to the identity of the army's commander and the authority given by the Crimson Dynasty, Planet Gilman had no right to prevent the army from building a division here. They had no choice but to send people to help the Black Star Army build their base.

As the players were waiting with anticipation, the army finally announced to the entire planet that they were going to build a division there!

The news became a storm in the forums. All the players in the Constellation Corridor were overjoyed and filled with excitement.

After more than half a month, the Black Star Army had appeared. The players had speculated a lot about how they would come into contact with the Black Star Army, but no one thought that the Black Star Army would directly appear in their public area!

The responses of the players were clearly displayed on the forums. The topic of the army appearing on Planet Gilman instantly became the most discussed topic on the Constellation Corridor page!

The anticipation from the past half a month turned into flames of passion!

This was the first inter-Star Field faction that the players had contact with. Even the players from other pages on the forums were attracted.

Especially the Shattered Star Ring.

At the Black Star Army headquarters in the Shattered Star Ring, countless players stopped their footsteps simultaneously and opened the forums.

"The army has crossed a Star Field!"

"The forums over there have exploded!"

"Haha, let those foreigners experience what it's like to be in our army."

"Although we're in different Star Fields, we might all belong to the same faction in the future."

The players in the Shattered Star Ring were excited and visited the Constellation Corridor page on the forums. They made a post there with the title of 'Welcome to the army, foreign friends'.

"Congratulations from the Black Star Army headquarters."

"Congratulations from the Shattered Star Ring."

"Welcome to the Black Star Army!"

"Remember, our slogan is 'Captain is awesome'!"

Through the versions, the Black Star Army had become deeply rooted in the hearts of the players. Seeing that their own growing faction had developed to such heights, many Shattered Star Ring players felt proud. It almost felt like raising a child who had finally become successful.

The various players who met Black Star long ago including Frenzied Sword, Bun-Hit-Dog, and Maple Moon felt most deeply for this. They had experienced a lot of things with the Black Star Army, and those memories resurfaced in their minds.

We've come so far...

Their feelings were complicated.

To the players, this act of the Black Star Army was like the opening of a new era. Maybe this would be the beginning of the players being able to travel between Star Fields. Maybe, one day, all the Galaxy players might be able to gather in the same Star Field, and this might be its beginning.

The influence of officially building a subdivision on Planet Gilman could be seen immediately. Almost all the players doing missions elsewhere rushed right back from various Star Systems as soon as they heard this piece of news.

From Version 2.0 when the players entered the universe, never had the players all gathered in one place in the Constellation Corridor. This time, due to the popularity of the army itself and the impact of crossing Star Fields, almost everyone gathered there!

The army subdivision made an announcement on the quantum network saying that since the subdivision had just been built, they needed to recruit a lot of manpower. The details could be found on the main page of the army.

As the players in the Constellation Corridor did not have any sense of belonging to the army, what attracted them was purely the army's fame and the potential profit. With the example of the Shattered Star Ring, almost all the older players knew how good the Black Star Army's benefits were. With Han Xiao working things for three versions, the army's brand among the players had a very high position.

Vodka finished reading the recruiting information on the communicator and sighed. "The benefits are too good..."

Be it salary, bonuses, internal services, missions, or resources, the benefits of the Black Star Army were miles better than all the factions that the Constellation Corridor had experienced!

The faction store was especially attractive. Han Xiao had tons of low-level blueprints and had mass-produced them throughout the years. Currently, the army sold more than ten thousand mechanical items and equipment of all kinds of uses and functions. There were also tailor-made options, repairs, enhancements, and other services. Other than that, there were many Dungeon Crystals, Genetic Medicines, materials, and many other items, as well as the products from other financial groups. The faction store of the army was like a trade transit station with plenty of products.

"Vice president, are we going to join the Black Star Army?"

"Come, let's go to their subdivision." Vodka was thrilled. Not mentioning how attractive the benefits of the army was, just the Black Star Army being the Crimson Dynasty's ally would have made him not hesitate about it.

Vodka took the guild members along and headed to the army's subdivision in their spaceship.

They flew into the dock, descended from their spaceship, and followed the robot receptionist to the hall. The hall was already crowded and filled with people at this time—almost all the players who were on Planet Gilman had rushed there.

There were many other big guilds there. Vodka saw many old rivals and familiar faces from guild wars.

They were all there to join the army. They had to submit their resume and participate in a test, which was mainly to test their combat capabilities. Other than the brand-new players, almost no player was still below Grade C, so this recruitment requirement was not a problem for them.

Vodka squeezed into the middle of the hall, and before him were gates leading to Combat Testing Rooms. Tons of players queued there and waited for their turn.

Vodka and the rest waited for a while before it was finally their turn. A mission popped up on their interfaces.

Faction Mission: Black Star Army Test

Mission Introduction: The rise of the Black Star Army is filled with legends. It is now a gigantic organization of the Shattered Star Ring and an ally of the Crimson Dynasty. The Black Star Army has crossed Star Fields and built a subdivision in the Central Galaxy. You have received the chance to join the army. However, the army members have all been through strict selection processes. In order to join this faction with seemingly infinite potential, you must prove your strength...

The same thing was happening to many other players.

At the same time, somewhere in the Constellation Corridor on a boisterous tourism planet...

This was a planet with close to no traces of artificial modification. Its scenery was marvelous, its water was clean, the seas were green, and the skies were blue. Its surface was covered with vegetation, and the plants emitted a faint light at night. It was dreamlike. All sorts of beautiful gentle creatures inhabited the surface. Tiny, silver creatures could be seen flying in groups between the forests, like fish swimming in the air.

"This planet is really beautiful..."

Han Xiao and the others had been passing this planet, so they stopped by to tour it. The spaceship was hovering in midair while the group of them slowly walked in the night forest. The scenery was beautiful everywhere they looked.

Aurora loved nature; it was filled with life. She walked at the front, Ames and Hila and the other Black Star Guards walked in the middle, and Han Xiao walked at the back. He was walking with his hands behind his back, looking at the backs of the others with a smile on his face.

Having lived with the smell of mechanical oil and metal for most of the time, the fresh air seemed to clear up his lungs and made him feel refreshed.

Hila slowed down and came to Han Xiao's side. She glanced at him and said, "You seem to be in a very good mood today."

Han Xiao chuckled. He would finally be harvesting the wild-grown leeks. How could he not be in a good mood?

Chapter 809: Decision and Guilds' Stand

You have joined a new faction—[Black Star Army]!

You have received a new identity—[Black Star Army Member]!

[Black Star Army] Faction Interface activated.

[Black Star Army] Contribution System activated.

[Black Star Army] Faction Store activated.

According to the relationship between [Black Star Army] and other factions, some organizations now have a different attitude toward you.

In the crowded Planet Gilman army subdivision hall, Vodka and the officers of his guild walked out of the Combat Testing Room with the crowd. They were all looking at the notification on the interface with joy.

Looking at the new unlocked faction store, they could not take their eyes away from the tons of items in it.

"Vice president, the club side just asked us how things are going."

"Haha, tell them it's great, and those professional players can join too. Almost all the knowledges up to Advanced Knowledges are sold here." Vodka rubbed his hands with excitement.

At this time, a group of guild players approached them. The one at the front was Captain Old Henry, the vice president of the Kangaroo Guild, which was the official guild of the famous Australia professional guild, Kangaroo Boxing. He was also an old rival of Vodka's; the two sides had fought quite a number of guild wars.

Captain Old Henry saw Vodka and the others and greeted them. "G'day mate, I see you guys have come earlier than us."

"You guys are here too?" Vodka stopped his footsteps and chatted with them.

After having fought each other and played together for three versions, they were considered semi-friends. When they were not fighting guild wars, their relationship was quite good. Although they were competitors, there was no need to hate each other.

"You guys have already joined?"

"That's right. There are quite a lot of people. Have fun queuing."

After chatting for a while, Captain Old Henry led his people along to take the test. Vodka watched them leave and caressed his chin.

"All the guilds will send someone to join the army," a guild officer said softly. "This means we will all be in the same faction in the future. Does that mean that competition will decrease?"

"Humph, not at all. Since the Black Star Army is planning to expand, there will definitely be a lot of missions in a short period. Among these missions, there will be good and bad ones. The large guilds will definitely fight for better missions and better resources. I think that not only will the competition between guilds not decrease, but it will be more frequent instead." Vodka shook his head and was not very optimistic.

"Really? The Chinese in the Shattered Star Ring seem to rarely have guild wars to fight for resources."

"Who said so? They're doing the same, just not as intense. After all, most guilds there are from China, so they don't fight as much with each other. Here, however, there are a lot of guilds from different countries, so we're destined to be opponents. Furthermore, we're used to opposing each other here."

Then Vodka suddenly thought of something.

"By the way, speaking of the Shattered Star Ring... we're now members of the Black Star Army. The army is an inter-Star Field faction, and its headquarters is at the Shattered Star Ring. I wonder if we can follow the army back to the Shattered Star Ring."

This was a very important question and got everyone curious.

Vodka took out the communicator and downloaded the mini army assistant.

Phillip's holographic projection appeared above the screen. He was about a finger's size and very adorable. He bowed and said with a childish voice, "Welcome to the Black Star Army's internal assistant. I'm the sub-program of the army's artificial intelligence, Phillip. Glad to be of service to the brave Black Star warriors. If you want, you can give me a new look and even give me a new name, hum..."

"Ohhh, how cute..."

The adorable projection struck Vodka's soft spot. His heart was almost melting. The originally tough and bearded muscular man was now smiling like a wrinkled flower. Traces of a Russian bear-fighting warrior were nowhere to be found.

"Ahem, vice president, maintain your image." The guild officers at the side almost wanted to carve their own eyes out.

"I want to ask, for us the new members, can we follow the army back to the Shattered Star Ring?" Vodka hastily asked.

"According to the highest order from the army commander, the members recruited here will usually be stationed here to help with the army's expansion. However, if you want to head toward the army's headquarters, it is indeed possible. According to the army's schedule, we will occasionally borrow the Crimson Dynasty's military stargate and transport resources from the headquarters to the subdivision here in the Constellation Corridor. If you want to go to the Shattered Star Ring, you can submit a request to follow the transport team on their way back, hum..."

Vodka and the others' bodies shivered as they exchanged looks of excitement—they really could go to another Star Field.

Vodka suppressed his excitement and asked, "Will the army have any teams that are heading back to the Shattered Star Ring soon?"

"Yes, hum..." Phillip said. "The Army Commander will be heading back after some time, in about one to two months. You can follow His Excellency Black Star back if you want, hum..."

Vodka nodded heavily and looked back at the others.

"We must have a chat with the president and the club..."

Those who happened to be on Planet Gilman joined the army one after another and shared the news about the army on the forums.

Players from all Star Fields were paying attention to the Constellation Corridor's forums page. Most people came to know that the Constellation Corridor players could choose to cross Star Fields and were very jealous.

Those who were still rushing back to Planet Gilman discussed this topic passionately, arguing over whether to stay or leave.

The majority of people hesitated.

"We've played here in the Constellation Corridor for so long and are very familiar with it now. We've farmed so much Faction and Character Favorability. If we go to the Shattered Star Ring, won't all that go to waste? We can still do the army's missions here. Is there really a need to start from scratch in the Shattered Star Ring?"

"That's right. We mainly joined the army for their benefits. Why would we go to the Shattered Star Ring? There are millions of players there, mostly Chinese, and they've been there since the start. We'll have to compete with them once we're there, and we have no advantages."

"Exactly. We have yet to even explore the Constellation Corridor fully, so why should we go to another Star Field?"

"This is the Central Galaxy, the most prosperous place in the entire universe. What good will it do to go to a much more rural border Star Field?"

Many players were not willing to give up the results they had achieved with the time and effort over the past three versions.

If they could go and come back any time they wanted, they would not hesitate at all. However, they could only follow the army to cross Star Fields, and who knew when the army would send another transport team? Furthermore, they also did not know if their return would be approved. If things did not go well in the Shattered Star Ring, they would waste a lot of time before they could return.

Of course, there were players who supported going to the Shattered Star Ring.

"We're the first batch of players to ever travel across Star Fields. Why give up such a great opportunity? The others can't do it even if they want to."

"I want to play with my Chinese friends over there in the Shattered Star Ring."

"Don't forget about the Flickering World mission that is pinned at the top of the army's mission list. It's clearly a new main storyline. Furthermore, according to the mission introduction, exploring the Flickering World is the Crimson Dynasty's operation. The Black Star Army is just a participant. This main storyline looks more like the dynasty's storyline! Therefore, us joining the army and exploring the Flickering World is actually doing things for the Crimson Dynasty!"

"That's right. Maybe helping the dynasty to explore a new Star Field is one of the main storylines of the Constellation Corridor, and the hidden meaning behind the Black Star Army recruiting us is to take us there so that we can participate in it."

In the past decade, the Crimson Dynasty's desire for the Flickering World had become known to the world, and those players were no exceptions. Although they still did not know how important the Flickering World would be in the future, they were very interested in it.

After the Tyrant Party, Han Xiao had kept the Flickering World's main storyline mission pinned at the top of the army's mission list, and it was very effective. It attracted the Constellation Corridor players to explore the Flickering World with him, which basically made it easier for him to move the wild leeks back to his own field to grow them together.

Of course, there was no way he could bring all the Constellation Corridor players back. Meeting the Ruler and other official matters would only take a few days, but the Great Mechanic Han had already planned to stay in the Constellation Corridor for two to three months so that the players there would have enough time to make up their minds. From his perspective, the more players that were willing to follow him back to explore the Flickering World, the better.

As the arguments on the forums became more heated, the issue's influence grew. After a few days had passed, more and more players rushed to Planet Gilman to join the army.

Very soon, the number of players on Planet Gilman exceeded two million and was still growing every day.

Almost all the big guilds had a stronghold on Planet Gilman. Very soon, the clubs of Russia, Australia, and the various smaller countries started to discuss this topic.

At the stronghold of the Power and Glory Guild, the presidents and vice presidents of the six large Russian guilds gathered. These six guilds were the biggest guilds in Russia, and they all had a club behind them. They basically represented the entire Russian professional player circle. They would occasionally have guild wars with each other, but when there was something crucial, they would also discuss the matter together.

"Guys, have your clubs decided? Will you stay or leave?" the president of the Power and Glory guild asked.

"The people above said that the professional players won't be going but told us to send some of the guild's people to the Shattered Star Ring and try to open a sub-guild."

"Us too. Those people at the club feel that the opportunity to cross Star Fields is rare, and we can't give it up. It might lead to greater benefits in the future."

The rest replied one after another. Power and Glory's president looked around the group and said, "Looks like our plans are all similar. For us, we decided to have the vice president take some people there and open the way for us."

Vodka stepped out and nodded at everyone.

"I wonder what the Australians will do. Probably the same as us."

"So, we still have to compete with them even at the Shattered Star Ring. Then we must take some normal players there, or we will be at a disadvantage in terms of manpower."

As these six guilds were the recognized representatives of the professional circle, they had a certain amount of authority to the normal players. If they expressed their stand to the normal players, it would attract quite a number of people to do the same.

"Hey, not just the Australian guilds. That place is the Chinese's territory."

"Let's communicate with the Chinese clubs first. They've been there for three versions. It's better to notify them before going."

At the same time, the Australian guilds also gathered and came to a similar conclusion.

The Russia and Australia clubs contacted the top Chinese guilds very soon. As they were all in the professional circle, they had the contact details of each other.

The various large Chinese guilds had a conference.

[Jade Green Sky entered the chat room.]

[Morning Snow Twilight Frost entered the chat room.]

[Jupiter entered the chat room.]

The presidents of the four biggest clubs—Temple of God, Long Sky, Dynasty, and Fried Eggplants With Fish—as well as Thunder Storm, Fanatics, Rivervale, and other known official guilds all joined the chat room.

"Those Europeans and Australian guilds are planning to come here? What are they trying to do?" Sky Territory president, Jade Green Sky, asked.

Drizzling Rivers president, Mountain Rain, sight. "The Shattered Star Ring is our base. We've worked here for three versions. What are the people at the club thinking to agree with this?"

"Whatever the club says, I'm okay with it," Nine Gates president, Three Times Three Equals 9, said in his local dialect.

"... Type in Mandarin, I can't understand!" Guild of Gods president, Jupiter, exclaimed.

Although they were the managers of the guilds under their clubs, they had no say in this matter and could only follow what the upper echelons of the guilds wanted them to do. The people above told them to prepare for the possible competition, so they could only obey.

Of course, the clubs were not willing to fight for resources with more competitors and wanted to have the army's resources for themselves, but this was not for them to decide.

The actions of the Black Star Army were decided by the storyline. Since the army had decided to bring some people back, they could only accept the truth.

Of course, they were not worried. The Shattered Star Ring was their headquarters, so they were at a massive advantage. The players from the Constellation Corridor had no way to beat them.

If those foreign guilds were not going to cause trouble, there would be no problem. However, if they wanted to fight for profits with the Chinese clubs... the Chinese clubs would not mind starting a war to secure the resources of their professional players and show those foreign guilds who the real masters of the Shattered Star Ring were.

As this topic triggered discussion between both the Constellation Corridor and the Shattered Star Ring players, Han Xiao, who had been taking his time sightseeing on the way, finally arrived at Planet Gilman. This was the first time that the players of another Star Field had seen him in person.

Chapter 811: Tinder Awakening and Origin of Mechanical Lives

Every Ultimate Knowledge involved the territory of the gods. The prerequisite to learning them was an extremely high Intelligence.

Han Xiao did not choose the Energy Branch [Mechanical Life Tinder] just to activate [King's Mentor]. It was also because this Ultimate Knowledge had a very wide application range.

Compared to the Virtual Technology Ultimate Knowledge, [Mechanical Life Tinder] was more useful for him now.

As the complex knowledge flew into his mind, images flashed before Han Xiao's eyes.

On the desolate black earth, a man planted a mass of metal. As time passed, mechanical cities rose from the ground, and metal spread out on the surface extremely quickly and replaced the black soil. Countless blue, well-dressed beings kneeled on the ground. Their minds entered mechanical bodies through pipes one after another, leaving their physical bodies behind.

In a rift under the ground, countless scrap parts scattered around in the darkness. One day, a golden streak of lightning landed from outside the sky right onto the waste mechanical parts, and a golden energy wave expanded. The scrap mechanical parts were united into one by an invisible force, forming a rough mechanical life..."

"These are the origins of mechanical lives..." All kinds of images flashed past as Han Xiao's understanding deepened.

Machines were initially just tools, tools that countless races learned to use and build as their civilizations grew. There were countless races in Galaxy, but mechanical lives born from nature were almost non-existent. Most of them were artificially built.

Some races built mechanical soldiers for war, which led to mechanical lives. Some left their weak body behind and became mechanical lives to get through a disaster. Some races lacked the ability to move themselves so they created mechanical lives as slaves.

Beyond Grade A Mechanics were the peak of creating mechanical lives.

As the knowledge learning was complete, Han Xiao took a deep breath and slowed down his mind.

He looked at the new abilities on the interface. [Ultimate Knowledge Possessor] was the talent rewarded when learning the first Ultimate Knowledge, and [Mechanical Life Creator] was the talent given by [Mechanical Life Tinder].

Han Xiao then looked at the new ability, [Tinder Awakening]. This was the most important one.

With a thought in his mind, the hovering guards behind him trembled and flew in front of him. They assembled with cracking sounds into a human-shaped mechanical soldier.

It had silver alloy armor and a streamlined body, and cannon barrels were embedded in its palms, knees, shoulders, and head. Psionic blue light emitted from within the armor's gaps. It had a very heavy futuristic vibe.

This was one of the elite mechanical soldiers that Han Xiao could build. Its name was Hovering Fissionist. It could both act as his hovering guard and assemble into a mechanical soldier. It was an orange, high-level machine.

This Hovering Fissionist was controlled by the combat artificial intelligence, Sparta. It stood still before Han Xiao.

"Let's see its effects..."

Buzz!

Han Xiao raised his palm, clenched his fist, and used [King's Mentor].

A mass of blue and gold Mechanical Force appeared in his palm and made cracking sounds like a thunder cloud. The next moment, this mass of Mechanical Force dashed onto the Hovering Fissionist, turning into electric sparks on its mechanical surface. Then, they entered through the gaps between the Hovering Fissionist's armor and fused into its energy furnace.

Han Xiao did not stop there. Another mass of Mechanical Force appeared in his palm and entered the Hovering Fissionist. It was [Machinery Fusion].

After that, Han Xiao activated [Tinder Awakening]. Gold light shot out from his eyes, a bright gold sphere of Mechanical Force appeared on his hand, it was blinding.

Although [Tinder Awakening] did not have a cooldown, it could only be used on targets already enhanced by [King's Mentor] and [Machinery Fusion], and these two abilities had cooldowns.

These three abilities in addition to [Emperor's Gift] were the complete set of abilities to create a mechanical life.

Han Xiao extended his hand forward, bright gold Mechanical Force flowed into the Hovering Fissionist.

His health, stamina, and energy immediately decreased a huge chunk.

Having lost half his health and energy instantly, he felt extremely weak.

This ability is really tiring to use... Han Xiao's mouth twitched. Ever since I became a Beyond Grade A Super, this should be the most health I've ever lost in a single instance...

He exhaled and let his body slowly recover, staring at the Hovering Fissionist before him.

Ding!

Suddenly, the light from the energy of the Hovering Fissionist became much brighter!

The next second, the mechanical parts on it moved on their own. The armor plates on its surface opened and closed like scales.

Clank!

Han Xiao could feel that the Hovering Fissionist was going through a change on the microscopic level.

Countless nano-grade silica-based neural fibers grew extremely quickly in its body. The parts on its body gradually turned into an organic 'whole'. The electrical sparks of a mind ignited in its chip, forming special thinking organs and fundamental logic. Energy flowed through its entire body and fueled this change.

Bang!

It was as if something in the Hovering Fissionist had awoken and ignited the tinder of life.

Hum...

This lasted quite a while before the light emitted from the Hovering Fissionist returned to normal.

Han Xiao sized it up and said, "Sparta, give me the inspection report."

"... Inspection complete. A new consciousness has been born in this unit. It's very young and is trying to communicate with me. I temporarily closed its network port. What should I do now? Please give the order, master."

Sparta appeared in the quantum network and spoke with a serious and formal tone, completely different from how lively Phillip was.

"Hmm... Build a data firewall around its consciousness first, and check its fundamental logic to see if an order to never betray me is fixed. Open its network port and filter some information for it to download."

Han Xiao gave the order and slapped Hovering Fissionist to deal some damage, triggering the combat information.

Hovering Fissionist's attributes appeared on the interface—there was no longer the equipment introduction but the attributes of a character.

The race was shown to be [Mechanical Life] and its level was as high as Lv185. It could level up like normal creatures. Its armor value became its health, and its various parameters became its other attributes. Its weapons and parts became many talents and abilities that had growth potential.

It has become a living unit.

"Sparta, let it control its own body."

Sparta responded and temporarily stopped controlling the Hovering Fissionist.

Hum!

Hovering Fissionist shivered. Its tensed body seemed to have relaxed. It then stretched his head around as if it was adapting to the vision provided by its senses. It raised its palm and touched its face.

It felt completely different.

When the combat artificial intelligence controlled all the mechanical soldiers at once, although their movements were not stiff, they did not make any unnecessary movements and were objects that only followed orders. When control was given back to the Hovering Fissionist, its movement felt immediately lively. It had become a living being that could think, doubt, and move on its own will.

Phillip and Sparta were artificial intelligence; their nature was different compared to mechanical lives. Mechanical lives' individual consciousness was equivalent to their 'freedom' and 'soul'; they had emotions and feelings.

However, that consciousness was born from the circuits in their chips, so they did not have the general 'soul'. Hence, they were immune to normal psychic and mind attacks. To the mechanical lives, only the Virtual Mechanics' attacks were considered 'mind attacks', as they could hack into the consciousness of mechanical lives and rewrite their fundamental logic.

Han Xiao had preset the ordering logic of Hovering Fissionist to be one level lower than his artificial intelligence, so orders from his artificial intelligence were like military orders that could not be disobeyed.

Hovering Fissionist looked around. It turned to look at Han Xiao and said in a wondering tone, "Mas... ter?"

It used the Universal Language.

Han Xiao nodded. He then walked around it once and sized it up from head to toe.

Hovering Fissionist stood still, but its head turned 360 degrees to keep looking at Han Xiao. It was filled with the ignorance and doubts of a newborn baby.

Why does it feel a little creepy? Han Xiao asked, "Is there anything you want to ask?"

"Want? To? Ask?" Hovering Fissionist said word by word as if its consciousness circuits were quickly working. After some thinking, it then asked, "Who... am I? Where... am I? What should I do?"

Okay, the ultimate three questions... Han Xiao thought it was funny. He then shook his head and said, "Sparta, open its network port and send it data."

The next moment, Hovering Fissionist's movements stopped. An enormous stream of data relating to the universe, life, and combat entered its consciousness and was quickly digested. It skipped the ignorant stage of a newborn instantly.

It stayed silent for a while before suddenly getting down on one knee and changing the way it spoke.

"Your Excellency Black Star, my creator."

Its voice system simulated a respectful tone.

Han Xiao raised his brows, thought for a moment, and asked, "Now, do you know who you are?"

"My name is Psionic Prime." It gave itself a name.

Psionic Prime? Why don't you call yourself Optimus Prime? Han Xiao complained in his mind.

"You're the first mechanical life I've created. Show me your strength."

Ka ka ka!

Psionic Prime moved and tested weapons one after another. It disassembled into singular hovering guards and flew around like butterflies before assembling again. Its combat style was extremely swift and flashy—mechanical lives had a very high application level to their own bodies. They could acquire abilities on their own and fix them on their character information interfaces.

Han Xiao's Mechanical Force bonus was effective on it as well. Psionic Prime was stronger than it was before Tinder Awakening.

"Come back."

After some testing, Han Xiao gave an order, and Psionic Prime automatically disassembled into hovering guards and floated around him obediently.

"Not bad." Han Xiao was satisfied and started planning in his head.

He could only create mechanical lives with self-growth potential using the set of abilities including [Tinder Awakening], [King's Mentor], and others, so its efficiency was limited, only creating elite and mini-boss units over time.

As for the majority of mechanical soldiers, Han Xiao was not planning to turn them into mechanical lives. One reason for this was the efficiency limit; he had to turn the high-level machinery first. Another reason was that the casualties of those mechanical soldiers were too high, so its long-term effect would be inferior compared to high-level machinery.

"After turning into mechanical lives, their growth potential is increased tremendously, and they are even able to grow into mechanical civilizations. Manison has some mechanical civilizations under his command..."

Han Xiao pondered. He could imitate this and let his mechanical lives develop into civilizations.

If he had a mechanical civilization under his command, they would automatically operate, reproduce, and create offspring, which meant that they would provide him with a continuous source of soldiers. The only problem was that this was extremely time-consuming.

However, his life span and the time between version updates were both very long, so this was not a huge problem.

"Or can I take someone else's mechanical civilization?" Han Xiao got rid of this thought as soon as it came up. He thought it was better not to create enemies everywhere.

Steady and firm, that was the Great Mechanic Han's personality.

Having learned an Ultimate Knowledge, Han Xiao was content and had a smile on his face. He walked out of the workshop and saw a few people immediately. Hila and the Black Star Guards were all waiting at his door.

"What are you guys doing here?" Han Xiao looked around and then fixed his eyes on Hadavy. This guy stood at the front of everyone else and had a mysterious smile on his face.

Hadavy took out a deck of Wayne Cards and showed Han Xiao the top card. "Look, your card has been updated again."

Han Xiao looked at it. This was the Strong Card with his image on it.

"Black Star—Han Xiao."

It was finally updated to become a Beyond Grade A, as well as the 'Crimson Dynasty Ally' trait. Its description also included his fight with Heber and Psyker, and its card effects were greatly increased.

"Isn't that just a matter of time? Did you guys come all the way just to show me this?"

Han Xiao was speechless. With his position, how could the Wayne Card company not update his card?

Hadavy chuckled and skillfully moved his fingers to fan the cards. Han Xiao looked through it and raised his brows. These cards were Hila, Feidin, and the others. They were now marked as 'Black Star Guards'. Like the Bloodshed Land's Vanguard Officials, they had their own cards.

One of the reasons he had formed the Black Star Guards was to make Hila and the others famous. Now, this goal was achieved. The Black Star Guards name became their identity, and they were now famous, so they came to share this piece of good news with Han Xiao.

"That's not bad, congratulations on becoming known in the universe." Han Xiao smiled and casually rubbed Feidin's shoulders, which led to Chen Xing rolling her eyes.

This time, Aurora spoke with her crispy voice. "Uncle, one more thing, there's someone special here to see you."

"Who? Someone from the dynasty?"

"No, that guy calls himself the ruler of Sodrian. His name is Troy."

Sodrian's ruler?

Sodrian was the novice planet of the Constellation Corridor players in Version 1.0. Due to its ruler being involved in sensitive political matters, the ruler was treated as a traitor. The ruler then escaped with his fleet and hid from everyone, still not captured till today.

What is this guy doing here? Han Xiao was curious.

...

Troy was the only one in the conference room, and he seemed to have a lot on his mind.

He was a tall humanoid. His yellow hair was tied into a foreign-style braid. His eyes were sharp, and his nose was a pair of small holes in the middle of his eyes. He was not considered to be ugly looking, just quite old. He had two hands and two legs but no tail. He had a pair of large wings behind his back with yellow feathers on them.

"Will Black Star help me?" Troy's eyes flashed.

He escaped with his fleet and had been chased by the Star System civilization till now. The situation was not looking very bright. If this continued, he would be captured by the Star System civilization sooner or later. Due to the political secrets that he was involved in, Troy knew that if he was captured, his fate would be worse than death.

Just as he was being extremely anxious about his future, he received the news about the Black Star Army building a subdivision and recruiting manpower on a large scale on Planet Gilman. Suddenly, he saw some hope and felt that Black Star Army might be able to help him.

He just had to join the Black Star Army and follow the army's fleet to borrow the Crimson Dynasty's stargate, leave the Central Galaxy, and take refuge in the Shattered Star Ring. That way, he would be safe.

Troy initially wanted to hide his identity while joining the army and secretly smuggle his way out of the Central Galaxy. However, he thought about it and felt that the risk of being discovered by a Beyond Grade A was too high, and he would very likely be discovered. By then, he would lose even this opportunity. Therefore, he felt that it was better to request to see Black Star, explain the situation, and sincerely make his proposal to convince Black Star to help them.

In his eyes, the only way he could rise again was to leave the Central Galaxy and return in the future to take revenge on his political enemies.

When he thought of how his political enemies had destroyed what he had been working on for so many years, Troy's expression became more furious and full of hatred.

He was now a traitor and would never be able to return to his civilization. The only thing he could do was flee. If he ever got the chance, he would destroy his political enemy's everything without hesitation and take revenge on the civilization that kept hunting him down.

Swoosh.

The sound of the door opening broke Troy's train of thought. He hastily stood up and looked at Han Xiao with admiration.

"Your Excellency Black Star," Troy hastily greeted respectfully and introduced himself, deliberately acting trepidatious.

"I've heard about you. You're now a rebel. What do you want from me?" Han Xiao asked.

"Well..." Troy took a deep breath and used the sincere tone that he had practiced a hundred times to explain the situation in words he had prepared long beforehand.

Basically, he was saying that he was framed by his political enemy and misunderstood by his civilization. In order to protect himself, he could only resist and escape, which forced him to become a rebel. He wanted to join the Black Star Army and work for the army, in exchange for an opportunity to take refuge in the Shattered Star Ring.

"I see..." Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and sized Troy up.

Suddenly, he seemed to have recalled something, and the look on his face became strange.

Chapter 812: Stealing Leeks Makes Me Happy

Looking at Troy's trepidatious and respectful expression, Han Xiao chuckled and asked, "So what you mean is, the reason you're in this situation today is all because you were framed, and you're innocent, right?"

Troy swallowed and said, "I was tricked by my political enemy. They framed me for many crimes."

"Oh..." Han Xiao did not express whether he believed Troy's explanation and said, "So, now you want to take refuge under my command and let me protect you?"

"I won't dare to ask for your protection," Troy said cautiously. "All I'm asking is for you to allow me to follow the Black Star Army's fleet and leave the Central Galaxy through the stargate. I'm wanted by a Star System civilization. I can't use any stargates without someone's help.

Han Xiao laughed and shook his head. "All the civilizations in the Constellation Corridor are ruled by the dynasty. Don't you know that I'm the dynasty's ally? You're now a wanted criminal of a civilization under the dynasty's rule. It's already kind of me not to capture you right here, but you still want me to bear the risk and take you to the Shattered Star Ring? All you have are words, yet you want me to help you for free. Do I look like a philanthropist to you?"

"No, no, you're mistaken." Troy quickly waved his hands. "Although I do want to take refuge here, my intention to join the Black Star Army is sincere. Your rise in the Shattered Star Ring has spread across the universe, and I've admired you for a very long time. If you don't mind, I'm willing to work for you and be loyal to you in the future."

"Oh?" Han Xiao placed his elbows on the table, and his palms crossed before his nose. He stared at Troy and slowly said, "You said you're innocent, do you think I believe that? Your ambitions failed, and you're wanted by a civilization, so you want me to back you up and use my name to pay the cost of your failure for you. Do you think there are such great things in the world?"

In fact, this guy was not innocent at all. In the years he ruled Sodrian, he secretly planned a lot of conspiracies to obtain more power. When these things got exposed, he rebelled against the civilization. His political enemies did indeed exaggerate some of the things he did, but he was no saint.

The situation Troy explained to Han Xiao was not completely untrue; he just changed some of the reasoning behind it and deliberately kept the factors regarding his own ambitions a secret. He wanted to put the blame on others and make his crimes seem less severe, so he would look like he was forced and helpless, which he deludedly hoped would lower Han Xiao's suspicion toward him.

However, this was completely ineffective to Han Xiao. Sodrian was the earliest novice planet in the Constellation Corridor. With so much information that the players had dug up, Han Xiao knew what had happened all too well. Troy could not hide it from him at all.

Furthermore, Han Xiao had searched through the forums and found a hidden mission in the Galaxy Chronicles recorded by the Constellation Corridor players. When Troy was retreating and fleeing, he arranged people to plant enough high energy explosives in the political building of Sodrian's capital city to wipe out more than ten blocks. He completely ignored the civilian casualties and was extremely cruel. However, this triggered the players' hidden mission, and the trap was destroyed by the players. This was more than enough to prove that Troy was nothing but a cruel and heartless man who would have his revenge no matter the means and the unnecessary casualties.

Under Han Xiao's glare, Troy's expression stiffened. He was anxious. If not because he had no other way out, he would not have taken such a desperate gamble. He clenched his teeth, let go of all his pride, and suddenly dropped prone before Han Xiao. In the universally accepted cultural standards, this position represented complete obedience.

"With your position, who dares lie to you! It's my fault for not saying things clearly and causing your misunderstanding. I am sorry. Please save my life. I'm willing to work for you forever."

Han Xiao curled his lips in his mind. He knew exactly what Troy was intending to do—it was nothing but an attempt to take refuge after making a huge mistake. Since the army was recruiting, he thought that this was his opportunity, so he intended to use sweet words to convince him.

If not because Troy had a special use to him, he would have let people capture Troy long ago in exchange for the bounty.

Han Xiao stood up, glanced at the top of Troy's head, and said, "I don't need your loyalty, and I don't need your appreciation even more. I'm too lazy to capture you, so I'll act as if I never saw you. Get out of my sight right now and don't let me see you again, or else..."

Whoosh!

The door opened, and Hila walked in. She stared at Troy coldly, clearly signifying him to piss off.

Troy's face was pressed onto the floor, and his expression could not be seen. Only after two seconds did he stand up and pat his shirt as if he was patting away the non-existent dust. With his head down, his eyes were fixed to the floor, and he did not dare look up at Han Xiao's eyes. Under Hila's sharp gaze, he walked out of the room step by step silently with clenched fists and was escorted out of the subdivision.

After he left, Han Xiao's expression relaxed and turned into an odd smile.

"I wonder if this will be of use in the future..."

The Great Mechanic Han had a motive to deliberately let Troy leave. As the main storyline NPC of one of the novice planets, Troy still had some storyline in him. According to how things turned out in his previous life, Troy would barely escape from the chase in the end.

Since he was a wanted man, he fled to the border of the Central Galaxy and survived there. Afterward, he was accepted by the Fallen Ark and became one of EsGod's subordinates, but he did not even make it to the officer position. The players only noticed and recorded this because he was once the main storyline NPC of a novice planet.

The fact that an important NPC in the early stages became someone so insignificant in the later stages was like an Easter egg to the players, which was why Han Xiao remembered Troy.

Therefore, before Han Xiao let Troy leave, he secretly planted a ward on him.

EsGod was immune to the Observer's Mark, but Troy's appearance gave Han Xiao a flash of insight. If Troy joined the Fallen Ark in the future like he did in his previous life, Han Xiao would be able to monitor EsGod's movements.

Although he had no idea when and if this would work out, since it was not a significant plot, Han Xiao was casual about it. After all, he did not have any good way to deal with EsGod yet. It would be great if this ended up working, but it would not be a big deal even if it did not.

Forty days passed very quickly.

Han Xiao stayed on Planet Gilman the whole time, waiting for the subdivision to recruit more people. During this time, he expanded his mechanical army every day and used the new Ultimate Knowledge to slowly create mechanical lives. Starting with Psionic Prime, he now had three thousand first-generation mechanical lives under his command.

There were a few reasons he did not create more. Firstly, [King's Mentor]'s cooldown used days as a unit, and this was the prerequisite ability of [Tinder Awakening].

Secondly, although [Tinder Awakening] could be used on multiple targets at the same time, its upper limit was not very high. Even at its maximum level, it could only be used on little more than ten targets at once. Furthermore, Han Xiao had discovered that if he used it on multiple targets at the same time, their initial level would not be as high compared to if he used it only on one target. The cost of this ability was the same, be it single or multiple targets, so when his energy was spread among multiple targets, they naturally received less energy individually.

Thirdly... his body could not take it if he used it too frequently.

This had also made Han Xiao's thoughts about developing a mechanical civilization firmer. The efficiency of creating mechanical lives was not high just with [Tinder Awakening]. His health and energy recovered fast, but stamina required rest to recover. In comparison, a fully developed mechanical civilization could provide him with a supply of soldiers at a much faster efficiency without him having to put in so much effort.

In the past forty days, the recruiting of the Planet Gilman subdivision had settled.

There were many Beyond Grade A organizations in the Central Galaxy, so the Black Star Army's appeal there was not as high as back in the Shattered Star Ring. The Planet Gilman subdivision had recruited little more than ten million new members, and it was slowing down. Compared to the Beyond Grade A organizations in the Central Galaxy, this number was quite low. This was only the beginning for this subdivision.

Among the new members, more than four million were players, which made up about eighty-five percent of all the players in the Constellation Corridor. Through the army's benefits and word of mouth on the forums, the majority of the Constellation Corridor players had rushed there to join.

Of the more than four million players, most decided to become members of the mercenary department. There were two types of army members; one was the full member who obeyed the army's orders, and the other was the semi-member who worked for the army but generally had complete freedom. Mercenaries were a typical example of the latter.

The mercenary system was lenient, and the mercenary department of the army did not violate the rules of galactic mercenaries. Most of the Constellation Corridor players were there for the benefits, so being mercenaries was a choice with more freedom. They basically had a very simple relationship with the army of doing things for the army in exchange for resources; this way, their faction would not be locked.

Han Xiao was not surprised about this. The players in the other Star Field had just met his army. He knew that feelings needed time to develop.

He gave the Constellation Corridor players more than enough time to make their choices. Among the more than four million players, seven hundred thousand accepted the Flickering World main storyline mission and requested to go to the Shattered Star Ring with the army.

The majority of the seven hundred thousand players were normal players. The remaining millions of players decided to stay in their birth Star Field to continue exploring while watching how things turned out for those that decided to go to the Shattered Star Ring.

Han Xiao was able to dig up seven hundred thousand leeks just in the first batch, so he was quite satisfied with this.

It was the day of departure. An enormous Black Star Army transport fleet was ready to leave—all seven hundred thousand players had already boarded the ships.

At this time, players from all the Star Fields were paying attention to this occasion from the broadcasts on the forums.

All the players were interested in the first time a player would cross a Star Field. This might be an example for them in the future when they got the chance to do the same. Therefore, this became the most-watched occasion ever since the Black Star Army's creation. Its popularity among the players had broken the record!

On the transport ships, the players chatted with excitement.

"I wonder what it feels to travel across Star Fields. How will it be different from normal stargates?"

"Will the Shattered Star Ring players bully us?"

"Guys, do you think something fun will happen if we jump out of the ship in the stargate?"

"Guards! That's the guy!"

Inside the command room of the main ship, Hila leaned against the wall with her arms crossed, Aurora busily operated on the main pilot seat, and Feidin stood beside her and watched.

Hadavy sat on the sofa with a blue, square-shaped crystal wine bottle in his hand, gulping down the mercury colored wine inside that made him choke and his face blush. Wayne Cards were on the table; the rule was to drink if you lost. There was a pile of empty bottles beside his seat, and opposite him was the speechless old man Aesop who had been dragged there.

Ames stood behind the scenery window with hands behind her back and looked at the fleet around. With Han Xiao, Hila, and Aesop, these people she was close to accompanying her for the past more than a month holiday, she had quite a good time.

Han Xiao stood before the star map. The destination had been set long ago. When everyone had boarded, he gave out an order to the entire fleet.

"Depart."

Boom!

The thrusters shot out flames, and the battleships took off.

"We've finally departed!" The many players on the ships were thrilled, and the countless people watching on the forums were looking closely.

The fleet slowly headed away from the Planet Gilman subdivision and accelerated. Carrying seven hundred thousand leeks, it headed to the Shattered Star Ring.

Chapter 813: Ames' Request

The Crimson Dynasty Military Shattered Star Ring Stargate Station, the Black Star Army transport ships rode out from the blue vortex stargate one after another, as the space energy covering their shields quickly dissipated.

"We're back." Inside the main ship's command room, Han Xiao exhaled.

Despite being prosperous and peaceful, the shadow of the universal civilizations always shrouded the Central Galaxy like a mountain, giving him an invisible sense of pressure. Although Shattered Star Ring was rural, he had been there for more than twenty years, and this was the army's headquarters; he felt calmer and secure there.

Ames walked to his side, looked out the universe outside the porthole, and said, "I've had quite a good time traveling with you guys for the past two months. Now we're home, I shall get going."

"What's the hurry? Come with us."

"Floating Dragon recently drifted to another Star Cluster. We're not on the way for you."

Han Xiao reluctantly nodded and said, "Alright then, I'll have my men prepare a spaceship for you. By the way, the preparations on the dynasty's side are almost complete, so I'll be departing very soon to explore the Flickering World. Do you want to come? There should be much new and interesting stuff there."

Ames waved and said, "That's the Crimson Dynasty's mission. I won't go."

Aesop rubbed his beard and interrupted them. "Yesterday, I had a new prophecy that's related to the Flickering World."

Another prophecy? Han Xiao's eyes sparkled and said with curiosity, "Old man, you've helped me with your prophecy ability again?"

"Er... let me explain. I did not help you particularly. It's just that those people who are close to me will have some kind of fate connection with me, and my ability can randomly sense what might happen to these people in the future. It's like a dream, very blurry, basically just a feeling.

"Yesterday, I sensed what might happen to you in the Flickering World..."

Then, Aesop paused and said in a very serious tone, "You'd better be careful about the Arcane Church."

The Arcane Church? Have they still not given up taking back the Evolution Cube? It does seem possible.

Han Xiao blinked and realized that Aesop did not continue. "Is that it? Don't you have any useful information like time and location or something?"

Aesop shrugged. "Things can change any time since the future is so far ahead. There's no accurate prophecy, just intuition."

"Got it. I'll keep a lookout and have people keep an eye on the movements of the Star Pupil Holy Race. If the Arcane Church wants to do something to me, Psyker will definitely be part of it."

Han Xiao nodded and patted Aesop's shoulder.

"Oh, by the way, one more thing." Aesop rubbed his beard. "I heard that some Ancient Ones members have been secretly asking around about you. A few of them seems to be interested in you."

Han Xiao looked at Aesop from head to toe and said with a doubtful tone, "Where did you hear that?"

"I used to be one of them. What's so weird about me having a few friends?" Aesop shrugged. "When I followed you to the dynasty's capital and met those dynasty allies, Ravenlaude told the other Ancient Ones about me. Now, those guys all know that a former member of the Ancient Ones is now with you and Ames, so some friends contacted me."

Han Xiao could not help but feel amazed. For someone this ancient like Aesop, both his connections and history were unfathomable. Somehow, Aesop could always obtain information that was extremely rare and inaccessible to most people.

"Who are the ones that are asking about me?"

"Manison, Sun Hunter, Void Overlord..." Aesop's voice suddenly got deeper and said with a soft voice, "And Thousand Shadows."

Other than Manison, Han Xiao did not have any contact with the first few Ancient Ones. Sun Hunter was a Cannon Master, and Void Overlord was a Void being, so Han Xiao had no idea why they were asking about him. However, when Aesop mentioned Thousand Shadows, Han Xiao's eyes narrowed immediately.

Back when they interrogated Thousand Shadows' Shadow Warriors, Aesop was the one who had helped. Aesop knew that Thousand Shadows had once had his eyes on Han Xiao, so he mentioned this to alert him.

"Maybe he still wants to capture me or something. He's in the Federation of Light's Star Field, so I can't do anything for the time being. I'll wait till I have the chance to deal with him." Han Xiao committed this matter to memory.

The mission [Prey] was still inactive. In the past, he did not know if Thousand Shadows had given up on him, but now, it seemed that this guy had yet to give up. However, he was no longer a Calamity Grade, so Thousand Shadows would not be able to capture him so easily.

This time, Ames suddenly said, "Black Star, I've been thinking about something recently, and I want to discuss it with you."

Han Xiao turned to look at Ames and captured a tint of hesitation on her face. This was very rare for Ames, so Han Xiao said curiously, "What do you want to discuss with me? Do you want to borrow money? Is fifty million Enas enough?"

"Who's borrowing money from you? Do you think I'm that poor?" Ames's brow twitched slightly. "Actually... I've been thinking about Floating Dragon's development plan recently..."

Both Aesop and Han Xiao's eyes widened immediately. Their faces were filled with complete shock.

"What happened to you? Is that something you should be thinking about?"

"Am I this unreliable to you?" Ames said with resignation. "I'm Floating Dragon's leader. What's so strange about me thinking for my organization occasionally?"

"It wouldn't be strange for others, but for you... it is indeed strange! Who doesn't know how laz... ahem, carefree you are?"

Han Xiao changed his words at the last minute and hid his giggle. Ames had never thought about developing her faction, and her slacker image was already deeply rooted in everyone's heart. God only knew why she suddenly changed her mind.

"Stop kidding, I'm serious this time." Ames gave Han Xiao a glare.

She had never been passionate about growing her organization, but that had lasted for too long, and she felt like it was time to make a change—especially after how she witnessed Han Xiao leading the rise of the Black Star Army for the past ten or so years with her own eyes. With such a positive example, it made her feel a tiny bit interested in growing her own forces. She wanted to imitate Han Xiao and operate Floating Dragon Island better. It had nothing to do with her ambition or anything of that sort; Ames mainly saw it as an interesting thing to do.

However, Ames was never going to admit to Han Xiao that the things he did were what piqued her interest.

"Alright then, I'll pretend it's serious..." Seeing the not so friendly glint in Ames' eyes, Han Xiao tried his best not to laugh and waved his hands. "Okay, okay. It's serious. So, you want to develop Floating Dragon. What do you want to discuss with me?"

Ames stayed silent for a while before slowly saying, "Floating Dragon has been drifting in the universe for a very long time. I want to make it stay in one place."

Han Xiao pondered for a while before nodding.

"Yo, that's quite a good idea. With a fixed location for the headquarters, it'll be easier for people to feel confident about Floating Dragon. As a Beyond Grade A, you have an extraordinary amount of appeal. As long as you can turn the image that the Shattered Star Ring Supers have about you around and show that you're serious about expanding, the number of people who are willing to work for you will definitely be tens and hundreds of times more than now.

Han Xiao caressed his chin, sized Ames up, and joked, "Plus, you're pretty, so your appeal might be even stronger than mine."

Ames' expression became odd. She stared at Han Xiao and said in a shocked and doubtful tone, "You actually think I'm pretty‽"

"What's so strange about that?" Han Xiao was confused. He had no idea why Ames had such an exaggerated response.

Han Xiao shook his head and got back to the topic. "Have you decided on where Floating Dragon should stay?"

"That's what I wanted to discuss with you..." Ames calmed her emotions. She seemed to hesitate for half a second before slowly saying, "I'm planning to have Floating Dragon stay at Planet Aquamarine. What do you think?"

Han Xiao was stunned in place.

"No?" Ames raised her brows and gave a faint smile. "More than ten years ago, your mother planet faced a disaster. Through the galactic media channels, you announced that Floating Dragon was interested in Planet Aquamarine. Using Floating Dragon's name, Planet Aquamarine has received a lot of investments and funding from a ton of financial groups and has been developing very well. Even Godora allowed Floating Dragon's control over Planet Aquamarine... You're not going to go back on your word, are you?"

Han Xiao shook his head with resignation. During that time, the Black Star Mercenary Group had still been a tiny organization that belonged to Floating Dragon. Only through using Floating Dragon Island's name had he been able to give Planet Aquamarine the opportunity to so quickly step into the galaxy.

After he left Floating Dragon, the Black Star Army had taken over the management of Planet Aquamarine. Floating Dragon did not say anything about it, so he thought Ames did not mind. Unexpectedly, Ames suddenly brought it up.

"Since Planet Aquamarine is a planet ruled by my Floating Dragon on paper..." Ames' smiled brightly. Han Xiao's troubled expression made her very delighted. She smiled and said, "It should be justifiable for me to choose Planet Aquamarine as the location of my headquarters, shouldn't it?"

"Are you going to chase my people away from my mother planet?" Han Xiao was surprised. Planet Aquamarine was the foundation of his seat in the Shattered Star Ring Civilization Conference. There was no way he would give it to anyone else.

"Am I such a horrible person to you?" Ames said with a displeased tone. "Don't worry, just like your army's headquarters, Floating Dragon Island will just be parked outside the planet's atmosphere and will not interfere with Planet Aquamarine's government. That's why I'm discussing it with you."

Han Xiao's eyes spun around. If that was the case, not only would it not be a bad thing—it would be a great thing.

In the time that the army headquarters had stayed around Planet Golden Gate, it had brought Planet Golden Gate an almost unparalleled chance for development. Its economy, security, and many other aspects had improved tremendously since then, and it had become a beyond top tier colonial planet of Godora.

If Ames did the same, Planet Aquamarine's development speed would rocket instantly as well and indirectly receive tons of resources. Furthermore, with a Beyond Grade A as its neighbor, Planet Aquamarine would be massively safer, which would free Han Xiao of many worries.

With some thoughts flashing through Han Xiao's mind, he understood what Ames was thinking—the reason for her choosing Planet Aquamarine as the headquarters of the Floating Dragon was much more than it just being 'justifiable'. He sighed and said, "Looks like I'm going to owe you another favor."

"Good that you know." Ames smiled.

"Alright, I agree. I'll have the army subdivision at Planet Aquamarine work with you. Sylvia and the others will take care of the details..."

"Hmm, I'll let Jenny settle it..."

Speaking of Jenny, Han Xiao suddenly thought of something. "By the way, about this, have you told Jenny yet?"

"No."

The two of them stared at each other and stayed silent for a moment.

So, this is indeed a sudden idea... Han Xiao sighed. He really thought that Ames had seriously considered this, but as it turned out, this was exactly her style.

"Ahem, now that that's settle, I shall get going." Ames coughed with her fist covering her lips to hide her awkwardness before turning around and leaving.

Han Xiao watched as Ames and Aesop boarded the small spaceship and split off from the fleet, turning into a stream of light. He then ordered the fleet to continue advancing back to the army's headquarters.

The task of traveling across Star Fields was completed. Han Xiao opened the forums to see what the players' responses were.

When they just passed through the stargate, the more than seven hundred thousand players inside the fleet did not really react to it much, but instead, the Shattered Star Ring players had bigger responses. It was because the players from another Star Field had come to their territory, and they could not wait to meet them.

The first example of players crossing to another Star Field had extraordinary significance. The players from the various Star Fields recorded this moment in their Chronicle posts.

"Galaxy Calendar: Year 705, March 18th.

"Led by the Black Star Army, more than seven hundred thousand players left Constellation Corridor and arrived in the Shattered Star Ring. This was the first example of players successfully traveling to another Star Field in the entire Galaxy."

The recruitment of players in the Constellation Corridor this time went quite smoothly, and Han Xiao knew exactly why—there were not many factions that the players could choose in Version 3.0, and he knew what the players needed. Therefore, the Black Star Army was a top-notch faction in this stage and had excellent appeal.

As the players' level increased, the number of powerful factions they would be able to choose would increase, including the three universal civilizations and beyond Star Cluster civilizations. By then, the army would not be able to recruit players as easily. This was unavoidable; there would always be people who wanted to try out new factions for a new experience.

This was also one of the reasons Han Xiao kept expanding his army and increasing its competitiveness. From a certain perspective, it was a good thing to have chosen the rural Shattered Star Ring as his headquarters as there were fewer direct competitors there.

After traveling for more than ten days, the fleet finally returned to the army's headquarters.

Millions of Shattered Star Ring players were gathered in the army headquarters, looking forward to meeting the foreign Constellation Corridor players. The majority of them were there to rubberneck.

The seven hundred thousand Constellation Corridor players looked at the army headquarters satellite outside the porthole, their hearts filled with excitement.

After staying on the ships with anticipation for so many days, they had finally arrived.

Chapter 814: Players: I Don't Want to Socialize. Han Xiao: No, You Do.

The transport spaceships landed at the headquarters' docks one after another.

As the Constellation Corridor players stepped into the headquarters, the millions of army players quickly came. The harbor and the hall were all filled with players. Luckily, the army headquarters satellite was large enough to carry billions of members.

This was the first time that players from different Star Fields had met outside of professional competitions. Be it the Chinese, Russians, or the Australian players, they all sized each other up in this first meeting.

When comparing the two sides, the difference was obvious.

The equipment on the Constellation Corridor players varied broadly in terms of color and models. It looked quite messy.

On the millions of army players, the color of their equipment and weapons were mainly black and silver. Although their equipment models differed, they were not as messy as the Constellation Corridor players. Most of the army players used the few sets of widely recognized army combat armor with the best performance. They looked neat, like an elite military force. The small individual differences between them were not that obvious. Furthermore, their equipment all had the Black Star Army symbol.

After getting off the ship, some of the newcomers greeted and talked to the others, some curiously observed and looked around the headquarters, and some went to communicate with the army NPCs. Generally, they scattered around and familiarized themselves with the headquarters.

Vodka and Captain Old Henry led their guild officers and looked for the guild leaders of the large Chinese guilds.

While the Long Sky club was in their rented base in the Black Star Army headquarters, the leaders of Sky Territory and Ancient Dynasty, Jade Green Sky and Morning Snow Twilight Frost, went to meet the Russian guild officers.

"It's good to see you, my Chinese friends. I'm the vice-president of Power and Glory, Vodka."

Vodka and his friends introduced themselves.

"Good to see you," Jade Green Sky said with a smile. The translation function relayed the meaning of his words to Vodka and the others.

They chatted casually for a while before getting down to business.

"The people above told us to build a guild branch here. Some time ago, the guilds on your side and our side contacted each other. The people above said that your guilds would provide us with some help in the early stages..."

Morning Snow Twilight Frost smiled and said, "That's right. If I may ask, how many guild members did you bring here to build your guild branch?"

"I brought twelve guild officers, a hundred and fifty official members, and one thousand two hundred external members," Vodka said.

The representatives of the other guilds said their numbers, all around a thousand. Being an officer or an official member of the large professional guilds was a proper job; they received salaries for playing the game. As for the external players, some of them were casual volunteers, and some were similar to studios—they received bonuses from the clubs as well.

"For the thousands of you to start guild branches here, the road ahead is quite tough. You have to start from scratch. You will need to purchase all kinds of tools, items, and carriers, which all require money; it's the same for equipment repairs, enhancements, and renewals; building your bases is quite costly as well, and don't forget about the traveling fees to do missions. Furthermore, you need to search for channels that can provide stable streams of EXP, materials, and money. The earlier you turn losses into profit, the better, right?"

Vodka and the rest nodded continuously. To them, operating the guilds was a job; they were there on a mission. Their jobs depended on how well they operated the guild branch.

Morning Snow Twilight Frost secretly exchanged looks with Jade Green Sky, smiled, and said slowly, "Some time ago, we completed the Black Star Army's main storyline mission [Secret War]. Many of us obtained the army exclusive honorable title [Secret Warrior]. Anyone with this title can enjoy a ten percent discount on any purchases within the army. Of course, you guys don't have that treatment."

Only the army players who had taken part in the secret war had such privileges. This was a limited title. The players who joined later had no chance to obtain it.

These guilds who had just come from another Star Field had heard about this long ago through the forums. Of course, they were jealous.

"You mean..."

"Yes, we can provide a channel for you to enjoy that discount. We will purchase products from the army at ten percent off, and we will sell them to your two guilds at three percent off. Large guilds like us have more than enough funds and Contribution Points to fulfill your mass purchase needs... Of course, you can also look for normal players and ask them to help, but there's a risk of getting scammed."

Vodka did not respond. It was clear that Dynasty and Long Sky were planning to profit from the price difference. As the manager of this guild branch, he had to be calculative.

Compared to purchasing resources of these Chinese clubs, he was more willing to work with reliable normal Chinese players. He could borrow their title to purchase at ten percent off and give them some resources from time to time, which would be much cheaper than a mere three percent off.

However, Morning Snow Twilight Frost saw right through them and knew exactly what these Russian guild representatives were thinking. He smiled faintly and said, "If you purchase from us, we will provide help to you in other ways too.

"In what ways?"

"For example, quality mission resources or hidden NPC intel. If you accept some kind of high difficulty mission, we can provide manpower to help you. Also... we can ensure your safety."

"Safety?" Vodka's expression changed. "What do you mean?"

"The Shattered Star Ring is the territory that us Chinese clubs have been operating in since many versions ago. The dozens of large guilds and many more medium to smaller guilds have split most of the quality resources here. As outsiders who have suddenly arrived to build your guilds, I can't guarantee that no other guilds will have conflicts with you. And if it just so happens that you guys will have to fight guild wars with other local guilds, since you're just a guild branch and have very limited manpower, you will be at quite a massive disadvantage."

One of the goals those guilds that belonged to clubs had was to provide resources for their professional players, and the large guilds of the various nations were each other's biggest competitors. There was no way the Chinese clubs would watch other professional clubs peacefully operate their guild branches. Their higher-ups had already informed these guilds to think of some ways to restrain the development of those competitors.

No matter how rich the foreign clubs were, if there were always people disrupting their missions, robbing their resources, and chasing down and killing their members, they would not be able to grow and would always make losses.

What Morning Snow Twilight Frost said was a reminder to Vodka and the others, saying that if they did not pay some 'protection fees' to them, there were more than enough people there that could make trouble for them.

Of course, the Chinese clubs were not too excessive about it. After all, players from all around the world were watching the situation of these first batch of players who had traveled to another Star Field. As the hosts, they could not openly bully these newcomers who had absolutely no foundations there. Even though they were competitors, they had to care about how much attention this matter attracted. They did not want the other countries to have a horrible image of the Chinese professional circle, so they still gave a small discount and some help so that it would look like the foreign clubs did not make too great a loss on the surface.

The normal players, of course, would not be targeted. However, the clubs of the various nations were, first and foremost, commercial businesses. In order for their business to bloom, they had to rely on the glory of their professional players. While they had to make profits, they also had the hopes of the players on their shoulders. Professional players fought in competitions, and they, the official guilds, had to fight in the game as well. If the Chinese clubs went to another Star Field to start their guild branches, they would be treated very similarly, restricted in many aspects.

Vodka and the others exchanged looks before agreeing with resignation. Deep down, however, they did not yield so easily. They secretly decided to look for chances to work with normal players without letting the Chinese clubs know so that they would pay less protection fees.

Meanwhile, in the guild base of the Temple of God guild, the guild presidents of the other two clubs, Jupiter and Cowherd Star, were having a meeting with the Kangaroo Boxing guild branch president, Captain Old Henry, and the other Australian guild representatives. They were discussing the exact same thing as Long Sky and Dynasty...

The four largest clubs had already made agreements behind the curtains to do the same thing. Compared to their plans, these small protection fees were just minor earnings.

To the more than seven hundred thousand newcomers, the army headquarters was their new main city.

While they were familiarizing themselves with the environment, Han Xiao returned to the office of the Army Commander. The officers who had been managing the headquarters for the past two months were reporting to him.

Han Xiao leaned back in his chair and looked at the group of officers in front of him.

"How's the army been doing while I wasn't here?"

Sylvia took a step forward and reported, "We have digested the gains we made through the last expansions, as well as successfully linked with the business channels of the various allies in the Shattered Star Ring. The Black Star Army's current business range covers more than ten industries, forming a complete trading system, intelligence system, transportation system, and many others."

"The Logistics Department has built 126 factories in various locations, making rushed orders of more satellite bases," Reynold said with a deep voice. "According to the army's future blueprint, we will continue to build more divisions in all seven Star Clusters and expand our forces."

Herlous nodded and said, "Due to the increase in the number of members and the size of our forces, the army's fleet is expanding as well. The Logistics Department already has a lot of things on their hands that are yet to be completed, so I made orders with the financial groups we're working with, and there are new batches of battleships being built every day."

Han Xiao nodded. These were all things that he had told them to do before he left. "Anything else?"

"Er... our funds are running out," Sylvia said a little awkwardly.

Han Xiao's eyes widened. "We have so many businesses, including the resource planet mining rights from many civilizations. How are we lacking money?"

"The cost of expansion was too high. The current maintenance fee of the army is extremely costly, and the Logistics Department has been producing at full capacity the whole time, which is reducing our funds at quite a terrifying speed. Furthermore, it's the off-season for trading, so many of the financial groups working with us have seen decreased sales. Thus, the profit period of the mining of resource planets is extended, and our capital flow is a little tight..."

"Did you not go to the Crimson Dynasty and the Purple Crystal Civilization's men and ask them to send funds? Didn't I tell you that you can go to them whenever we're lacking funds if it's caused by normal operations?" Han Xiao asked.

"I did..." Sylvia replied with resignation. "They did not reject, but they said that they will only do so when you tell them personally. They only recognize you."

"Alright, I'll contact them later." Han Xiao's mouth twitched. These two only recognized him as their ally, which was unavoidable. Although his army was enormous, its true core was still him.

"One more thing. You told me to gather the teams needed to explore the Flickering World. I've already done so. They are split into many fleets and are now standing by in the various sub-bases around Colton, ready to depart anytime," Sylvia said.

"Good, Zoel will be hurrying me to get going very soon." Han Xiao gave Sylvia a very satisfied look.

The three of them then reported some of the details. Seeing that Han Xiao had no other orders, they relaxed and started casually chatting.

"Why haven't I seen Lagi? I've returned, and my vice-captain isn't here to see me. What's he been busy doing?" Han Xiao wondered.

"Hehe, he's been busy every day, either busy playing cards or busy sleeping!" Sylvia felt angry whenever Lagi's name was brought up. She then shot Herlous a glare and said, "You too. He drags you away to play cards every day—why don't you ever reject him‽"

"What do you know about fun between card-mates?" Herlous snorted.

"Don't mention playing cards in front of me," Han Xiao complained. "How has Lagi been teaching Tomar?"

Tomar was a protagonist character that he had brought back, and Han Xiao did not forget about him.

"I heard he's learning very fast."

Han Xiao nodded. He looked at Reynold and said with anticipation, "What about my godson? Has he shown any special talent in terms of machinery?"

"Er... no," Reynold told the truth. "But he's learning very fast, too. He's quite talented on the path of the machinery."

Sigh, I wonder if this will help in getting [Perfect Mechanical Sense]... Han Xiao waved his hand with resignation.

"I'll take him out in a few days. That'll be all."

The three of them nodded and left the room. Han Xiao took out his communicator and contacted the Purple Crystal Civilization and the Crimson Dynasty, successfully requesting funds.

Zoel also reminded him that the Crimson Dynasty was done preparing their exploration team and told Han Xiao to lead his people to the Flickering World's Dawn Star Cluster soon to rendezvous with the dynasty's army. Then, they would officially start to explore the Flickering World.

After settling the official matters, Han Xiao looked at how the new players were doing in the army's headquarters.

These Constellation Corridor players were still familiarizing themselves with the headquarters' structure and map. Han Xiao had noticed something—although these players had already traveled to another Star Field, they were still posting on their Constellation Corridor forum page out of habit.

Although the players of both sides communicated quite a lot on the forums, only a minority of players interacted with each other in the army's headquarters. Despite all of them being army members, there were obvious differences between the players of the two Star Fields. They were not completely avoiding each other, but they were basically playing on their own.

"This won't do..." Han Xiao shook his head.

He pondered before quickly writing two Faction Missions and issuing them through the faction interface to all the army players.

[Teach a Recruit] (Repeatable)

Mission Introduction: The recent expansion of the Black Star Army has brought back new warriors from another Star Field. The senior members of the army can choose to teach the new members, helping them become familiar with the tasks in the army quickly.

Mission Requirements: Team up with one or more new warriors (players) from another Star Field and complete any one army mission.

Reward: 100 – 300 Black Star Army Contribution Points.

Remarks: Only players who have been in the army for more than a year can accept this mission.

[Consult A Veteran] (Repeatable)

Mission Introduction: As a new member of the Black Star Army, the veterans are the best people to learn from. Go and consult them, let them teach you more about the army.

Mission Requirements: Team up with one or more senior warriors (players who have been in the army for more than a year) and complete any one army mission.

Reward: 100 – 300 Black Star Army Contribution Points.

Remarks: Only players who have been in the army for less than a year can accept this mission.

"Hehehe..." Looking at the two missions he had just distributed, Han Xiao giggled mischievously.

After existing for three versions, the army's Contribution Point had already become a key resource that was just as important as Enas. No amount was too much for anyone.

He did not want the players of the two Star Fields to form their own circles. Those club guilds were commercial competitors with each other, so there was nothing he could do, but there was definitely something he could do for those normal players. Since they were all there in his headquarters, they were all leeks in the same field. He needed those new and old members to interact with each other and play together.

The social aspect of a game was a key factor in the players' gaming experience!

Since players of both sides were so shy and did not interact with their foreign friends, Han Xiao decided to lure them to socialize.

This would be beneficial for the Constellation Corridor players to embrace the army's system. Not only would they be able to adapt to the new environment quicker, but the 'Constellation Corridor' tag on those players would also slowly disappear, and they would soon just think of themselves as 'army players'.

This way, the personal connection between the players would become another reason for them to stay in the army. He was using players to 'attract' players, indirectly enhancing the appeal and sense of belonging to the faction!

Han Xiao suddenly patted his forehead, and his expression became weird.

"Why does it feel similar to the oldest profession?"

Chapter 815: Socializing Mad Genius

As Han Xiao distributed the two new missions, notifications popped up on the interfaces of all the army players.

"Doing missions with new members gives bonus Faction Contribution Points? That sounds like a great deal."

"Any mission? Does running errands count?"

"For sure, even using the army Dungeon Crystals counts."

"These can be repeated? Awesome!"

"Must team up with players who have been in the faction for less than a year, so only the new players born on Planet Deirdre in Version 3.0?"

"The Constellation Corridor players count too, right? Didn't they just join the army?"

The two faction missions became a faction event and stirred up a wave among the players.

Han Xiao's missions were not compulsory. He used the reward to lure them instead. Most of the players would not miss such a rare opportunity to farm Contribution Points. It was just teaming up with new players; they had nothing to lose and a lot to gain.

Maybe some players could not be bothered, but most players were willing to grab this opportunity.

As long as most people were deliberately teaming up with new members and not just with their inner circle friends, they would have taken the first step to socializing with players from other Star Fields, and Han Xiao's goal would be achieved.

When playing together, they would build some kind of relationship in one way or another. At the very least, adding each other to their friend lists would be common.

The two missions were a set targeted at different groups. [Teach a Recruit]'s purpose was to make the older members willing to team up with the new members, and [Consult a Veteran]'s aim was to make the new members look for old members to help them.

The Constellation Corridor players were not the only ones considered as 'recruits'. The players from the Version 3.0 novice planet, Planet Deirdre, were also new members of the army. The Shattered Star Ring old members would, of course, be more willing to play with them, so [Consult a Veteran] ensured that those foreign players would look for the senior army members as well.

Compared to those senior members of the army, these new members needed the Contribution Points more and were more passionate about this mission.

Secretly guided by Han Xiao, the situation in the army headquarters changed very quickly. The areas where players gathered became boisterous, and groups of people asked to team up in the public channel.

"LF1M[1] new army member above level 100, no Pugilists. All old army members here. Let's do missions together to farm Contribution Points."

"Level 88 Cannon Master, newbie here, need an old member to team up with to farm Contribution Points!"

"Thirty-man team here, planning to enter the [Secret War—Protection Warfare] dungeon. LF4M high-level Constellation Corridor players above Grade C+. Tank and disables needed, no damage dealers! Again, no damage dealers! Come quick!"

The interactions between players immediately became frequent.

The foreign players entered different army player teams and quickly mixed in with the environment. As the players were waiting for the Flickering World main storyline, they were mainly farming dungeons, which indirectly increased the sales of Dungeon Crystals.

The players had no suspicion of these two missions—to the players, it was very normal for the army to encourage the old members to teach the new members since a group of new members had just arrived from another Star Field.

"Hey, Chinese pal, do you know when this event will end?"

"Who cares? Just farm it as much as possible."

"You guys don't seem surprised at all. In our Star Field, group activities like this are very rare."

"Haha, this happens very frequently in our army. I've already taken part in many large missions that had hundreds of thousands of participants. You'll get used to it soon. This is a specialty of the Shattered Star Ring."

As the normal players were teaming up, so were the club guilds. The four biggest Chinese guilds were overjoyed.

They had just made the price difference agreement with the foreign guilds, and this mission popped up right after. The Russian and Australian guild players were all recruits, so these guild representatives came back right after they had just left.

Even the faction was helping them!

After monitoring for a while, Han Xiao nodded and was rather satisfied with the impact he had made. This was a good start to make the players from different Star Fields mix together.

This would largely increase the efficiency of communication between the players from two sides and was beneficial for the faction.

He planned to keep these two missions active for some time.

They would have to explore the Flickering World very soon, which would have countless missions, so this mission would encourage the players from two sides to work together.

Closing the forums, Han Xiao left the office and returned to his bedroom.

His bedroom in the army had a very minimalist layout. The walls were metallic, and there was a window on the ceiling that looked right into the vast universe. A large black bed sat in the middle of the room, with a bookshelf, fridge, automatic cooker, waste bin, and other simple items beside the wall. The one plant pot in the corner of the wall grown by Han Xiao personally gave this cold and boring looking room a sense of liveliness.

Han Xiao took off his clothes and took a shower. He then took out a hand full of special grade nutrition pastes of different flavors and casually gulped them down. This thing recovered stamina extremely quickly, and it was not cheap.

Beyond Grade As basically did not need to sleep or eat at all, but he decided to retain his habit as a human. The increase in strength and change in the race would make beings look at the world in a different way. He did not need to rest, but he wanted to remind himself he was still human.

Due to the astonishing control that Beyond Grade As had over their bodies, there was no way for Han Xiao to fall asleep naturally. He could only control his brain to enter a rest state.

Since travelling to the Central Galaxy, this was the first time he had slept.

Han Xiao lay on the bed. Before sleeping, his consciousness entered the quantum network and told Phillip, "I'm sleeping. Call me up if anything. Goodnight."

"Goodnight, master, hum..." Phillip replied.

...

After sleeping for a night, Han Xiao's eyes opened exactly on time. He came out from under the blanket, washed up, took off his pajamas, and donned his black robe, once again recovering to the image of Black Star.

The first thing he did was open the forums. Due to the team-up missions, more and more new members of the army had become active on the Shattered Star Ring page and interacted with the Chinese players.

Han Xiao noticed a new pinned post—it was the new episode of Galaxy Times.

"They should mention the Star Field migration..."

Han Xiao opened it up.

After the familiar opening, the two hosts shared what interesting things were happening around the various Star Fields. They soon mentioned the first batch of players to travel to another Star Field.

"Not long ago, the renowned NPC faction of the Shattered Star Ring, the Black Star Army, provided the Constellation Corridor players a way to go to the Shattered Star Ring. Based on statistics, there are a total of 713,000 players who chose to leave with the Black Star Army, completing the first known event of any player traveling to another Star Field.

"In Version 2.0, the Black Star Army was the guiding faction to lead the Shattered Star Ring players to the galaxy. Now, they have once again guided the players of another Star Field to cross Star Fields. Maybe this is a signal—in the next version, the players might be able to cross Star Fields on a large scale and go to different areas freely!

"So far, this is how the activity areas of the players have developed: Version 1.0, novice planet; Version 2.0, entering the galaxy; Version 3.0, exploring the Star Cluster... The activity range of the players has been expanding every version. Initially, we thought that the players would be exploring their birth Star Field mainly in the next version, but the Black Star Army has given us new ideas. Due to the theme of Galaxy, the players of the various Star Fields will interact sooner or later. Therefore, according to this trend, we can speculate that the next version will be the stage where players can freely cross Star Fields."

Han Xiao shook his head and smiled as he finished watching the show. This speculation was very logical, but Galaxy Times was only half right.

In the next version, the players would indeed be able to cross to another Star Fields on a large scale. However, unlike what Galaxy Times had speculated, the players would gather in the Flickering World instead of freely going to different areas.

Galaxy Times misguided the players, which was unavoidable. Other than Han Xiao, no players knew that the Flickering World would be the main stage of the next version.

...

"The players who are following me to the Flickering World still don't know how much of an advantage they've gained."

After looking at the forums for half an hour, only then did Han Xiao start to do other things. He patrolled around the army headquarters before heading to the Logistics Department.

When he entered Reynold's office, he saw Nero, who was buried in the mountain of books.

"Godfather!" As soon as Nero looked up, his deep and dark eye bags were clearly visible. Realizing that it was Han Xiao, joy bloomed on his exhausted face. He immediately threw away the theory book in his hands and dashed into Han Xiao's arms.

Looking at the terrifying amount of homework Reynold had given, Han Xiao's mouth twitched.

This is almost on the level of child abuse...

Scolding Reynold in his mind, Han Xiao patted Nero's head and said, "Come, I'm taking you out."

"Really‽" Nero was so overjoyed and surprised that his tears almost gushed out.

When he left Planet Aquamarine, Nero thought that he had followed his godfather out to play. To his absolute shock, there was an infinite amount of homework that he could never finish waiting for him!

Given Reynold's personality, the thing he was best at was forceful education. In the past two months, Nero felt like he was in living hell, and seeing Han Xiao was like seeing an angel who had come to save him—he could finally escape this endless misery!

"I promised you, right?" Han Xiao smiled. Actually, the main goal was not to take Nero sightseeing but to go to the Tyla Civilization, which Harrofal had been part of, and search for the set of wormhole travel data back from when EsGod's doppelganger entered it.

Other than Nero, Han Xiao only took Hila, Aurora, and Feidin along. They took the extremely quick Blacklight Stealth, so it would not take long for a return trip and would not delay the Flickering World mission.

As Harrofal had been killed by EsGod's subordinate long ago, the chances of finding the wormhole data were very slim, which was why Han Xiao brought his two lucky mascots—Feidin and Nero—to offset his luck.

After all, those who believed in luck were... the unluckiest ones.

...

The Blacklight Stealth flew through the stargate and did not make any stops along the way. Not many days later, Han Xiao and the others arrived at one of the Tyla Civilization's governance planets to visit the high-level mechanic school that Harrofal had been part of.

With Han Xiao's identity, as long as his intentions were not hostile, he was welcomed as a guest by all the civilizations in the Shattered Star Ring... except the Klent Kingdom, who had been cursing him every day, and the Star Pupil Holy Race, who had been secretly sticking needles into his voodoo doll.

This mechanic school was government-based and raised many Mechanic talents for the Tyla Civilization. The school was vast and magnificent.

The principal was already waiting at the entrance of the school with others. Han Xiao was met with a warm welcome the moment he arrived.

"Your Excellency Black Star, it's our honor to have you." The principal smiled brightly.

"You're too kind." Han Xiao nodded.

"Please, follow me." Mechanical hoverboards arrived as the principal raised his arm. These were all public carriers inside the school.

Han Xiao stepped onto the hoverboard and followed the principal to head to the guest room, chatting and laughing along the way.

They passed through the school, and to Han Xiao's surprise, they attracted a lot of attention.

It seemed like some students had recognized him and spread the message out, leading to groups of students following behind them on mechanical hoverboards and watching them from afar.

Han Xiao looked behind him and said with surprise, "These are all students of this school, right? Why are they following behind us?"

The principal said with resignation, "Your Excellency Black Star, as you know, this is a mechanic school. All the students here are Mechanic class Supers..."

"And?"

"Ahem, you don't seem to know your significance in the hearts of the Mechanic class students..."

Han Xiao suddenly understood. He then looked back and realized that the students behind him were all filled with excitement, surprise, and admiration as they looked at him. It was almost worshipping.

He was the one and only Beyond Grade A Mechanic in the Shattered Star Ring, so his position was even more special in the eyes of the Mechanic Supers. He was basically the top authority of the Mechanics in the Shattered Star Ring. His visit to this school caused a sensation among the students.

The principal smiled and said, "Your Excellency Black Star, why don't you host a lecture here and teach them a tiny bit of your infinite wisdom on the path of the machinery. What do you think?"

"Hmm..." Han Xiao thought about it and did not reject it. He waved his hand and said, "I'll see to it, if this trip goes smoothly."

"Is there a goal for this visit?" the principal asked. Han Xiao only requested to visit and had yet to tell him his goal.

"Harrofal was my friend. I'm here to look for a set of data he had left behind."

The principal was stunned for a moment. "Oh, him... alas, some time ago, the school was attacked, and he was killed by a group of kidnappers. He was an amazing researcher, and regretfully, we lost a crucial talent."

"Those killers were EsGod's subordinates. I've already avenged him."

After a moment's silence, the principal suddenly asked, "Did those EsGod subordinates you spoke of kidnap him because of that set of data you mentioned?"

This was not difficult to deduce, so Han Xiao was not surprised. He glanced at him and nodded.

"Yes. When Harrofal was doing wormhole research, I visited him many times. One time, we were attacked by the DarkStar leader, and I was forced to fight an EsGod doppelganger. However, back then, I was no match for it. Only thanks to Harrofal's help was I able to lure the EsGod doppelganger into a wormhole and banish it. What I want is that set of location data for that wormhole."

The wormhole cluster of the Taralam Star Cluster was the center of the Shattered Star Ring. The teleportation location of every unstable wormhole was random, unlike stargates, which had a fixed destination. Also, the chance of those random destinations repeating was infinitely close to zero, so finding that same wormhole would do nothing. Only the recorded coordinates data would be useful.

The principal shook his head. "When Harrofal was kidnapped, all the wormhole detectors in his lab were taken away, every single one of them."

"He should've recorded the data into the internal database of your school. I hope that you can give me the authority to search for it."

"Er... the database consisting of the research data is highly confidential. I can only allow outsiders to browse it when it's approved by the upper echelons of the civilization... I'm not even sure if Harrofal backed up that data. Also, there are too many sets of wormhole data he recorded. If you don't recall the date and time, we won't know which set of data you're looking for..."

"Then please notify the upper echelons of the Tyla Civilization for me," Han Xiao said with a deep voice.

Internal databases that had something to do with the government definitely had extremely strong virtual defense measures. As there were still hopes of obtaining the data through a just method, he did not want to use Virtual Intrusion and make a Star Cluster his enemy.

As a Beyond Grade A, he could not always do things sneakily. Furthermore, he still had no idea what was so important about the set of wormhole data that EsGod mentioned.

[1] LFxM is a common term in MMOs meaning Looking For x More player(s). Back

Chapter 816: Mechanic Class Top Mentor

The group of them entered the school's central building. The Mechanic students were not allowed to enter, so they loitered around outside for a while and gradually left one after another.

Han Xiao and the others came to the principal's guest room. A bionic mechanical assistant secretary brought them some drinks. The principal invited them to sit. "Your Excellency Black Star, please wait for a moment. I'll relay your request to my superiors."

Han Xiao nodded and watched the principal leave. The group waited in the room.

Nero leaned on the window and curiously looked at the scenery in the school. Small mechanical islands hovered in the sky, metal buildings in yellow and blue stood tall on the ground, students crossed between the buildings riding mechanical skateboards, and the red, yellow, and green forests waved with the wind. The alloy buildings coexisted with the artificial greenery, forming a harmonious color tone. It had a special sense of beauty.

"This place looks so different from Planet Aquamarine. It's so beautiful." Everything was fresh to Nero.

"This is nothing. The dynasty school at the Crimson Dynasty's mother planet is much more magnificent than this." Han Xiao chuckled. He had brought Nero out not just to rub some luck from him but also to broaden Nero's knowledge.

"Really? I want to see that." Nero was really interested.

"I'll take you there if there's a chance." Han Xiao beckoned Nero over, pointed at the drink on the table, and said, "Come, try it. It's good."

On the table were a few cups of hot white liquid flickering with a tint of light gold, giving off a thick milky fragrance. This was some kind of milk product provided by the Tyla Civilization.

Nero picked up the cup and took a sip. His eyes widened, and he gulped down a mouthful. He exhaled in satisfaction, licked away the white stain on his mouth, and looked like he wanted more.

"How was it?"

"Godfather, what is this? I've never tasted such delicious milk before."

Han Xiao smiled and explained, "When the Tyla Civilization was exploring a certain colonial planet, they discovered a galactic being that was on the verge of extinction. They were called the Herepoli Beasts, commonly known as the Giant Nebula Beasts. They are extremely large and can travel in the universe with their body. Some even call them the Mount of Giant Gods. However, the reproduction speed of the Giant Nebula Beasts is very long; they only mate every hundred years or so. After their cubs are born, they enter a three-month lactation period. The Giant Nebula Beasts only produce milk in those three short months. Their milk is rare, expensive, nourishing, and very unique. That's what you drank."

"I see." Nero rubbed his stomach. "No wonder my body feels so warm after drinking it."

"Do you want more? Drink mine too." Han Xiao smiled.

Nero licked his lips and was very tempted. After some tough internal conflict, he shook his head and said, "This is so valuable and rare; I can't drink it all. Godfather, you drink it too."

The others all laughed.

"I'm fine." Han Xiao shook his hand. Luxurious things that were extremely valuable to normal galactic residents were nothing much in his eyes. He could have plenty if he wanted.

However, he did not have much interest in luxurious consumables. He preferred to buy more special grade nutrition pastes with that money, which were much more convenient to consume and recovered his stamina very quickly, much higher quality-price ratio.

After chatting for a while, the principal had yet to return. Han Xiao turned around and looked at the mechanical assistant secretary that stood still beside the wall.

"How may I be of service to you?" The mechanical assistant secretary sensed his sights and responded immediately.

Han Xiao shook his hand and observed the bionic skin of this mechanical assistant secretary.

This principal looked respectable and reputable, but the bionic appearance given to this mechanical secretary was extremely seductive and sexy. It might really have the full set of functions of a 'secretary'...

After waiting a while longer, the principal finally returned.

"Sorry to have kept you waiting, Your Excellency Black Star. The people above have agreed with your request and allowed me to use my authority to help you to find that data."

"Okay, thank the upper echelons of the Tyla Civilization for me." Han Xiao was relieved. Things were much easier now that it was settled with his face.

He was reminded of how even Star System civilizations did not give him face at all in the past, and he had to find someone to help him. Now that he was a Beyond Grade A, even the Star Cluster civilizations were willing to give him face.

The principal pressed a few times on the office desk. The color of it suddenly changed as it became the control screen of the internal database. He looked up and asked, "Your Excellency Black Star, do you remember the time and location of the data?"

Han Xiao nodded and told him. The principle then inputted the corresponding parameters and ran the search engine to look for related data.

Although they agreed to help, they were not going to let a Beyond Grade A operate their internal database, so the principal was assisting him.

Countless items flashed past the screen. After scrolling for a while, only one item was left that perfectly matched the parameters.

The principal exhaled deeply. "Found it. Looks like Harrofal uploaded the data; the time and location are both right. See if this is the data you wanted."

Han Xiao walked over and browsed through it carefully. Although he did not professionally study wormholes like Harrofal, he had related professional knowledge of it and could understand the coordinates. However, this set of coordinates was outside the star map of the known universe and had a very complicated set of parameters. Without a star map, nothing could be discerned from just the data. He would only know where it led after studying it.

"EsGod was so concerned with this set of data. Which corner of the universe did his doppelganger get thrown to?" Han Xiao wondered.

Confirming that this set of data was from when Harrofal banished the EsGod doppelganger, Han Xiao blinked and took hundreds of photos instantly, which were transmitted to Phillip's database. He then nodded at the principal.

"Looks like I'm in luck. I've already made a back up. Thank you for this."

The principal shut down the screen, and the desk returned to normal. He then smiled and said, "I'm glad you've found what you came for. I have one thing I hope to ask from you."

Han Xiao was not surprised at all—the Tyla Civilization would not help him for free if they did not want to obtain something from him in exchange.

"If it's within my capabilities, I will help."

"Haha, you're mistaken. All we want to do is for you to become an honorary professor of the Tyla Official Mechanic School."

That's it? Han Xiao was a little surprised. After some thinking, he then understood their intention.

As the one and only Beyond Grade A Mechanic in the Shattered Star Ring, if he became a professor at the Tyla Civilization's official mechanic school, the name of this school would be much more famous and would attract tons more students. Many Mechanic students would apply to study in this school, which would give the Tyla Civilization more talents. Furthermore, as a professor of the Tyla Civilization's official school, it somewhat meant he was on their side. The Tyla Civilization would benefit a lot from this.

Since they had just helped him, Han Xiao was not going to reject such a small request. He nodded and said, "Sure."

The principal was delighted. "Then I shall have my people settle it immediately. By the way, since you're an honorary professor of the school, I hope you can host a lecture here. Either tomorrow or the day after is fine. It won't take too much time. If you don't mind, I'll get my men to announce it within the school."

"Alright, I shall stay here and trouble you for a few more days."

Thinking about it, Han Xiao suddenly said, "By the way, since I'm now a professor of this school, why don't you give me a copy of the basic and advanced lessons of your school?"

The lessons of official schools like this were all very carefully authored. The fundamental textbooks would be quite useful for factions, so he could take them back and train the Mechanic Supers of the army in a systematic way.

Some high-grade Supers might not be good at teaching despite their strength... for example, Rey 'Forceful Education' Nold...

Since Han Xiao was now an honorary professor of this school, he might as well gain something from it.

The next day, the Tyla Civilization immediately announced in a very high-profile way that they had successfully hired Black Star to be the honorary professor of their official mechanic school. They contacted a bunch of galactic media outlets to spread this news.

Currently, many of the civilizations in the Shattered Star Ring were the Black Star Army's business allies, but being an honorary professor of a civilization's official school signified an even closer relationship. The first ones to receive this news were the various Star Cluster civilizations of the Shattered Star Ring; they were all shocked and felt it was so sudden. Why did Black Star suddenly get mixed with the Tyla Civilization?

The Purple Crystal was even more shocked. Never mind you sneaking into the Crimson Dynasty's bed, we can't mess with them, so we'll live with it, but how can you flirt with that shameless neighbor? You *sshole, did you forget I'm your origina... ahem, your earliest ally who has invested the most in you‽

Han Xiao's communicator was almost exploding from Ralph's calls, and he spent some time to finally calm him down.

This piece of news also shocked the many students in the Tyla Official Mechanic School.

Black Star is now our school's honorary professor, and he's going to do a lecture‽

How did that perverted principal convince Black Star‽

The students were exhilarated and honored.

Originally, the lecture was supposed to be carried out inside the building, but there were too many students attending, so the school decided to have Han Xiao give the lecture at the open central square.

As the day of the lecture arrived, the area was completely filled with people. There were absolutely no empty seats, and countless students even hovered in the air, riding mechanical skateboards. More than ninety percent of the people in the entire school came.

Most of the teachers and professors went to listen too—in front of a Beyond Grade A Mechanic, they were all students.

Han Xiao stood in the middle of the freshly built tall stage in the middle of the central square, looked around, and smiled bitterly in his mind.

He had thought that he would just be teaching a small group of students; never had he expected to create such a scene. Not only were there so many people here, but there were also even many recording devices around that videoed his every move. It was almost like a concert or even preaching.

Of course, he had no problem doing this. He did not even mind fist fighting with Heber in front of trillions of galactic residents back then, so this would not affect him at all. With his Beyond Grade A standard, he just had to casually share some experiences, and these students would be satisfied.

However, Han Xiao was not really used to this. Currently, the person who used lectures as core competitiveness was that old man Austin.

"Ahem, let's get started..." Han Xiao cleared his throat and started speaking.

At the Bloodshed Land's headquarters, Heber was confused. "Black Star went to give an open lecture to a Star Cluster civilization's official school? He's got to go to the Flickering World soon, yet he still has the time to do that‽"

Inside the Palace of Hidden Spells, Austin murmured with a strange expression, "This guy, is he trying to imitate me and form a Hidden Machinery Abbey or something?"

"Tsk, I hate Mechanics." On the Star Pupil Holy Race Mother Planet, Psyker shut down the screen without hesitation. He did not want to see Han Xiao at all. Every time he saw the Evolution Cube on his neck, his heart would ache... every single time.

In the Crimson Dynasty Diplomatic Building, Zoel shook his head and laughed. "Yo, this guy is doing it again?"

From the way he looked at it, Han Xiao was not satisfied with his current position and went to form alliances with more Star Cluster civilizations.

He was happy to see this as long as it did not affect the main business. The more influence the dynasty's ally had in a Star Field, the better it was for them.

As for the players who were at the Black Star Army headquarters, some also discovered the broadcast on the galactic channels. Word quickly spread among the players, and more and more players turned on their communicators to watch Han Xiao's lecture curiously.

"Huh, I thought the Army Commander has been in the headquarters. Turns out he went to another civilization."

"What's he talking about? Why does it sound like complete gibberish?"

When the many players were watching curiously, the Mechanic players among them were suddenly startled—a notification popped up on their interfaces.

You are listening to Black Star (Lv ?) share his knowledge of the Mechanic class. Due to the wide level difference, judging INT and LUK... Judgment complete. You are not sure if you understood. 1 random Mechanic class ability has received 50,000 EXP.

You are listening to Black Star (Lv ?) share his knowledge of the Mechanic class. Due to the wide level difference, judging INT and LUK... Judgment complete. You kind of understood. 2 random Mechanic class abilities have received 120,000 EXP.

You are listening to Black Star (Lv ?) share his knowledge of the Mechanic class. Due to the wide level difference, judging INT and LUK... Judgment complete. With a flash of insight, you suddenly figured it out. 4 random Mechanic class abilities have received 350,000 EXP.

All the Mechanic class players who were watching the broadcast were shocked.

"This is... imparting ability experiences‽"

The Mechanic class players were overjoyed.

This was the notification that would pop up when NPCs shared abilities or their experiences with the players, but events that gave random ability EXP were very rare. The Mechanic class players did not expect this at all; they had only watched the broadcast out of curiosity and happened to trigger this amazing event.

Very soon, this piece of news spread on the forums like a typhoon. All the Mechanic class players came to know about it and all went to watch the broadcast with excitement.

"Holy, my Mechanic class ability leveled up!"

"Is this a random event?"

"This is so much quicker than doing missions... damn, my [Intermediate Machinery Affinity] is at Lv.9, one level from maximum!"

"The Army Commander is awesome, as always!"

Leveling up abilities was always a bottomless pit of EXP, so the Mechanic class players were euphoric.

The players of the other four classes could only watch the Mechanic class players with jealousy.

It had been a very long time since Han Xiao had personally taught the players any abilities. As his interaction with the players decreased, many players had gradually started to forget the things he did in the past. This accident coincidentally made countless players recall that he was once a mentor.

Because of this, he became the recognized Top Mechanic Class Mentor!

Chapter 817: Pioneering

"Your Excellency Black Star, you're welcome to come and visit the school any time."

At the harbor, the principal brought his people along and sent Han Xiao and the others off. The lecture in the morning was very effective. The students were not the only ones who learned from it—he did too. So, his closeness and gratitude toward Han Xiao now were very sincere.

"Hmm, keep in touch." Han Xiao nodded before leading the rest onto the Blacklight Stealth. It took off, turned into a stream of light, and disappeared in the dark, vast cosmic space.

Having obtained the data and completed the promised lecture, the goal of this trip was achieved. He did not stay any longer and left the Tyla Civilization.

As for the impact of this, he did not care about it much. The Tyla Civilization was considered a neutral and powerful civilization in the Shattered Star Ring. Other forces rarely messed with them, and they did not mess with others deliberately. The afterheat of the Black Star Army's expansion had yet to vanish, so this bit of news would not cause too big a storm. At most, it might trigger some responses from the Star Cluster civilizations of the same grade.

Instead, the excited Mechanic players on the forums surprised him. Only through the forums did he know that his open lecture triggered a random ability EXP reward event.

There were many ways the players could obtain EXP, and this was one of them, but a very rare one. Other than their luck, it also depended on the knowledge difference between the players and what the NPCs were teaching. Pugilists and Mages were no strangers to this. Pugilists could secretly listen and learn abilities from some dojos. It was risky and did not guarantee success. The players mainly did this to avoid spending Contribution Points. It was the same for the Mages.

"What a surprise, this coincidentally strengthened my Mechanic class mentor image." Han Xiao shook his head.

His consciousness entered the quantum network and poked at Phillip.

"How's the study of that set of data?"

"It's too complicated, hum... I can't estimate the time needed to decipher it."

The location data of the wormhole had been given to Phillip to analyze. It required a huge amount of experiments and tests, and even Han Xiao did not know how long it would take before there were any results.

However, Han Xiao was not in a hurry. Since the Tyla Civilization now knew that EsGod and he had their eyes on this set of data, they would definitely feel that this data had secrets. Therefore, they would have professional scientists secretly study this data. The efficiency of an entire Star Cluster civilization would definitely not be slower than him or EsGod, and this was one of the reasons he had befriended the Tyla Civilization. If the Tyla Civilization discovered any clues, he would have a chance to learn them as well, which would be quite nice.

He also planned to send the data to the dynasty when he had time and borrow the dynasty's technology to decipher its secret.

...

After a smooth flight, the Blacklight Stealth returned to the army headquarters.

They rested for a few days, and the gathering order of the dynasty was officially announced. The dynasty had notified the Black Star Army, the Bloodshed Land, and Klent, the various Shattered Star Ring allies, to immediately head to the Flickering World through the dynasty stargate at the border of the Star Field.

After preparing for so long, the dynasty was finally about to start its first stage of exploration of the Flickering World!

Han Xiao immediately announced this as well.

When the departure date arrived, Phillip's broadcast announcement echoed in the entire army headquarters.

"All army members participating in the developments of the Flickering World, please board the ships immediately. We will be leaving in thirty minutes! I repeat, all..."

The players moved with anticipation and entered the harbor, boarding the transport ships one after another.

After the secret war ended, the Flickering World had become the next main storyline in the eyes of the players.

Exploring a new Star Field... this was the largest main storyline they had ever seen!

The millions of players were exhilarated!

Furthermore, with the example of the limited title [Secret Warrior], most of the army players accepted the Flickering World's main storyline mission. The players were excited just thinking about it.

Among which, the Constellation Corridor players were even more excited. The Shattered Star Ring players at least had similar experiences before, but the Constellation Corridor players had rarely had any large group missions like this, if any.

In the past, they had only heard about the benefits of being in the Black Star Army. Now, they had personally experienced it. The new recruits had an even higher rating for the army in their hearts.

The people at the army headquarters gathered and boarded the spaceships very quickly. With Han Xiao's order, the fleet departed.

Sylvia had already prepared all the fleets a few months ago. While the main fleet departed from the army headquarters, the teams in standby at the various sub-bases in the Colton Star Cluster departed as well. According to the plan, these subdivisions would rendezvous with Han Xiao one after another along the way.

The number of fleets and people the army had dispatched this time was enormous. Almost all the members who could move freely went along. It was the largest-scale operation in the history of the army.

No amount of manpower would ever be enough in exploring an entire new Star Field, so this exploration team would be building strongholds in the Flickering World and not return for a very long time, including Han Xiao.

The Black Star Army had already stabilized itself in the Shattered Star Ring, and its business was consistent. Furthermore, with the support of its two allies, the dynasty and Purple Crystal, as well as the protection of being a member of the Shattered Star Ring Civilization Conference, there was basically nothing to worry about.

The Flickering World would be the central stage of the next version. Developing the Flickering World was a crucial part of the next stage of development for the army.

The dynasty allies in the Shattered Star Ring were the ones to start the exploration first. Han Xiao had gone through a lot of planning to obtain such an advantage, so he could not possibly miss it. In order to deal with the countless organizations that would be fighting for territory in the future, he had to gain bigger advantages and build firm foundations in the early stages.

...

Somewhere in the Shattered Star Ring drifted Floating Dragon Island.

"I see, so Black Star has departed..."

Han Xiao's message appeared on the communicator. Ames looked away from the communicator and glanced at the floating dragon officers at the two sides of the throne.

"Let's go, toward Planet Aquamarine."

...

In the Central Galaxy, on the Federation of Light's mother planet, the president of the Federation of Light, Bader Ohoside, put down the deck of intelligence in his hands, looked at the Elders in the room, slowly said, "The Crimson Dynasty is finally going to officially start to explore the Flickering World... The dynasty will be focusing on this in the future. The exploration of the Flickering World is estimated to take decades or even an entire century."

The Chief Elder tapped the ground with his crutch and said with a hoarse voice, "It was our detectors that discovered the Flickering World. Back then, we transferred the ownership of the Flickering World to the Crimson Dynasty for a lot of profits. It will take a very long time for them to make a net profit from developing a new Star Field."

Back when they compromised with the Crimson Dynasty, it was not just to exchange for profits and calm the Crimson Tide. They also had more secret plans.

"Hmm..." Bader said indifferently. "In order to develop a new Star Field, the dynasty will definitely put in a lot of manpower and resources. The Flickering World will become a pond of quicksand that keeps dragging the dynasty's men down in the decades to come. The dynasty will have a very difficult time fighting for anything else during that time. This is highly beneficial to us."

The Chief Elder caressed the crystal at the top of his crutch and said, "When the dynasty purchased the ownership of the Flickering World from us, we made an agreement that only the Crimson Dynasty is allowed to build stargates at the early stages of the exploration. Any unauthorized forces in the Flickering World will be seen as enemies of the dynasty... However, the agreement is just words."

"Without us having to do anything, those ambitious beyond Star Cluster civilizations are smart enough to know the Arcane Church's and our stand on this," Bader said. "They know very well that this is a perfect chance for them. Almost none of them will be willing to give up on the resources of a new Star Field. Although these chess pieces only obey us on the surface usually, as soon as they see something with low risk and high reward, they will act according to our goals without needing us to do anything."

After a pause, Bader continued. "With so much attention on them, the dynasty doesn't have the ability to have the new Star Field to itself. Due to multiple factors, the dynasty will open the Flickering World to the entire universe around the time they complete creating a full star map of it. This way, they will be able to obtain an infinite amount of foreign labor and resources, and most of the dynasty's military and manpower will be able to retreat."

The Chief Elder nodded. "The dynasty has the ownership of the Star Field, but the larger the profit, the more pressure they will have to endure. Let them endure it. Something can only be said to be lost when it was once possessed. We can obtain larger profits by taking a step back here."

Bader crossed his arms and narrowed his eyes. "Since the dynasty is willing, let's give them more pressure."

...

On the Crimson Dynasty Mother Planet, the Dynasty Ruler, Urranrell, had just finished reading the intelligence of the Black Star Army and the Bloodshed Land departing. She put down the deck of data in her hands and looked up. Everyone there was a top-level official of the dynasty.

"Your Excellency Ruler, the Shattered Star Ring allies are the ones to carry out the earliest explorations. We will continue to put in more dynasty troops and allies in the future. The Federation of Light compromised on paper, but they will definitely violate the agreement secretly. The Federation of Light, the Arcane Church, and those beyond Star Cluster civilizations will undoubtedly move discreetly."

"I know," Urranrell said calmly. "Ever since the universe entered the Galaxy Calendar era, the Federation of Light lost their sharpness and are no longer willing to endure the pressure, so they don't deserve the largest profits. I never expected them to obey the agreement anyway. In the coming decades, things might be tough for us, but history will eventually prove that those who have given up on the future will be abandoned by the future."

Everyone nodded in silence.

"Those who cause trouble secretly will not expose their identity. Using this chance, we shall strike fear into those beyond Star Cluster civilizations who are getting more and more lawless."

Urranrell's eyes became focused as she spoke with a powerful and firm voice.

"Let's remind them of the dynasty's way of doing things!"

...

On the Fallen Ark, Harrison woke EsGod up from his sleep.

"The Arcane Church has responded."

EsGod woke up, breathed, and said slowly, "What did they say?"

"They say that they've never heard about this."

"That means they agreed." EsGod narrowed his eyes. "Tell the fleet to turn around and go to the desolate universe belt near the Arcane Church. Let's see where the temporary stargate they've prepared for me is."

...

At the edge of the Shattered Star Ring, inside the endless darkness, a gigantic stargate stood in the cosmic space. The enormous Black Star Army was approaching slowly.

This was the Crimson Dynasty's exclusive stargate connecting to the Flickering World, which was currently the only way to go to the Flickering World. A lot of dynasty's battleships were stationed there to keep anyone from sneaking through.

After reporting their identity, the Black Star Army fleet entered the stargate one batch after another, disappearing into the blue space vortex.

"We're going to do pioneering!"

"Brothers, I'm a little excited!"

The players on the transport ships were filled with anticipation.

As the main ship was about to enter the stargate, on the bridge, Hila and the Black Star Guards all turned around subconsciously to look at the bright stars behind them.

Han Xiao glanced behind him as well.

The next time I'll be back here will be very far in the future...

Looks like I'm going to have to spend the ten-month EXP penalty period in the Flickering World.

When I am back in the known universe by then, my level should be far higher than the 240 I am at now.

And the Evolution Cube might not be the only Universal Treasure in my hands...

Turning his head back, Han Xiao looked at the blue stargate vortex ahead. The other side of this stargate was a wide world filled with opportunities.

Boom!

The next moment, the main ship entered the stargate and trembled.

In an instant, there was only a bright blue light in their sights.

Chapter 818: Black-sheep-wall!

The main ship crossed the stargate and arrived at the Flickering World immediately from the Shattered Star Ring.

There were dynasty's fleets stationed on this side of the stargate too.

Han Xiao looked outside the window at the masses of star lights distributed around.

Unlike that prosperous Star Field in his memories, the Flickering World was still very primal and desolate. It did not have any traces of being developed before. The quantum network was silent; the only quantum network signal that he could connect to was the dynasty's military base station channel. This meant that this new Star Field was not open to the public.

"Beep beep..."

As soon as the main ship crossed the stargate, it received a communication request from the dynasty's military.

After the communication request was accepted, a 3D projection appeared. It was an old dynasty officer and a familiar face.

Hila glanced at the dense number of badges on this person. She looked at the military ranking badge on the sleeve of his army uniform and concluded that this person was a dynasty admiral, a well-established upper echelon of the military.

This person's eyes were locked onto Han Xiao. He slightly raised his head and smiled gently.

"I'm Tarrokov, the commander in chief of the development team of the Flickering World. Your Excellency Black Star, welcome to the Dawn Star Cluster."

"Commander." Han Xiao nodded.

Tarrokov was someone he was familiar with. In his previous life, when the players were active in the Flickering World, Tarrokov was also the commander in chief of the dynasty's troops stationed in the Flickering World. Back then, many of the missions were distributed in the form of military documents, and they were all signed by Tarrokov. He was in charge of the dynasty's troops in the Flickering World; all the dynasty missions came from him, so of course, the players were familiar with him.

Now that he had come to explore the Flickering World, Tarrokov would be considered as his semi-boss. Tarrokov would be contacting the dynasty's many allies on behalf of the dynasty, relaying the dynasty's orders to them. Han Xiao knew that he would be seeing this guy a lot for quite a long time.

Luckily, Tarrokov was a very senior military boss, and he was very gentle and steady, easy to get along with. This was also the reason the dynasty had sent him to take care of the matters in the Flickering World.

"Bloodshed Land and Klent arrived at the Flickering World two days ago. Come with your fleet as quickly as possible. When you're here, we will discuss the field exploration plans."

"Okay."

Han Xiao nodded, and Tarrokov hung up the communication.

Han Xiao opened the 3D star map. The current map of the Flickering World appeared before everyone's eyes. Only the Dawn Star Cluster was marked as green and completely explored, which had a rather complete star map. The other ninety percent or so of the area was all gray and had no details.

The dynasty had built many strongholds in the Dawn Star Cluster, among which the main stronghold was on a planet at the border of the Dawn Star Cluster that connected to the unexplored area. The planet was named Planet Lighthouse, signifying its place as the lighthouse that guided the explorers' return.

The gathering location marked by Tarrokov was there.

"It will still take some time till all the fleets cross the stargate." Aurora pressed here and pulled there on the operation table, bringing up the gathering countdown that was calculated by the artificial intelligence.

Officers with important jobs such as Sylvia, Herlous, Reynold, and Lagi had all remained in the Shattered Star Ring to maintain the army headquarters' operations. Han Xiao had only brought some of the army's officers along this time, such as the Black Star Guards. Most of them did not have any jobs to do usually, and they were now assigned to different posts to take care of different matters in the exploration team.

The tons of non-combat knowledge that Aurora had learned could now be of use. She became Han Xiao's administrative officer and was responsible for the miscellaneous matters.

"Phillip, plan the route," Han Xiao said.

"Roger that, hum..."

An illuminated line immediately appeared on the star map, marking the quickest route to Planet Lighthouse.

The dynasty knew the importance of transportation and had built many military stargates in the Dawn Star Cluster to allow frequent jumps, tremendously reducing the traveling time within the Star Cluster. These were all marked on the star map. However, this was only the case during the closed exploration period. Han Xiao knew that once the Flickering World was open to the public, the dynasty would recover some of those military channels.

Han Xiao thought for a moment and said, "Split a few engineering fleets out from the main fleet and build the quantum communication stations for our army in the Dawn Star Cluster. Let the dynasty know about it. Tell them that this is for us to interact with the people in the Shattered Star Ring headquarters more easily."

It was the countless base stations and network nodes everywhere in the known universe that allowed the quantum network to exist in all places. However, as the Flickering World had no such stations, it had yet to connect with the quantum network of the known universe and could only redirect signals from the dynasty's nodes and base stations. This move from Han Xiao was to plot out the army's network base stations here. When the Star Field was open to the public in the future, they would become natural intelligence channels. Usually, this was an authority only high-level civilizations had.

However, now, this was one of the privileges given to the dynasty's allied forces. The dynasty would not stop him.

The army's battleships passed through the stargate one after another. Very soon, they all arrived at the Flickering World and immediately headed toward Planet Lighthouse in hyperdrive.

There were currently no outsiders in the Dawn Star Cluster, so the trip was smooth. After traveling for a few days and through dozens of military stargates linking the various strongholds, they crossed the entire Dawn Star Cluster, and Planet Lighthouse was within their sights.

A planet surrounded by countless battleships appeared outside the porthole.

On a tiny planet, the dynasty's direct exploration team, the Bloodshed Land's exploration team, the Klent Kingdom's exploration team, and the late to the party Black Star Army's exploration team gathered. The number of spaceships gathered there exceeded a hundred million!

It was marvelous!

Among which, the dynasty's direct spaceships had the highest number. They made up to about seventy percent of all the spaceships.

Not far away from the planet, there were many stargate stations coexisting but were yet to be activated.

The surface of Planet Lighthouse was covered by machinery and metal, not showing even the slightest soil. The dynasty's exploration team used the dynasty's well known 'Foolproof Planet Base Expansion Pack' on Planet Lighthouse. It flattened the ground through high pressure, increased the planet density, changed its landscape, and modified its crust, directly turning this planet into a Planet Grade Military Base.

The fleet stopped outside the atmosphere. Han Xiao and the Black Star Guards took a small spaceship and landed on Planet Lighthouse's dock.

Whoosh!

The hatch opened.

Han Xiao stepped onto the metal dock, looked across at the metal buildings, and fixed onto the most conspicuous building far away.

It was a few-thousand-meter-tall building. All the buildings around it looked like dwarfs under a giant. This was Planet Lighthouse's stronghold headquarters.

There were already officers waiting at the dock. After they did their formal military greetings, they invited Han Xiao and the rest to board the ground carrier and head to Planet Lighthouse's headquarters together.

Whoosh!

As they traveled across the buildings on the planet's surface, the sound of wind howled outside their carrier.

Han Xiao observed around and realized that the buildings on the surface were mainly hangars and warehouses. Countless carriers and mechanical assistants were transporting trucks of resources like hard working ants.

Seeing that they were looking around, the officer explained, "Planet Lighthouse is the logistics base of the exploration team. A large amount of supplies and resources are stored here."

Han Xiao nodded. The three Star Clusters that would be explored in the first stage were Renault, Garu, and Crown, all neighboring Star Clusters of the Dawn Star Cluster. Planet Lighthouse was located at a crucial junction and was the best transit station.

The ground distance was very short, and they arrived at the Planet Lighthouse headquarters very soon. Through the anti-gravity lift, they came all the way to the middle level at the headquarters, more than 1,400 meters above the ground.

Following the instructions, they walked into an enormous strategy conference room. There were already many people in the room. Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and immediately saw Heber—with his tiny-mountain-sized body, he was the most conspicuous.

Heber turned and looked over. Their eyes clashed in midair. Heber's eyes had no emotions in them. He sat still on his seat and did not move before casually nodding in greeting.

Behind him were the Eight Vanguard Officials of the Bloodshed Land, who all looked at Han Xiao with hostility in their eyes.

That was especially so for the Chief Vanguard Official, Fosters, who looked like he wanted to turn his sight into knives and stab Han Xiao with them.

Although the Black Star Army and the Bloodshed Land had agreed to have a ceasefire, the hostility that the Bloodshed Land officers felt toward Han Xiao would not reduce because of it.

"Humph."

Seeing this, Hila took a step forward, and the Black Star Guards behind her followed right after, staring at the Vanguard Officials of Heber.

Hila and Fosters' sights met and almost created explosions in midair. The atmosphere became very tense.

In the past, when Han Xiao attended the Tyrant Party the second time, Fosters had challenged Han Xiao's subordinates. As the captain of the Black Star Guards, Hila had accepted the challenge, but Heber had appeared and told Fosters to back off, so the two of them did not end up fighting in the end.

Now that they had met again, this history appeared in both of their heads.

One was the Bloodshed Land's Chief Vanguard Official; the other was the Black Star Army's captain of the Black Star Guards. Be it their position, identity, or strength, they were naturally opposed to each other. Whoever beat the other would prove that their faction was better than another. The two of them stared at each other coldly while adding each other's name to the list of enemies they had to fight in the future.

Since Aurora had more than enough safety assurance, other than to repay Han Xiao, Hila continued to work for Han Xiao to become stronger. As she had the experience of being restrained by others, she had a very strong desire for power. Although she did not take the extreme path like she did in Han Xiao's previous life, she did not give up on any opportunities to challenge someone strong.

Han Xiao was not bothered. He waved and told the Black Star Guards to take a step back.

There was no way they would end up fighting right under the dynasty's nose, so there was no point in just staring at each other.

Seeing that the two sides had settled down, Han Xiao smiled at Heber.

"You're quite early."

"Unlike you, I don't like to be late," Heber replied indifferently.

He saw Han Xiao as someone on his level but had no intention of learning more about him or befriending him.

The two sides had a deep hatred for each other and only reluctantly became allies because of the dynasty. Although they were now at peace, they were still competitors in terms of the Flickering World exploration.

Since they were business competitors, Heber did not want to be friendly. His action of asking for a ceasefire with the Black Star Army in the past had already reduced his reputation within the Bloodshed Land. He could not let people mistakenly think that he was actually afraid of Black Star.

Han Xiao chuckled and knew exactly what Heber was thinking, but he did not mind.

Ty-Ty has been having a hard time. Let's not make it worse.

Not bothering about Heber, Han Xiao turned and looked at Tarrokov, who was standing beside the strategic analysis board. He smiled and said, "Chief commander, we finally meet."

"Your Excellency Black Star, Zoel might have already said this, but let me say it again. On behalf of the dynasty, we welcome your alliance."

When Han Xiao was speaking with Heber, Tarrokov watched from the side and did not speak. Once Han Xiao spoke to him, only then did he give a formal reply.

"Looks like we're going to be colleagues for a very long time in the future." Han Xiao shook Tarrokov's hands.

"Please, take a seat." Tarrokov smiled and pointed at a seat.

Han Xiao nodded and led his people to sit down. His men and Heber's men sat on opposite sides of the room, and the Klent Kingdom's men were in the middle.

The leader of the Klent Kingdom was someone Han Xiao did not know. They did not show Han Xiao any politeness at all, not even a greeting.

Compared to Klent, Heber's hatred was nothing. Klent's decade-long plan had been completely shattered. The secret war had been ended by Han Xiao single-handedly, and the resources they invested had yielded zero profit.

The loss they made was uncountable!

Hate Purple Crystal? They basically won without doing anything.

Hate the Crimson Dynasty? As if we would dare!

Hate the Bloodshed Land?

... Wake up!

Therefore, their hatred could only land on Han Xiao, no one else.

If the Bloodshed Land's hostility toward Han Xiao was two stars, Klent's hostility was at least ten stars.

"Since everyone's here, let's get started."

Tarrokov completely ignored the conflict between the three sides and turned on the strategic analysis board behind him. He brought up the unexplored star map of the Renault, Garu, and Crown Star Clusters.

"These three Star Clusters are the targets of the first stage of developments. The Bloodshed Land and Klent will explore Renault, the dynasty's direct teams will explore Crown, and the Black Star Army will explore Garu. These are your choices, which were made long ago. Now, let me talk about the details... The task of exploration is very cumbersome, but in the end, it can be divided into a few key points."

Tarrokov extended a few fingers.

"The drawing of the star map, the large-scale deployment of area observation buoys, the installation of a traffic network, the construction of transit stations and strongholds, the completion of the detailed information of the various planets... and the collection of resources."

Han Xiao nodded. These were just the main goals. There were tons of tasks that had to be carried out in reality. They had to carry out construction at the same time as exploring the map. The reason they had brought so many people there was to split up and increase their efficiency.

This time, Tarrokov said, "The dynasty has the most manpower. In order to ensure progress, we will be sending some teams to follow the three of you and provide assistance.

The dynasty made up to seventy percent of all the forces there, so it was normal to give them some of their manpower. However, this was just one reason; surveillance was another reason.

The dynasty was willing to let its ally forces take part in the exploration and share the benefits, but it could not completely leave things to its allies. Sending out these surveillance teams would prevent its allies from not reporting the resources discovered or reporting the incorrect quantity deliberately, ensuring the accuracy of the results of the exploration.

The dynasty has invested a lot of this, so of course, they're getting the largest portion of the resources in the new Star Field. Completely sensible...

However, there was still a lot of room in terms of how much extra profit the explorers would obtain.

The others had no idea what was on those unexplored planets and could only explore them one by one. It completely depended on their luck.

Han Xiao also did not know what was on most of the planets. He was an extremely experienced player in his previous life, but he was not as experienced as remembering the information about every single planet... However, he still knew full well about the famous and unique planets in the Flickering World.

This meant that he did not need to do field exploration to know which planets were extremely profitable and rich.

"Hmm..."

Han Xiao caressed his chin and contemplated.

Chapter 819: Special Exploration Route

Heber and the Klent commander knew that the dynasty would send out surveillance teams, so they were not surprised either.

Tarrokov explained the details as he pointed at the locations on the star map. The others listened silently.

When Tarrokov was finished, the Klent commander suddenly said, "We know what you've just said. What I want to know is, us Shattered Star Ring allies are the first teams to take part in the exploration, and the dynasty will be sending its allies from other Star Fields here too, so when will the next batch of dynasty allies arrive?"

Star Fields were too huge. Even all of them combined were just a leaf within a forest compared to a Star Field; they were very tiny. With just them, God only knew when the Flickering World would be fully explored. Therefore, the dynasty would be sending more manpower there in the future. Those dynasty allies who arrived later would be both allies and new competitors.

What Klent cared about was when the next batch of competitors would arrive, basically how much time they had ahead of others.

Tarrokov smiled.

"That depends on the arrangements of the dynasty's upper echelons and the gathering speed of our allied forces, as well as the progress of our exploration. I have yet to receive any notification on the exact time. However, according to my estimation, the next batch of exploration teams will only arrive in half a year's time at the earliest. Before that, the dynasty will have to rely on you guys. If the progress of the exploration is outstanding, the dynasty will not be petty in terms of rewards."

The few of them nodded. If the exploration was smooth and the results were beyond expected, it would all become their contributions. The dynasty would take a large portion of the resources, so they would be given rewards based on the results of the pioneering. This was the key factor of their competition.

The one whose exploration went the smoothest and obtained the most profit would be merited the most.

Tarrokov paused and asked, "For the Star Clusters you've decided to explore, what direction are you guys planning to enter from?"

The Star Cluster could be divided into dozens of Star Systems. They were all exploring into the center from the edges of it.

The border line was extremely long, so the direction they were going to enter from was very important. If they started exploring from poor locations, they would make a huge loss since they would waste a lot of time not discovering many resources.

The only information they had to decide on this was the semi-complete star map drawn through astronomical observations. The most they could do was just avoid the obvious desolate universe belts, but the resources on the planets were still unknown.

Although Tarrokov had only just asked, the few of them had discussed and analyzed this privately long ago.

Heber and Klent were on the same side. They planned to split into twenty-three teams and enter one Star System of their choice from twenty-three different locations. The teams would not be far from each other and would advance together in a fan shape, gradually gathering at a certain point to build a large transit stronghold. They would then continue to split and explore, making sure the exploration range of every team would not be repeated as much as possible.

Han Xiao listened as the Klent commander described their plan and nodded in his mind.

Heber had made a good choice. The first area they were going to explain was called the Jeraton Star System, a rather rich Star System of the Renault Star Cluster in his previous life. It did indeed have rich resources.

If the Flickering World's star map was 2D and linked with the known universe, the Dawn Star Cluster would be at the most west side of the Flickering World. As for the three Star Clusters right beside it, Garu was at its North, Renault was at its East, and Crown was at its South. The Jeraton Star System, which Heber and Klent were going to explore first, was the border Star System on the southwest side of Renault.

Tarrokov nodded, turned to look at Han Xiao, and asked, "What about you?"

Han Xiao pointed at the border Star System at the southernmost point of the Garu Star Cluster. He drew a route upward that penetrated more than ten Star Systems, connecting the southernmost part of the Garu Star Cluster to its easternmost part.

"What do you mean by this?" Tarrokov was surprised.

"Well..." Han Xiao smiled mysteriously. "I will have my main force explore from the border Star System at the southernmost side and send out a team carrying stargate devices. This team will only build stargates along the way and not make any other stops. I'm going to build a stargate route and connect these ten Star Systems together first."

"You want to build the important long traffic route first?" Tarrokov raised his brows.

"Not only that, whenever this team connects to the next Star System, I will split up more men to explore other Star Systems." Han Xiao shrugged.

Tarrokov frowned slightly. Heber and the Klent commander exchanged looks, too. They were a little speechless.

In their eyes, the problem with Black Star's exploration plan was too obvious—insufficient manpower.

With only so many people, even exploring one Star System would take a lot of time, yet Black Star wanted to explore more than ten Star Systems at the same time. How would he have enough manpower? They all thought that his appetite was too large, and it had exceeded his capabilities.

Building an important long traffic route first was a good thing to the dynasty, so Tarrokov had no problem with that. However, this did not match the profit perspective of a dynasty ally, so Han Xiao's decision surprised him.

This was not a horse race. There was no point in connecting all these Star Systems if he would not be able to finish exploring all of them. Since the exploration efficiency was limited, wasting manpower to build long-term stargate channels would only make traveling to other Star Systems much easier for the forces that would come later. This looked like it had many more cons than pros.

Klent and the Bloodshed Land wanted to finish exploring one Star System before going to the next. In comparison, they were exploring in areas while Han Xiao was exploring in lines.

To balance the profit between its allies, the dynasty's plan was also to gradually move forward and slowly explore, not preparing to install complete stargate traffic networks in the unexplored areas immediately. The astronomical observations had already given them a semi-complete star map, so what they lacked was the completion of detailed information and field inspection. Therefore, the goal of the first stage of the exploration was just the three areas beside the Dawn Star Cluster.

During the slow process of exploration, the exploration team would always be building stargates. Therefore, the long-distance stargate channels would eventually appear, and there was no need to build it specifically.

This meant that the Black Star Army was wasting its own resources and time while reducing its results. This made Tarrokov, Heber, the Klent commander very confused.

"Do you want to reconsider?" Tarrokov asked out of good intentions.

Han Xiao waved and chuckled. "No need, I like to rely on my luck. Maybe I can discover some rich resource planets in advance."

Seeing that Black Star remained stubborn, the Klent commander ridiculed him in his mind.

With such a poor exploration plan that clearly lacked consideration, their pioneering would definitely not go smoothly. This meant that they would most likely beat the Black Star Army this time.

"Okay then." Tarrokov did not insist.

No matter what method its allies used to explore, the dynasty would not make any losses. After all, the entire Star Field belonged to them. The only one that would make losses was the Black Star Army itself, and since Black Star did not care, he did not care either.

Han Xiao had a smile on his face, and the others could not figure out what he was thinking.

This exploration plan that looked to be very desperate for merit suited his goals the most.

The reason that the fewest organizations decided to explore the Garu Star Cluster, as mentioned by Zoel, was that in the few Star Systems at the south of the Garu Star Cluster, there were obvious desolate universe belts. If he imitated Heber and the others and only explored one border Star System, he would definitely not produce many results.

He used this exploration plan to first develop those known rich planets in his memories.

On this traffic route stretching from the south of Garu to the east, there were a few Star Systems that were extremely prosperous areas with many renowned rich planets in the previous life, which only he knew about now.

Also, as he stretched the exploration line, the surveillance of the dynasty would likely be less intense, which would give him room to operate.

Han Xiao was not going to give up on such a good opportunity.

Another goal he had was to distract the others away from his true goal.

Han Xiao hoped to go to the south of the Garu Star Cluster as soon as possible without seeming too obvious.

This was because the ownerless Universal Treasure in his memories was located in the other Star Cluster connected to the south of the Garu Star Cluster!

He would only be able to obtain that Universal Treasure as soon as possible if he built this stargate route!

Tarrokov turned off the star map and said with a deep voice, "It's all decided then. You guys, wait here for two days. I'll dispatch teams to fuse into your teams as well as pass the stargate, buoys, and the other exploration devices to you. We shall depart officially in two days."

"Okay," the Klent commander replied.

Han Xiao and Heber nodded and did not speak.

They stood up and left the conference room.

Walking out of the door, Han Xiao and Heber glanced at each other at the same time, as if their clashing sights created flames in midair. They then turned around and left with their officers in opposite directions.

"Hey, what do you think Black Star is thinking?"

Heber and Klent's men were walking together. On the way, a Vanguard Official could not help but ask the chief staff sergeant, Jorde, beside him.

"What are you trying to say?" Jorde glanced at him.

"Don't you know what kind of person Black Star is? He's never one to be willing to make losses. He clearly knows that there's no benefit in building the long-distance stargate route in advance, so he definitely has other motives."

Jorde's eyes flickered. "Indeed, Black Star's decision is strange..."

"Chief staff sergeant, what do you think his motive is?"

The people around all eavesdropped at the conversation.

"I'm not Black Star," Jorde said with resignation. "The only reason I can think of is that Black Star is not willing to explore the poor border Star Systems of the Garu Star Cluster. But still, there's no need for him to waste time and cross more than ten Star Systems. I can't think of any other reasons... Maybe his appetite is too large, or maybe he really wants to rely on his luck."

"Maybe he wants to first take over the planets that will be traffic stations in the future."

"No way, the dynasty won't allow it."

As the Flickering World was an undeveloped Star Field, everyone subconsciously had one assumption—no one knew the detailed information of the Flickering World. Therefore, there was no way anyone could guess Han Xiao's motives.

The Klent commander quickly walked to Heber's side and said softly, "Your Excellency Tyrant, what do you say we..."

"Finish your sentence if you have something to say. Don't make me guess." Heber looked straight forward.

"... what do you say we send people to secretly head to the Garu Star Cluster and monitor Black Star's movements?"

"What's the point of that?" Heber glanced at him. "Do you dare disrupt the exploration right under the dynasty's nose?"

The Klent commander was stunned for a moment. He pondered carefully and came to a realization.

Exploring the Flickering World was the dynasty's key strategic goal, so even if they did know what the Black Star Army was planning to do, they could not do anything about it. If they disrupted the exploration progress for their own interest, the dynasty would definitely not show mercy and make them an example, to show the other allied organizations who would participate in the exploration in the future what the consequences of daring to disrupt the dynasty's plans were.

Having realized that, the Klent commander backed off and did not mention this matter anymore.

It seemed like the only way to be above the Black Star Army was to compete fairly through their pioneering results.

Luckily, not only did Black Star choose the Garu, but he also chose to use a horrible plan. The Bloodshed Land and their victory were certain.

Chapter 820: The Star of the Main Storyline and Stowaways

The fleet stayed on Planet Lighthouse for two days receiving all kinds of exploration devices from Tarrokov. Huge alloy containers were loaded into the transport ships of the Black Star Army and neatly arranged.

These were all exploration supplies provided by the dynasty. There were stargate devices, Foolproof Planet Base Expansion Packs, universe surveillance buoys, and so on. These were all military devices that were unavailable to the general public and only occasionally appeared on the black markets.

Han Xiao told Phillip to do a count. They had received about five hundred sets of stargate devices, six thousand Foolproof Planet Base Expansion Packs, and fifteen billion universe surveillance buoys. These were not given but lent to him as mission items.

Also, Tarrokov had dispatched a dynasty fleet that temporarily joined the Black Star Army's teams to assist him in exploring the Garu Star Cluster. The commander of this fleet was a major under Tarrokov. His name was Senico.

Tarrokov would be stationed on Planet Lighthouse as the chief commander, and the dynasty fleets he sent out all had their own commanders. Senico was Tarrokov's direct subordinate, as well as one of the dynasty officers stationed in the Flickering World according to Han Xiao's memories. Han Xiao had a faint image of him.

As they would be working alongside each other during the exploration, Han Xiao met and spoke with Senico. They came to a simple consensus; Senico expressed that he would not interfere with Black Star's exploration plan and would only be assisting them mainly.

After preparing for two days, the chief commander finally announced the start of the operation. The fleets of various forces went in their separate ways to the Star Clusters of their choices.

The Renault Star Cluster would be explored by the Bloodshed Land and Klent, Garu by the Black Star Army, and the Crown Star Cluster by the dynasty's remaining fleet. Comparatively, the Crown Star Cluster had the most people, and the Garu Star Cluster had the fewest.

The Black Star Army and Senico's fleet headed to the most South Star System of the Garu Star Cluster.

Before departing, Han Xiao had already announced the army's exploration plan to all the members, including the millions of players.

He had put up all kinds of tasks on the faction mission list, such as exploring planets and deploying buoys, which were also classified into different areas. There were plenty of missions, but each one of them had a maximum participant limit.

The many kinds of exploration missions sparked discussion on the forums. Different exploration missions gave different Exploration Points, and the Exploration Points relied on the actual results of those missions. The players would only know how many Exploration Points they would get when they completed them, so the players could only speculate and analyze for the moment, but they were still enjoying it.

On the forums, the players generally agreed that exploring planets theoretically would lead to the most results. As discovering resources and lives, digging up the planet's history, mining the resources, and the other activities that would possibly happen during exploring planets all gave Exploration Points as a reward. At the same time, the process of it was filled with the joy of discovering the unknown.

In comparison, those missions to deploy buoys, build stargates, and construct strongholds were considered hard labor tasks. They were the least popular missions among the players.

Han Xiao knew that once the players were more familiar with the process of the exploration, the guilds would start fighting each other as the large guilds would want to make planets with rich resources their guild resource point. Although they would only be able to obtain a small portion of the total resources mined, that would still be considered a large reward to the players.

In his previous life, there were two reasons for the players of different nations to fight each other—faction wars and planets with rich resources. Now, however, all the millions of the players were in his faction, so there would be no faction conflicts. The only reason they would fight each other now would be for the ownership of resource points.

Although things had yet to reach the stage of intense guild wars, he knew that there would definitely be competition since there were club guilds from different nations in the army.

One reason he encouraged socializing between players was to reduce the impact of the guild conflicts on normal players as much as possible. The conflict between players was unavoidable, but he wanted to prevent the players from having direct hostility toward each other.

As long as the players in his army were not divided to such an extent, the competition between guilds would not affect his profit. After all, the players would still have to repair their equipment in the army after they damaged it during battle.

After some days, the various fleets arrived at their respective locations and officially started their exploration tasks.

The Black Star Army's exploration team came to the southernmost Star System of Garu and built the first transit station according to the plan, connecting with the Dawn Star Cluster.

The engineering team used a Foolproof Planet Base Expansion Pack on a desolate planet at the border of the Star System. The transport ship opened its cabin, and hundreds of thousands of gigantic mechanical bases that looked like needles flew out—they were all base nodes.

The base nodes formed a large net and shrouded the entire planet.

Then, the thrusters of these nodes shot out orange flames and penetrated the planet's atmosphere. Like hundreds of thousands of missiles, these nodes landed and plugged deep into the planet surface, stirring up endless dust.

The next moment, all the base nodes were activated. A red light appeared on the top of these nodes as they started to modify the planet's environment and terrain. Every node was vibrating and emitting impact waves one after another, triggering earthquakes and tearing the ground open.

Gray and silver metal extended from these nodes and spread over the ground, turning the planet surface into a metal surface. According to the preset program, bases, fortresses, and warehouses would rise from the ground.

After dozens of hours, the initial modification was complete. The once desolate planet now looked completely different; it became a planet fortress in gray and silver. This was the first stronghold in the Garu Star Cluster.

The dynasty's engineering ships were not just watching. They dragged along gigantic parts of the stargate and were assembling it beside this stronghold.

An unactivated stargate looked like a gigantic hollow mechanical ring. After it was activated, the inner circle of this mechanical ring emitted blue light and space energy, connecting to one of the stargates near Planet Lighthouse.

Then, the hollow part of the mechanical ring turned into a wormhole-like blue vortex, becoming a fully functional stargate.

Other than the team left behind to build the stronghold, the rest split up. Some went to deploy buoys nearby, and some went to explore the unknown planets nearby.

A Star System had about ten Star Zones. The main team of the Black Star Army was now exploring the first Star Zone.

According to the plan, Han Xiao sent out a special task force led by Hadavy to move alone with a hundred and fifty stargate devices. Its goal was to cross the many Star Systems and head to the east of the Garu Star Cluster, building a long distance stargate route on the way.

The spaceships given to this special task force were all high-grade transport ships that had a maximum speed of 14.1 warp speed. It would take about four months for them to reach the destination through nonstop hyperdrive.

After the special task force completed building the long distance stargate route, the four-month trip would be reduced to a mere few hours.

As countless army members were doing their part, Han Xiao led a group of army warriors and players to a planet at the center of this Star Zone on the main ship.

In his memories, this planet was a trade transfer station and one of the entrances into the Garu Star Cluster in his previous life. It was rather valuable. Furthermore, it did not have a harsh environment and was quite habitable. It also had a native civilization.

Currently, this planet did not have a name yet and only had a serial number. He wanted to head there in advance and start its exploration.

Outside the border of the Shattered Star Ring was the edge of the known universe, the desolate universe belt between the Shattered Star Ring and the Flickering World.

Fleets left from the border one after another from different locations, turning into hyperdrive streams of light and entering the desolate universe belt, heading in the Flickering World's direction.

News of the Crimson Dynasty exploring the Flickering World had spread across the entire galaxy. Although the dynasty clearly stated that the other civilizations were not allowed to enter, the mere words on paper were not enough to scare those powerful forces away. They all wanted to enter the Flickering World in advance to grab the opportunities there.

These fleets were from different civilizations and organizations; they all hid their identities.

As they were unable to use the dynasty's stargate, they could only sneak into the Flickering World, taking along stargate devices and planning to secretly build stargate routes without getting discovered by the dynasty.

Even though these fleets were all extremely quick. it would still take a very long time for them to cross the desolate universe belt and arrive at the Flickering World.

Among these smugglers, some were doing it for profits, and some had ulterior motives.

One of them was the group of people the Arcane Church secretly sent.

Chapter 821: Aesop's Fully Automated Enemy Radar

The blue colored planet, Planet Aquamarine, slowly rotated with spaceships constantly flying out from within the planet, leaving behind light trails as they departed.

The sun shone down on the tall buildings of the capital, and the windows reflected the blue sky and white clouds. Trains roared along the tracks, and anti-gravity suspension vehicles weaved within the city. There was a sense of liveliness within the city, a beautiful and prosperous sight.

At the terminal of Black Star City, Bennett stood there with a group of people in wait.

He stood by the window, observing the scenery of the vibrant capital outside. A sense of relief was seen on Bennett's face.

With Han Xiao helping Planet Aquamarine break into the Shattered Star Ring Civilization Conference, many of the financial groups and organizations began to pay more attention to the development prospects of Planet Aquamarine. This brought about a new round of development opportunities, with the frequent trade circulation resulting in the increasing prosperity of the planet.

As for the citizens, after experiencing so many hardships, they finally began to smile at the thought of better days. The more the people enjoyed the happiness and fortune brought to Planet Aquamarine, the more they worshipped their guardian Black Star, who had brought all this to them.

A spaceship flew into the dock, and its hatch opened. Nero walked out, accompanied by a few soldiers, and the moment he saw Bennett, his expression softened. He ran as fast as his short legs could to Bennett.

"Dad!"

Bennett turned around, looking down toward him with a hint of suspicion on his face. "Why did you come back so soon? What did Black Star bring you into the universe for?"

Nero scratched his head, his tone downcast. "We only studied Mechanic theories most of the time. Godfather only took me out to play a few days before throwing me aside..."

Han Xiao had taken the majority of troops over to the Flickering World, and it was unknown when he could return, so he naturally left Nero behind, instructing Sylvia to send some people to accompany him back to Planet Aquamarine.

As he spoke, Nero seemed frustrated.

"Mr. Reynold said that this time was a vacation for me, and he even gave me homework to do during this time. He said that I can only come back for two months. Following that, he'll send someone over to pick me up so that I can continue studying under him."

Having received Han Xiao's command, Reynold taught Nero whenever Han Xiao was not around. He seriously performed this duty, and he had already planned out the curriculum of the year in advance.

"It's a rare chance that Black Star is willing to groom and nurture you. Don't let him down." Bennett laughed and squatted so that his eyes were level with Nero's. Looking at his child kindly, he said, "Tell me what you experienced in the universe outside."

Twisting his fingers, Nero recounted his experiences. He sounded excited because while the homework he got from Han Xiao was boring, it was still his first time outside exploring the universe. He had seen many strange and interesting things, and he was still quite satisfied overall with the trip.

Bennett listened and nodded, sighing secretly to himself.

He could feel that Han Xiao had taken an interest in Nero. It was not just because this kid was his child, but rather, he seemed to have a talent that Han Xiao appreciated, so Bennett was quite proud of this.

His child could actually display such talents. It seemed that he had some superior genes. Bennett began to seriously consider if he should go for a second child.

He was not willing to see this in a utilitarian manner, but if he put the future of Planet Aquamarine into consideration, if he had a few more talented children, with all of them studying under Han Xiao, Planet Aquamarine would have even stronger ties with Black Star himself.

While he might be old, his body that was forged with Pugilist skills was still lively, full of 'ammunition'.

Among the list of most charming men, the Planet Aquamarine leader Bennett ranked second overall, which showed the love and support he received from the people. The hearts of the citizens were one thing; in addition, his status, age, and fit body formed the vibe of a stable and mature man, which was attractive to the women.

As for the number one on the list... it was without doubt Han Xiao. This position was something that no one could move or shake no matter what. With so many achievements, it did not matter what angle they looked at him from—they still found him handsome.

Before long, Nero spoke till his throat was parched, and he finally heaved a sigh. He was still excited over the happenings in the universe.

Bennett stopped him, rubbing his hair as he stood up. "Ok, that's enough. When we have more time, I'll talk in detail with you. You should return home to rest. I'm still waiting for someone here."

A look of surprise crossed Nero's face. "Aren't you here to pick me up?"

Bennett shook his head in response, looking at the universe far above from the window.

"I'm waiting for someone even more important."

...

At the same time, in the extreme end of Planet Aquamarine's area of influence, a deep blue spaceship was shuttling through the universe in hyperdrive, quickly approaching Planet Aquamarine.

"So, this is Planet Aquamarine, Black Star's mother planet..."

Within the cabin, a lifeform with deep blue skin stared at the screen, his tone pleasant. He was the captain of this spaceship, and he possessed four arms and three eyes, similar to the rest of the crew.

This entire spaceship consisted of members from the Star Pupil Holy Race.

The captain turned around to survey the crew before coldly remarking, "Black Star had stolen our national treasure, and this is a humiliation to our entire race. Our leaders are weak, not daring to do this nor that. But we, the Avitan Souls, dare!"

The captain's voice was sonorous, and all the crew showed excited expressions, holding their weapons tightly.

"Because of the Evolution Cube, our Planet Avitan suffered an attack, and countless compatriots died. Our loved ones and friends are still trapped within this disaster. So many of them died, just so the Evolution Cube would not fall into the hands of others! Thus, this war crime is not just pinned on EsGod but also on Black Star!"

The captain pointed toward the direction of Planet Aquamarine before growling. "Only by spilling the fresh blood for revenge can we allow Black Star to regret his shameless behavior, allowing him to understand the humiliation he has submitted the Star Pupil Holy Race to. The despair he has left for us, we'll take it from him!"

Many of the crew members roared with hatred.

Initially, in order to lure the tiger away from the mountains, they literally washed the entire Planet Avitan in blood. This disaster was the most painful memory of the Star Pupil Holy Race, and a few of the survivors had lost their minds because of hatred and turned into extremists. Thus, an extremist group was born, and they called themselves 'Avitan Souls'. These extremists were basically almost made up of the survivors of the Avitan, especially those who had closed ones and friends who died within the disaster.

Because they had lost their national treasure, the Evolution Cube, Psyker's prestige among the Star Pupil Holy Race had plummeted. The extremists who bore huge pain blamed Psyker for his incompetence and deeply hated the culprit, EsGod. Because the root of the disaster was due to the Evolution Cube, many of their comrades had sacrificed their lives. Thus, the Avitan Souls had developed a morbid obsession with the Evolution Cube, turning their hate toward Black Star, who had taken it.

The Evolution Cube was the treasure of their country in the eyes of the Star Pupil Holy Race. This impression had persisted for a long time, and now that the Evolution Cube had switched owners, the Star Pupil Holy Race treated Han Xiao with enmity. As for the Avitan Souls, they were even more extreme. Since Psyker was unable to retrieve the Evolution Cube, as though he was afraid of the dynasty retaliating, the Avitan Souls lost all faith in Psyker and decided to take matters into their own hands.

Upon hearing that Han Xiao would be taking his officers out for a trip for a long time, the Avitan Souls felt that their opportunity had arrived. Thus, they took the chance to plan an attack on Black Star's mother planet, to execute their revenge, allowing Black Star to only be able to watch as his homeland was being destroyed.

Since Planet Aquamarine was part of the Shattered Star Ring Civilization Conference, even Psyker could not move rashly against them. Of course, these sorts of rules that bound the upper echelons were not considered at all by the extremists since they were outliers. They disregarded rules, as well as consequences, and only inflicted destruction as everything of theirs had been destroyed.

While Psyker was regarded as the best leader of the Star Pupil Holy Race thus far, he was not a god and could not control the thoughts of every one of his clansmen. Every race would always have a few people who were more inclined toward extreme measures, drowned by hatred. This was something that even the advanced civilization of the Star Pupil Holy Race could not avoid.

The captain turned to his first mate. "How are the weapons?"

The first mate nodded. "The five high-class psionic energy bombs are enough to annihilate the entire planet. They're ready to be deployed at any time."

"Very good. It is said that this sort of ammunition can destroy a continent with just one bomb. Three is enough to destroy the planet's surface, and our objective is to ensure all five land on Planet Aquamarine, allowing this planet to accompany us in our demise. Let them feel our pain!" The captain's tone was sinister; they did not plan to leave alive.

While those high-class Psionic Energy bombs could not compare to the Primordial Psionic Energy Bombs, they were still restricted weapons prohibited by the three major Universe Civilizations because they left terrible psionic pollution. Only Star Cluster Civilizations would possess such a thing generally.

The Avitan Souls were an organization that had only recently been established and did not possess any technological or scientific strength. The bomb was actually quietly funded by someone belonging to a civilization within the area where the Star Pupil Holy Race was located.

This civilization had always been wary of the rising Star Pupil Holy Race, and because they had the backing of the Arcane Church, no one could act against them. However, the Avitan Souls were an opportunity for them to frame the Star Pupil Holy Race. Thus, they used this borrowed knife to try and cause trouble in the Star Pupil Holy Race.

Just as the captain was about to strike, a blip appeared on their radar, and the artificial intelligence of the ship sent out a notification.

"Warning! A large, unidentified object is approaching!"

Everyone turned their heads toward the porthole to look, seeing a huge floating island swimming in the universe toward them.

"Floating Dragon Island?" The captain recognized this homeless floating island and was confused over why it had appeared there, as though it was proceeding toward Planet Aquamarine.

Floating Dragon Island slowly moved toward the deep blue spaceship. Comparing the two was just like comparing an elephant to a sesame seed.

"Let's move away. Don't obstruct Floating Dragon."

The captain quickly gave the command. Floating Dragon was a neutral force and would not actively attack any passing spaceship. He planned to pause his operation for the time being, waiting for Floating Dragon to leave before continuing.

The spaceship was positioned below the entire island, and from the window, they could only see the rocks that made up the foundation of the island but not its entirety.

The pilot raised the spaceship and flew above the foundations of the island, level with the city line.

Everyone within the cabin got a rude shock at this time. They found out that in the most conspicuous position of the island, Ames stood there in a black dress, staring straight at them!

"She's looking at us?"

Just as this thought passed by their minds, an unparalleled force field descended on them.

Hong!

Blood flowers blossomed!

The bodies of all the Star Pupil Holy Race members were squashed and turned into piles of meat. They died without warning on the spot.

On the harbor of Floating Dragon Island, Ames casually waved her hand, dispelling the field before speaking to Vilna by her side. "Search the spaceship. See if there are any dangerous weapons within."

"Yes." Vilna immediately deployed her people.

Ames then turned to look at Aesop by her side, her brows slightly furrowed.

"Are you sure that the people within this spaceship planned to harm Planet Aquamarine? I didn't kill wrongly, right?"

Aesop only stroked his beard as he laughed. "When you spoke about moving Floating Dragon over, I did a divination a few days ago. These people are the natives of Psyker's race, and it seems that because of the issue with the Evolution Cube, they wish to eradicate Planet Aquamarine as revenge against Black Star. They did not succeed in the end as they were destroyed by the anti-space defense of Black Star, but since we're here, let's just do him a favor."

Ames shook her head helplessly. "I didn't expect to have become a guard for his house."

Aesop stared at her in surprise. "Didn't you move Floating Dragon here to help him defend Planet Aquamarine?"

"Oh, this is to obtain the greatest benefits for Floating Dragon. Furthermore, I'm strengthening our alliance. How is this of his concern? Even if it's for someone else, it would have to be for my two students." Ames turned around to leave, her dress spiraling like a blooming black flower.

Aesop sent Ames off with his eyes before turning to Jenny.

"We're almost here. Notify them."

Jenny nodded without any change in her expression.

...

Bennett continued standing by the dock, his head raised as he observed the endless universe.

A huge shadow suddenly blotted out the sun. It spread quickly, covering the entire dock in an instant.

One only saw a humongous floating island appear in their vision, leisurely cruising toward Planet Aquamarine.

Bennett smiled.

"The VIP is finally here."

Chapter 822: Handle

Floating Dragon floated beside Planet Aquamarine like a gigantic satellite, and the citizens on the ground could see a gigantic floating island in the sky if they looked up. Numerous individuals could not help but stop what they were doing and look up at the sky with shock on their faces.

"What's that? Why does it seem so familiar?"

"Mummy! I have seen it in the encyclopedia before. That's the legendary Floating Dragon Island. It drifts around in space! The palace of Dragon Emperor!" A young excited voice exclaimed while pointing at the sky.

"Oh! So, it's Ames."

After Planet Aquamarine broke free from Godora's information lockdown, the knowledge of the citizens rose rapidly in the ten subsequent years. They all had basic understanding toward the famous characters in the Shattered Star Ring and were extremely familiar with Ames because of Han Xiao.

The citizens all knew that she was once Black Star's superior and knew that they could only connect to the galaxy because of Floating Dragon's protection. Thus, Ames and Floating Dragon had a special position in the hearts of the citizens.

Upon witnessing Floating Dragon Island approach Planet Aquamarine, many of the citizens could not help be both surprised and curious. They immediately called their friends to inform them of the news, and a huge commotion was created.

The various financial groups stationed on Planet Aquamarine had also noticed Floating Dragon's presence and were extremely surprised. They approached the Planet Aquamarine government to find out what was going on.

At the same time, Ames and the others arrived at the dock in a small spaceship to meet Bennett.

"Your Excellency Dragon Emperor, Planet Aquamarine welcomes your arrival." Bennett bowed and spoke with reverence in his voice.

He was extremely familiar with Han Xiao, and they had known each other for over twenty years. Thus, he could naturally behave more casually around Han Xiao. However, he was not familiar with Ames, and even though Bennett knew that Han Xiao had a good relationship with Ames, he would not dare overstep his bounds.

Ames waved her arm to indicate that Bennett did not need to be so polite. She then said with a smile, "Black Star should have informed you of my request, and you should have contacted Jenny as well."

Bennett nodded. He had received news from Han Xiao a while ago and knew that Floating Dragon was about to be stationed near Planet Aquamarine. He had been truly shocked when he heard the news and was overjoyed shortly after. He knew that this was a rare opportunity and hurriedly mobilized manpower to work together with Floating Dragon.

He kept the matter a secret according to Ames' wishes and only planned to announce the matter to the public after Floating Dragon's arrival. The abruptness of the news would be beneficial to breaking everyone's impression of Floating Dragon and also establishing a new image.

As such, Bennett did not announce the matter to the citizens of Planet Aquamarine beforehand.

"I will hold a press conference in the name of Planet Aquamarine and announce that Floating Dragon will be setting up their base here."

"How long do you need to get it done?"

"I only need a couple of hours. Some of the galactic media groups have their reporters stationed here, and it won't take too long for me to invite them. What do you think?"

Ames then nodded to indicate her approval. Floating Dragon would remain there for a long period of time, and the reason for her arrival today was to attend the press conference.

"Right, I met with some extremists from the Star Pupil Holy Race just now. They were roaming around the vicinity of Planet Aquamarine and had dangerous explosives loaded up on their spaceship. It seems as though they intended to ambush Planet Aquamarine, so I killed them out of convenience. A recording is present on their spaceship, and I shall hand them over to you."

Bennett was taken aback.

The Star Pupil Holy Race... This should be because of Black Star right? They have transferred their hatred for Black Star to Planet Aquamarine.

"I will inform His Excellency Black Star," Bennett said with a grave tone. This matter involved the race of another Beyond Grade A Super, so it was not appropriate for the leader of a civilization that had not even reached the Star System level to handle it. Thus, he was prepared to ask for Han Xiao's opinion.

Although this matter was stopped in time, it could be said that the innocent Planet Aquamarine had been implicated because of Black Star. Planet Aquamarine had once suffered from a similar catastrophe before when Stephanie, who was under Thousand Shadows, had tried to cause chaos on the planet to deal with Black Star.

However, Bennett did not have any complaints. He was extremely clear that since they wanted to enjoy the benefits that Black Star brought to them, they would also be targeted by Black Star's enemies. There was no such thing as a free lunch.

The battle between those high up above was like a raging storm, and the current Planet Aquamarine was just like a little boat in the ocean. They would be easily capsized if they were not careful, with all of them ending up dead. However, it would be extremely cowardly for them to throw away the opportunity for their civilization to rise and cut off all ties with their own protector. Perhaps the leaders of the Six Nations would have considered such a choice, but Bennett definitely would not waver.

With Floating Dragon's arrival and a Beyond Grade A Super being stationed there, the safety of Planet Aquamarine would be increased by a few different levels, and no one would treat Planet Aquamarine as Black Star's weakness anymore.

Bennett naturally did not know Ames' intentions for coming to Planet Aquamarine. Thus, he felt that Han Xiao was definitely behind this matter. If not, Ames would not have shown Planet Aquamarine such a great deal of face. As such, he could not help but admire Han Xiao for his foresight.

...

Three hours later, many different galactic reporters were gathered in a hall, awaiting the start of the press conference.

"The Planet Aquamarine government called for a press conference shortly after Floating Dragon's appearance. Their agenda today is probably related to Floating Dragon."

"It is probably going to be big news."

"It can't be right? Floating Dragon is always drifting around in space and will never stay in a single place for long. It shouldn't be anything special for them to arrive at Planet Aquamarine, right?"

The reporters then saw a couple of workers carry some equipment in and set up a live broadcast station in the room.

Everyone could not help but be startled when they saw that.

They wanted to have a live broadcast to the entire planet. Only a large matter would require a live broadcast.

Just when everyone was guessing what the announcement would be about, the doors to the hall opened wide. Upon turning around to take a look, everyone's expression froze in place with a look of shock on their faces.

The individual walking in was not the usual media department of the Planet Aquamarine government but the leader of the government making a personal appearance. Beside him was a famous character whose name shook the entire Star Field—Dragon Emperor Ames.

All the reporters were truly shocked. Why would Ames appear in the Planet Aquamarine government's press conference‽

They then watched as Bennett and Ames walked onto the stage.

"There is something that I must announce to the entire Star Field." Bennett cleared his throat and said with a solemn tone, "From today on, Floating Dragon will remain outside of Planet Aquamarine's atmosphere for the long run, and I represent the Planet Aquamarine government in welcoming our new neighbor."

Before everyone could even react, Ames said, "Floating Dragon has been drifting for too long, and I have decided to stop it from drifting. From today on, this place shall be Floating Dragon's main camp."

Pin drop silence filled the place, and everyone was truly dumbfounded.

Boom!

The entire hall burst into an uproar!

All the reporters were trembling from excitement!

This was a huge scoop!

...

News of Floating Dragon setting up a base spread throughout the entire Shattered Star Ring like wildfire, and all the organizations were in shock.

For the Floating Dragon to stop drifting, it could only mean that Ames was going to set up a proper organization. However, this was not the piece of news that puzzled people the most. The most shocking piece of news was the fact that the address for her new base was on Black Star's mother planet!

All the large organizations knew that the most eye-catching base of the Black Star Army was their headquarters, which was usually located at Planet Golden Gate. After Han Xiao obtained a seat in the Civilization Conference through the name of Planet Aquamarine, many individuals all felt that Planet Aquamarine would become Black Star's second base.

Just what was Floating Dragon thinking, setting up their main camp in Black Star's main camp?

Did this mean that both Beyond Grade A organizations were going to have an even closer relationship?

No, there was definitely something more to this!

Back when Heber challenged Black Star, Black Star had joined hands with the Dragon Emperor. Furthermore, the alliance between the Black Star Army and Floating Dragon was something that everyone in the Shattered Star Ring was aware about. But even if both parties were allies, their scope of operations were still clearly defined and did not clash with each other. Black Star Army had many branches while Floating Dragon drifted around without a fixed location.

But now, Floating Dragon had chosen to stay on Planet Aquamarine. They were not setting up a casual branch but their main base!

For an organization at the level of the Black Star Army and Floating Dragon, they would not set up their main base at the same location if there was not a special reason. They would only set up a branch in the territory of their ally at the very most. However, Dragon Emperor had shifted her base over to Black Star's mother planet, and her intention obviously was not to fight over territory with Black Star.

This signified their absolute trust in each other!

They both believed that the other party would not betray them. If not, they would never expose their backs to each other. Such a level of trust was extremely rare among galactic organizations.

The relationship that both parties had displayed had already exceeded the realm of ordinary allies. They were close to the point that all the organizations could not help but think of another possibility. Could it be that there was a chance for both organizations to merge?

No Beyond Grade A Super would be willing to be a subordinate to another Beyond Grade A Super usually. Apart from submitting and working together, there was another relationship that was extremely common among normal beings but extremely rare among Beyond Grade A Supers...

The various organizations were not just letting their imaginations run wild but were making deductions based on the history between Black Star and the Dragon Emperor. Furthermore, Black Star had even taken Ames along with him to the Dynasty Ruler a while back!

This was a dangerous signal.

If both parties really merged together, an organization with unprecedented power would be born in the Shattered Star Ring, and the balance of the Shattered Star Ring would change greatly.

Back then, many organizations wished to drive a wedge between the Black Star Army and Floating Dragon, but they had failed. Now, many organizations still were not willing to see Floating Dragon and the Black Star Army become even closer.

Since this matter involved their interests, many organizations could not help but be alarmed.

...

On the contrary, many financial groups were extremely excited by this piece of news.

The development potential of Planet Aquamarine was pretty good before this, and with the addition of Floating Dragon's presence, Planet Aquamarine's potential had exploded.

All the financial groups that had cooperated with Planet Aquamarine early on injected another round of funds, and many other financial groups began to approach Planet Aquamarine to seek cooperation.

The citizens of Planet Aquamarine naturally would not reject it and were all filled with surprise.

...

In the Flickering World, rays of hyperdrive light sliced through the universe and stopped outside the atmosphere of a purple planet. This was the fleet that Han Xiao was in.

The majority of their manpower had already been sent out to explore other undiscovered planets, resulting in the small size of the fleet.

This purple planet was one of the transit stations in Han Xiao's memories and was the target that he was prepared to explore. It was called Planet Pangurus in his previous life.

Because the unexplored regions did not have a stargate, the fleet took quite some time to arrive.

"We have arrived at our destination. Army Commander, please give us your next orders."

Aurora stood up straight and pretended to mimic the voice of a soldier making a report, but before she could finish her sentence, she could not hold back her laughter.

"The engineering team should set up a stargate here, and the detection fleet should revolve around the planet to create a map. Make use of the detection devices to sense the presence of life and the resources on the planet. We will allow our exploratory squad to set off after the map is completed..."

Before Han Xiao could finish what he had to say, Phillip's voice sounded in his head and interrupted him.

"Master, there is an emergency message from Planet Aquamarine, hum..."

The message then appeared in his quantum network. It was news that was sent by Bennett. Bennett had reported about successfully receiving Floating Dragon and also mentioned about the Avitan Souls incident together with a recording of what happened in the spaceship, asking him how the matter should be handled.

Han Xiao immediately frowned.

"Psyker didn't provoke me, but there are people within his race who want to deal with me. Avitan Souls? There seems to be a small organization by that name. Don't they hate EsGod? Why have I been dragged into this? They even want to commit suicide and destroy an entire planet? Is there really a need for such hatred? They are truly a ferocious bunch. Also, where did their psionic explosives come from?"

Han Xiao was a little helpless. This was one of the side effects of him obtaining the Evolution Cube. He was not too bothered by such an extremist organization. Everyone's mental capacity was limited, and both war and calamities were the best way to cause the formation of an extremist group. Logic was not the only way for a living being to judge the things around them, and their emotions were usually more powerful than logic.

However, the vengeful actions of these extremists did Psyker a favor.

Han Xiao shook his head. He was not planning to pretend that nothing had happened.

Since Planet Aquamarine had a seat in the Civilization Conference, it was akin to them gaining the privileges of a Star System Civilization, and they would also be protected by the Peace Treaty. This was a good opportunity for him to exploit.

He then gave a reply to Bennett.

"Preserve the evidence and contact Purple Crystal on my behalf. Bring this matter to the Shattered Star Ring Civilization Conference and expose it to all the civilizations. I will take care of the rest."

Although this matter would not do anything to Psyker, it would still disgust him for sure.

A small extremist group of his race personally delivering an excuse and the evidence to his hands. In the end, the entire Star Pupil Holy Race would have to take the blame for the matter. Who knew how Psyker would feel about this matter?

Chapter 823: Natives

After giving instructions to Bennett, Han Xiao left the quantum network and returned to reality to monitor the work on Planet Pangurus.

The engineering fleet began constructing stargates outside the atmosphere, and the small detection squad revolved around the planet to scan the planet's situation.

Very quickly, a holographic figure of Planet Pangurus was created with the details being perfected rapidly. Han Xiao and the other officers watched as the holographic planet became more and more detailed.

Not too long later, the detection fleet returned; they had completed their first round of exploration.

Detailed figures of the planet were shown on the maps including the gravity pull, atmosphere breakdowns, climate, size, and ocean ratio.

Apart from this, the 3D map was also demarcated into various regions by color to indicate the different resources located on the planet and the locations where lifeforms had gathered.

Aurora read the report.

"This planet is extremely rich in common resources, and apart from that, there are plenty of rare resources underground such as Dark Gold Mines, Purple Silver Mines, Origin Crystal Mines, and a dozen of different rare materials. These are the important materials for magical Star Systems, and its market price is 60 Enas for 10,000 tons. This planet has billions of tons in the mines...

"At the extreme north of the planet, we also detected about 800,000 tons of the rare mountain essence. Every ton is priced around 6,000 Enas. We also discovered some ingots that had spiritual energy stored within them. There isn't much, and they should be worth about 1,200,000,000 Enas..."

Han Xiao listened for a moment before nodding. "Give me an estimate of the planet's value."

"According to our initial scans, the value of this planet should be about 18,000,000,000 Enas. If we can find more valuable resources when digging deeper, its value will go up."

"It's pretty valuable." Han Xiao smiled.

This planet could be considered rather resource rich when compared to other mining planets.

However, despite the initial valuation of the planet being high, it would take more than a hundred years to fully reap all the benefits.

In the universe, resource rich planets would be tightly grasped in the hands of the various civilizations, and they would not sell them off like uninhabited planets.

The civilization would slowly excavate the resources of the planet and ensure that the excavation could be sustained for a long period.

Even an advanced civilization would not destroy the golden goose if they did not meet an emergency.

Resource rich planets were an important source of revenue for civilizations.

A civilian miner could only mine on the edges of a desolate planet to feed their family. Civilizations did not think much of a desolate planet and would usually sell these planets to civilian organizations. The Black Star Army obtaining the rights to mine on a resource rich planet was already the limits of a private organization.

Exploring the Flickering World was definitely a good opportunity for development. After the allies of the dynasty discovered a resource rich planet, although they needed to inform the dynasty and let the dynasty take the majority of the share, they would be able to gain the rights to mine for a short while and share a portion of the benefits.

Since the Black Star Army had discovered Planet Pangurus, they would have the rights to leave their forces behind to mine on the planet.

The sheer size of a Star Field represented countless planets and a huge benefit. To the organizations that did not belong to any civilizations, this was akin to obtaining the rights to mine on many resource rich planets.

Furthermore, they would be able to obtain a bonus reward from the dynasty if they reported a certain number of resource rich planets.

However, the advantage of Planet Pangurus did not lie only in its resources. It would become one of the doors to enter the Garu Star Cluster and thus became a trading station in the future. With this point alone, Planet Pangurus was not merely an ordinary resource rich planet but had huge potential.

Seeing Han Xiao remain silent, Aurora continued. "We detected a large number of living beings on the planet, with the majority of them being wild beasts. We aren't clear how many different species there are, but only one of the species had traces of intelligence and the signs of a civilization."

As Aurora explained, a projection appeared in front of everyone. It was the projection of the living being that Aurora was describing.

This living being was three to four meters tall and looked like a human. It looked like the elf clan in the universe, but there were many subtle differences between the two. It was clad in beast skin for clothes like a caveman.

"According to our observations, this sentient being is a native of the planet and they have reached the level of a tribal civilization," Aurora said. "Their tribes are scattered all around the planet, and they rely on hunting to survive. Our detection fleet has not made contact with them yet."

Han Xiao nodded.

He had long known that Planet Pangurus had a native civilization that called themselves 'Children of the Forest'. In truth, such a title was extremely common in the galaxy, and there were at least a few thousand various native civilizations who call themselves 'Children of the Forest'. Some other complementary names included Children of the Magma, Children of the Mountain, and Children of the Ocean.

In his previous life, the others were used to using the name of the planet as a prefix of the civilizations name. This race was called Pangurus Giant Elves.

"Send out our scouts to make contact with them," Han Xiao said.

When pioneering in a new Star Field, there was a sensitive topic that was publicly acknowledged in the universe—how should they manage their relationship with the natives? There were far too many negative examples in history. Since the advanced civilizations wanted to mine for resources, it was extremely common for them to be treated as invaders and face the retaliation of the natives.

Maintaining biodiversity had always been the rule of the advanced civilizations, and a Universal Civilization like the Crimson Dynasty would not begin a needless massacre just to mine for resources. Thus, Tarrokov had explicitly stated that their priority should be to communicate with the natives, and they should not use violence senselessly.

Under such circumstances, it would be far easier to handle the weaker natives, and the discovery of natives could also earn them reward.

...

On Planet Pangurus, the Green Stream was a dense jungle with large trees that were over fifty meters tall. The leaves of the trees formed an ocean, and it swayed in the wind. The sunlight that managed to shine through the thick sea of leaves became spots of light that swayed together with the leaves.

A clear stream went through the jungle and cut the jungle in two. More than a hundred six- to seven-meter-tall beast skin tents were set up on both sides of the stream. Outside the tents, bunches of golden-red dried fruits were hanging as though they were decorations.

This was one of the tribes of the Pangurus Giant Elf race. There were some climbing up trees to pick fruits, others waving their sticks to chase their reared animals, and some who were holding onto spears and shields in preparation of a hunt.

At the entrance of the tribe, the chief said to the hunters who were about to leave, "Hunters, our tribe doesn't have enough food. You guys must hunt for a little more food this time."

"Haha, just wait for our bountiful return," the captain of the hunter squad said with a loud laugh.

The chief then let out a sigh. "We were attacked by the other tribes half a year ago, and our youths have been severely wounded. We can only rely on you old hunters to hunt for some food. However, all of you are growing older by the day, and I really don't know what we should do in the future."

The hunting captain then patted the shoulders of a youth beside him. "Don't worry, we are training a new batch of youths. Duki is the fastest learner, and he is already able to go hunting together with us. He may be the one to succeed us in the future."

Duki puffed up his chest and had a look of pride on his face.

"What a good lad."

"We shall rely on you in the future."

All the villagers by the side praised him with a respectful tone.

Upon hearing the praise of the villagers, Duki had a face full of confidence.

All of a sudden, his gaze looked through the crowd and arrived at a small campfire. A youth was sitting beside the campfire and looking at him with a face full of envy. It was his good friend, Roseau.

Duki raised his arms and flexed his muscles to Roseau, who was sitting afar, and both of them broke out into laughter.

"Let's go," the hunter captain said before setting off with the other hunters.

Upon seeing that, Duki waved to Roseau and hurriedly followed behind the hunters. The groups of hunters then entered the forest and disappeared before the sights of the crowd.

Roseau looked at his good friend leaving and suddenly let out a sigh.

"Hunter... sigh."

The hunters had the responsibility to hunt and fight, and they were the most highly respected within the tribe. Almost every youth aimed to become a hunter, but Roseau was an exception.

He did not have any interest in hunting and fighting, and he did not have any talent in that regard.

Roseau preferred to do other things that seemed meaningless to others, such as writing or thinking. However, this made plenty of people in the tribe dissatisfied with him and felt as though he was a sloth who did not want to do anything but get protected by others.

However, he also wanted to receive the respect of others like his good friend. Thus, he worked harder to pick fruits, sew clothes, and anything else within his abilities. However, these jobs were usually done by the old, young, and weak, and it was not enough to change the others' impression of him.

Although Roseau cared about how others looked at him, he did not wish to go against his own heart and do something that he was not good at just to change the impression that others had of him. He wished to use another method to contribute to the tribe. However, it seemed as though every youth in the tribe should only have become a hunter as their sole goal.

Right at this moment, a huge gust of wind suddenly blew over.

Whoosh!

Ripples could be seen on the clear stream, and a huge cloud of sand was blown up by the winds.

"What is going on‽" Roseau raised his head and looked up with his eyes wide open in shock.

He had never seen something like this before!

A black, squarish box floated down from the skies and hovered right above their tents, covering their entire tribe with a huge shadow.

The Pangurus Giant Elves in the tribe were all shocked.

"Our god of the forest! What is this thing‽"

"Is it a monster that can fly‽"

"Run!"

Upon witnessing a scene that none of them could understand, many of them became anxious.

All of a sudden, a small hole could be seen on the belly of this black 'beast', and a bunch of strange looking beings covered in metal descended from the sky.

The ten or so warriors who had remained in the tribe charged forward, and their wooden spears struck these beings who descended from the skies.

Kacha kacha!

Their wooden spears snapped upon coming into contact with the surface of the armor.

Taking off their helmets, half of them were the warriors of the army while the other half were players with their IDs above their heads. The majority of the players present were the core members of clubs, such as Hao Tian and Frenzied Sword.

These players had accepted the mission to meet the natives without killing them.

Frenzied Sword pressed onto the galactic translator and tried to speak with sincerity.

"&$#@!&$@..."

Just what are you saying‽ The Pangurus Giant Elves were completely puzzled.

It could not be helped. This was the first time that the Pangurus Giant Elf race had come into contact with the galaxy, and their language was not in the database yet.

"Monsters! Monsters!" Many ladies let out a shriek, and they began picking up stones to hurl at the 'monsters'.

The stones landed on the armor of the warriors and were naturally useless.

All the players looked at each other with helpless looks on their faces. How were they supposed to console the agitated natives if they could not even communicate?

On the other side, the NPC captain raised his rifle up and fired at the forest by the side.

Xiu!

A blue laser shot out and penetrated a few dozen trees, leaving behind a hole.

Following which, a loud explosion could be heard from the forest, and a huge crater was blown up.

This scene frightened all the natives, and a look of disbelief and fear could be seen on their faces after witnessing the carnage of the attack. They all stopped attacking and began trembling with fear.

"Hu..." The captain then looked toward the players. "Brother, did you see that? The best way to deal with natives that you can't communicate with is to scare them."

Just when the atmosphere was tense and the Pangurus Giant Elf race was in fear, Roseau tried his best to maintain his cool and analyze the intentions of the strange creatures before them.

These living beings don't seem to be hostile.

Although I can't understand what they're saying, they seem to be talking just now? Could it be that they have intelligence as well?

This shouldn't be wrong. They also want to communicate with us!

Roseau hesitated for a moment before taking in a deep breath and walking forward.

His actions immediately attracted the attention of both parties, and everyone's attention was focused on him.

After swallowing a mouthful of saliva, Roseau looked at his tribe mates and said, "Everyone don't be afraid. They do not wish to kill us. Please do not provoke them."

He then walked forward to Frenzied Sword and looked down at this 'dwarf' who was only up until his waist. Suppressing his fear, he half knelt so both of their heights were the same before pointing at his mouth and ears, hoping that the other party would understand what he was trying to say.

Frenzied Sword understood what the other party meant and threw a galactic translator over, gesturing to show the other party how to put it on.

Roseau understood what the other party meant and hurriedly put on the translator. The translator immediately read his mind and understood his thoughts.

"Can you understand me now?"

Roseau's eyes lit up and he nodded.

The captain then chuckled. "He knows how to communicate with us. This fellow is pretty smart. He shall be the representative of this tribe."

Chapter 824: Homeland

The sudden descent of the battleship from the sky and the loud explosion that came from the tribe resulted in all the hunters who left not too long ago rushing back. Their eyes were glued on the mountain like flying beasts before them.

All the hunters hurriedly returned to the tribe, and although the members of the tribe were still trembling in fear, there were no casualties. Only then did the anxious hearts of the hunters ease up as they asked around to find out what had happened.

Duki looked around, and his heart immediately sank. He could not find the figure of his good friend Roseau among the crowd. He anxiously went around to ask the different members of his tribe.

"Those individuals said a few words to Roseau before taking him away. Before leaving, he asked us not to be afraid and said that they did not come with ill intentions..."

"In which direction did they go?" Duki was enraged. He could not be bothered with what Roseau had said and only knew that his good friend had been taken away by a bunch of aliens. He could not sit around and do nothing.

The villager pointed in a direction. The members of the army did not return to the spaceship but walked into the forest instead.

Duki raised his weapon and charged in that direction without saying another word. The hunters beside him shouted for him to stop, but he ignored them completely and only thought about saving his friend from the hands of those beasts.

Upon witnessing such a scene, the hunting captain immediately followed behind Duki, afraid that Duki would meet with some danger.

The gigantic elves weaved through the jungle nimbly, and Duki could recognize the footprints on the ground. After running for a while, he finally caught up to the members of the army.

All the players were currently swinging their weapons to clear out a piece of land. They were preparing to form a mini stronghold.

According to their mission requirements and the orders of the army, they were to come meet the natives and set up a stronghold near the tribe for future communication.

"Hmm? A life form is approaching." Frenzied Sword waved his blade to slice down a tree, and his radar detected the presence of Duki.

Duki was currently squatting in the bushes, completely unaware that his whereabouts had already been exposed. He looked around and observed the 'beasts' who were clad in metal. He immediately spotted Roseau, who was currently surrounded, and his face broke out with a smile.

"Ha!" The next moment, Duki pounced into the air and landed not too far away from Roseau.

He then charged forward and aimed his spear at the lower body of the metal beast to launch a one hit ko attack.

Pa!

His wooden spear snapped into two instantly.

The member of the army gently sent out a kick, afraid that he may kill the native and fail the mission.

However, in Duki's eyes, this kick was fast to the point he could not react. He raised his shield to block the kick, and an irresistible force smashed down on his shield.

Boom!

The wooden shield exploded and was shattered into wooden splinters.

Duki's body was sent flying a few meters away, and a sharp pain could be felt in his arms. His chest had a dull aching pain, and he could not help but vomit out a stomach full of gastric juices. He lay flat on the ground and could not get up, staring at the attacker with a look of fear and disbelief.

"Don't kill him! He's my friend!" Roseau cried out and looked toward Duki. "What are you here for‽"

"Cough cough... I am here to save you," Duki said with a weak voice. He was only an ordinary being but had been kicked by a Grade C warrior. The only reason he was alive was because the other party had only used one percent of his strength.

"Sigh... I don't need you to save me. They didn't come with ill intentions and are my friends. Hurry up and leave."

Roseau then helplessly pleaded toward the warriors of the army. In that short period of time, he had already found out about the general situation. Although there were many words that he did not understand, it did not stop him from understanding that the other party did not have any ill intentions.

Upon hearing Roseau persuade him to return, Duki, who was on the ground, raised his head and saw Roseau talking to the unknown beings in some strange language. Roseau was not in any danger at all and did not need any saving.

Roseau received a reply and said with joy, "I have pleaded on your behalf, and they have agreed to let you go. Hurry up and return to the tribe. I am doing fine, and you just need to wait for news from me. Please do not make any rash moves again."

"Let me go..." Duki repeated those words again, and he looked at Roseau with a complicated expression. It was as though he had a new understanding of this good friend of his who had never been welcomed since a young age.

A sense of defeat rose in his heart, and Duki clenched his fists tightly.

At this moment, the hunting captain finally arrived, and he looked at the members of the army warily. Upon seeing Duki lying on the ground, he was extremely surprised. Roseau then hurriedly called out to him and explained the situation. The hunting captain then supported Duki, who had temporarily lost the ability to move, and left.

Roseau looked at their departures and heaved a sigh of relief.

Many different troops landed from the sky and came into contact with the tribes scattered all around the planet. The gigantic battleship that descended from the sky was like the descent of a celestial being to the Pangurus Giant Elves.

The silence in their lives had been disturbed, and all the natives looked at the descending aliens with fear and wariness.

The members of the army set up a stronghold beside the tribes and chose one or a few representatives from each tribe. These representatives were taught how to use the translating device so that the army could communicate with them.

At the same time, Han Xiao did not let the others remain idle and sent out the mining squad to the various resource rich locations. They began to construct a new base and started their mining operations.

Large patches of forests were uprooted and replaced with cold metal.

With a large amount of manpower under his charge, Han Xiao did not need to take action personally. He only needed to command the operation from the flagship and was extremely idle.

"Your Excellency Black Star, you discovered a resource rich planet that has rare materials?"

Senico from the dynasty was overjoyed when he received the piece of news.

At this moment, the majority of the forces were still exploring the first Star Zone, and the majority of the resource rich planets that they had found only contained ordinary resources. There were extremely few planets that had a value of over six billion Enas.

Planet Pangurus was the most valuable planet that they had discovered in the first Star Zone to date.

"Yes, I have already updated the information of the planet in the database. There are natives living on the planet, and my men are keeping in contact with them," Han Xiao said.

Senico thought for a moment before saying, "I see. The mining operation for the planet shall be handed over to you then. I will send a team over to help you."

According to the rules, Han Xiao would be able to temporarily enjoy mining rights to a planet that the Black Star Army discovered.

But if the planet was discovered by the dynasty's forces, the allies of the dynasty would have limited rights over the planet. Thus, the only way to maximize their benefits would be to mine a planet that they discovered. Senico's troops were both his comrades and competition.

After chatting for a while, Han Xiao hung up and opened the interface. A few notifications popped up from the Flickering World Main Storyline Mission. His discovery of a resource rich planet and native civilization awarded him with quite a few Exploration Points.

The players who followed him to Planet Pangurus were the ones who got the greatest rewards among the players.

On the forums, the players who explored the different planets began to show off their own Exploration Points. However, they were extremely envious of the Exploration Points that the players on Planet Pangurus got.

"We can earn the most from following our Army Commander."

"Sigh... what a pity. Most of the slots to follow Black Star have been given to the large guilds. I didn't manage to snatch the remaining slots because I was too ugly."

Although the players went to explore the various planets, they could still communicate with each other through the forums and share information with each other.

Of the players that Han Xiao had taken along with him, a large number of them were players from the various clubs, and many professional players were included.

Closing the interface, Han Xiao looked at the dots of light on the map that indicated the presence of his troops and asked, "How is their contact with the natives going? Did anyone fight back?"

Aurora shook her head and said, "There are more than ten thousand tribes on the planet, and the population of the Pangurus Giant Elf race is about ten million. Our warriors used scare tactics to instill fear in them, and thus, we don't have any injuries temporarily. Er... there seem to be some accidental deaths, but the numbers wouldn't exceed a hundred."

Han Xiao replied with a nod. The natives of this planet were still at the elementary stage, and their population was small. Under a hundred deaths on their first contact was still within an acceptable range.

"Let the ground troops console those tribes and slowly educate them. This is only the first day, and it will be a long process. Tell our men not to be eager for success. Even if the natives fight back, they won't cause much harm to us. Try not to deal with them using violence."

Even if no one fought back currently, it did not mean that no one would in the future. The natives had not understood just what they were facing. One day, some of them would fight back because of their love for the land.

Thankfully, the natives were far too weak, and their retaliation would be meaningless. This was also their saving grace.

Han Xiao knew that there were a few native civilizations who could barely reach the level of a Star System in the Renault Star Cluster, and it was far more difficult to deal with them. If the Bloodshed Land met those civilizations, they would have to suffer for a period.

It would take far too long to educate a bunch of natives. This was a job that would take a few decades or even centuries. Han Xiao naturally would not remain on a single planet for such a long time. He was only setting the foundation and would hand over the job of educating the natives to the dynasty when they arrived. He only needed to leave behind some forces for his mining operation, and he could go and explore another planet.

The representatives of the tribes returned to their tribes with the goodwill of the Black Star Army and conveyed the message that the Black Star Army had no intention of harming them. At the same time, they brought back with them the seeds of a few different crops suitable for the climate of the planet.

With the assurance of the representatives, the Pangurus Giant Elf race was no longer that fearful toward their guests from the sky. After overcoming their fear, they could not help but be curious toward these guests.

Every stronghold beside the tribe had the function of being a school. The school was opened to the natives, and because the translator had gathered enough information about the natives' language, it was possible for them to communicate normally. There were a few bolder natives who had even attempted to study in the strongholds.

The stronghold taught them various different life skills, including farming and craftsmanship. They also gave out seeds and food for free, and some of the natives returned to set up their own plantation after learning from the stronghold.

Through this process, the various tribes understood the identities of these guests who had descended from the sky. They found out about the existence of the Black Star Army and the Crimson Dynasty.

The members of the army passed on some basic knowledge to the natives and the history of the army. The natives were not able to believe that there were such powerful organizations living in the sky, capable of easily traversing through the universe.

Everything had exceeded their knowledge, and the existence of the Black Star Army was like a miracle in their eyes.

In the Clear Stream Tribe, Roseau's life was getting better.

After becoming the representative of the tribe to communicate with the guests from the sky, Roseau continued to learn new knowledge and brought all his knowledge back to the tribe. He was extremely talented in this regard, and the tribe began to learn new things from the Black Star Army, changing their lifestyle.

Roseau suddenly realized that the members of his tribe who had disdained him were finally treating him with respect. In his tribe, his status had exceeded the chief's, and he became the most respected person within the tribe.

The culture of these natives had not been completely formed and did not have any concept of abandoning their own traditions. They were all immediately entranced by the new inflow of knowledge.

The most respected people in the past were the hunters who brought food back to feed the tribe. Now, the most respected ones were those who brought back knowledge from the stronghold. The seeds and food that they brought back allowed the tribe to feed themselves much more easily. The craftsmanship that they had obtained allowed clothes to be more comfortable and the tents to be warmer. Some of them even brought back a free weapon to the tribe called a crossbow. With this weapon, hunting became even easier.

The hunters were the warriors of the tribe, and they had the responsibility of protecting the tribe. However, these hunters were completely helpless before the members of the army, and the tribe gradually lost their reliance on the hunters. Although the hunters still received some form of respect, they were gradually being pushed to the periphery.

Duki looked at Roseau, who was being surrounded by the tribe, and had a complicated feeling in his heart.

This had once been his honor, and although he treated Roseau as his good friend, a sense of superiority had budded in his heart. He had felt that he was protecting Roseau at that time. But now, their statuses had been swapped. Roseau, who had not been popular in the tribe, was now a respected individual, and the young hunter who had been the hope of the tribe was now ignored.

Duki felt more and more depressed.

After talking to the members of his tribe, Roseau saw Duki and said with concern, "How are your injuries?"

Upon hearing Roseau's words of concern, Duki found it to be extremely piercing for some reason.

"... I am fine," he replied coldly and walked away.

Upon seeing Duki's cold response, Roseau was completely puzzled. Duki had been extremely cheerful in the past and became depressed after being beaten up previously. Roseau could not understand why Duki seemed to be avoiding him.

On the other side, Duki walked out of the tribe and sprinted at top speed in the forest to vent his frustrations.

Feeling the wind blowing on his face, his mood immediately became better.

After running for a long while, Duki wanted to go to his own secret base. He had once happened upon a clear lake in the forest, and he liked going there to take a bath occasionally.

However, the scene stunned him upon his arrival.

The lake had disappeared, and in its place was a deep crater. A few metallic towers were beside the crater, and the members of the army were using some strange apparatus to dig up the soil.

"What are you guys doing‽"

Duki flew into a rage. He disliked these guests from the sky and was about to charge forward with his weapon in his hands. All of a sudden, a member of the army blocked him.

"The mining site is up ahead, and it isn't open to outsiders. Please leave immediately."

"Where is the lake over here? Where is the lake‽ What did you guys do‽" Duki roared angrily and wanted to barge his way into the mine.

Bang!

Duki was pushed down by a powerful force and clutched his stomach in pain.

"I am sorry. Please do not obstruct our mining operations. If you have any requests, you can go to the stronghold near your tribe. This place is not open to outsiders."

"What right do you have to stop me? This is obviously a place that I discovered..."

Duki clenched his fists, and his face turned red from anger. At this moment, he saw the guests from the sky digging out a large pile of shiny crystal from the original position of the lake.

Upon witnessing that, he understood that this was their true intention.

Raising his head, he looked around at the trees that were chopped down and replaced with metal. Thinking back to his experiences over the past few days, he could not help but feel a sense of desolation but did not understand where it came from.

However, Duki slowly had a feeling in his heart.

All of those things should have belonged to them...

For the first time, he felt that this forest, land, and planet was their home.

In the flagship, Aurora hesitated for a moment before saying, "Uncle, is it alright for us to do this?"

Han Xiao raised his brows and asked, "What do you want to say?"

Hila, who was by the side, also looked over.

"We are actually invading the homes of the natives..." Aurora said softly.

"I know what you mean." Han Xiao waved his hands. "However, we are educating the natives and bringing knowledge to them. This is different from just invading their homes."

"However..." Aurora plucked up her courage. "This planet is their home, and the natives do not have the ability to protect themselves. They can only watch as their homes are being invaded by us and all their resources taken away. Aren't we being too much of a bully?"

"They should be glad that they do not have the ability to fight back. If not, the fatalities would only increase."

"But..."

"Sigh, you don't need to continue." Han Xiao interrupted Aurora and said helplessly, "Do you think that they have a choice?"

Aurora blinked and said, "Actually, we can avoid the planets with natives and explore other uninhabited planets."

Han Xiao shook his head and looked out of the window at the universe.

"You are far too idealistic. This planet... no, when this Star Field was discovered by the three great civilizations, the destiny of all the living beings changed. They no longer have the right to develop with freedom.

"We can avoid the planets where there are natives, but when the Crimson Dynasty opens up the Flickering World to the outside world, do you think that other wolf-like civilizations will let go of them? They are destined to lose many things and let outsiders share their homeland. This is already a very good ending. The weak will never be able to achieve perfection."

Aurora fell silent, and her heart was in turmoil. Because of her life Esper Ability, she was extremely sensitive toward the lives of others.

She empathized with the natives. Even if the Pangurus Giant Elf race still did not understand the meaning behind what was going on, she could not help but dislike the world where the strong preyed on the weak.

Hila had a calm look on her face. She was different from her sister, and she had always believed that it was a crime to be weak.

Han Xiao paused for a while before continuing. "You don't have to think too much about this. Digging up their resources isn't a classy action, but you have to know that nobody has the obligation to aid another race in their development. The dynasty will only educate the natives because of the rich resources on the planet, and this is a kind of exchange, an exchange that the natives are unable to reject."

In his previous life, after many years of development, Planet Pangurus had become a transit station, and the natives were split into two factions. One faction was educated by the dynasty and turned into galactic residents. They learned various technological skills and began building their own skill trees. Their civilization rapidly skipped past the primal stage. As a result, Planet Pangurus had their own cities, and the inhabitants of the planet could even travel to other planets.

The other faction rejected the education and chose to maintain their original lifestyle. They tried to put up a resistance, but it was completely useless. Thus, they decided not to come into contact with the outside world and lived deep in the mountains. They continued to live with beasts as their companions, and no one bothered them.

The Pangurus Giant Elf race was split in two because of this reason. However, there would always be some from the primal faction leaving the forests and joining the bustling cities.

"Compared to the exploration era, this is pretty good," Feidin said from the side.

Upon hearing that, Han Xiao nodded in agreement.

The exploration of the Flickering World was similar to the exploration era. The only difference being that the three Universal Civilizations had enough strength in the universe to suppress anyone who was dissatisfied. Thus, they had the confidence to employ some warmer means.

In the exploration era, the first thought after discovering another civilization would be to exterminate the other party. War broke out all around; it was a dark time.

Chapter 825: Unexpected Hidden Mission

In front of absolute power, regardless of what the Pangurus Giant Elf race felt or wanted to do, they would not be able to stop the fleet from mining resources.

The efficiency of the galactic mining equipment was extremely high, and resources were rapidly unearthed from all around the planet, filling up the warehouses with batches of raw materials.

During the mining process, some of the exploratory troops discovered even more resources hidden underground, raising the value of the planet even further.

Han Xiao was extremely satisfied as he looked at the report in his hands.

Although the benefits of mining the various resource rich planets in the Shattered Star Ring were not small, he was still in the territory of others, and there was not enough freedom. However, he could do whatever he liked on a resource rich planet that he discovered in the Flickering World. As long as he did not engage in unsustainable mining practices, the dynasty would not interfere.

These materials could be sold back to the dynasty or brought back to the Shattered Star Ring to sell. Han Xiao temporarily stored all of them and got an experienced individual to oversee sales.

After the construction of the stargate, a small troop from the dynasty appeared. After greeting Han Xiao, they also joined in the mining operation and took over the job of educating the natives.

After a simple handing over, Han Xiao called back a portion of his forces.

They had completed the elementary phase of exploring Planet Pangurus, and the only thing left for him to do would be to begin mining. He decided to remain on the planet for another two days and allow the players to enjoy themselves for a bit before setting off to discover another planet.

All the players from the army had discovered their first planet and had a certain understanding of the Flickering World mission. Furthermore, all the players who discovered a resource rich planet could choose to stay behind and mine for resources.

The ordinary players would naturally reject such a proposal. Why would they give up the entire forest for a single tree? However, many of the first-rate guilds actually did the opposite. Because the majority of their core members followed Han Xiao's main fleet, they could not bear to give up the precious resources on Planet Pangurus.

To the guilds, ten birds in the forest could not beat one in their hands. They needed a long-term supply of resources to provide benefits for the guild. As such, many of the guilds left behind a portion of their manpower to mine for resources.

Because the large mining equipment all belonged to the army, these guilds could only purchase a batch of Worker Bee Armor to issue to their members and allow them to mine freely. The resources that they obtained would be the long-term harvest of the guild.

The players had their own methods to harvest rewards, and Han Xiao would not stop them. After all, it was peanuts to him, and it would not be efficient for him to stop the players from freely doing as they wished. As long as he could satisfy the hunger of these guilds, their sense of belonging to the army would only be strengthened.

The various guilds that came from the Constellation Corridor had also managed to groom a batch of players and left some players behind to mine for resources. As the four large guilds saw that, they decided to work together with the other first-rate guilds and make trouble for these outsiders after the main fleet left. As long as the main fleet left, the outsiders would definitely be at their mercy.

In Version 4.0 of Han Xiao's previous life, the various guilds were busy destroying each other's mining locations when they were in the Flickering World. Now that players from the other countries were in the territory of the Chinese guilds, the Chinese guilds definitely would not let them develop in peace.

Because Han Xiao had allowed the players to cross Star Fields ahead of time, the competition between guilds appeared earlier.

...

A large storm was raging over some ocean on Planet Pangurus, and the waves were turbulent.

One of the mining bases was located on the ocean, and it remained steady despite the raging waves. A spherical shield covered the base from the waves, and droplets could be seen on the shield as the waves crashed into it.

At the edge of the base, many warriors could be seen diving down into the ocean with exploratory equipment on their backs. Underneath the base was a Fusion Crystal Vein, and these individuals were diving underwater to investigate the situation of the ocean.

Maple Moon had also accepted this mission. She put on her armor and very quickly dove down a few thousand meters.

Her field of vision was a deep dark blue, and the waters became black as she looked far ahead. The sense of the unknown filled her with fear, and she could only hear her radar beeping, her own breathing, and her heart beating.

This silent frightening atmosphere made Maple Moon shudder, and she wanted to curl up in a ball.

"I should probably return... I won't do this mission at the very most." Maple Moon was terrified in her heart. Although she had already reached Grade B, the attributes of her character would not help prevent her from feeling fear. She had a feeling that she had a slight phobia toward the deep ocean.

Just when she was prepared to swim upward, an alarm rang on her radar.

"Detecting a large living being! The target is currently approaching!"

The waters around her began to surge, and Maple Moon felt as though she could not control her body. She hurriedly activated her stabilizing device, and white light could be seen shooting out from her armor before her body was stabilized.

Before she could even observe her surroundings, her radar displayed a dot of light shooting toward her like a missile.

Maple Moon turned around in a fluster, and a gigantic beast suddenly appeared in her sights. It had countless claws, and its head seemed like a combination of a snake and a dragon. The mouth of the beast was wide open and approaching her rapidly.

Her sights then blacked out, and she was swallowed by the beast.

The beast slowed down after completing its hunt and was about to enjoy its meal. However, its body suddenly began contorting as though it was in immense pain.

The next moment, a brilliant blue light exploded forth from the body of the beast, and the beast exploded into pieces.

Boom!

Fresh, purple blood and meat fragments exploded in the ocean, and Maple Moon's armor was covered in a sticky liquid. It was the mixture of the beast's blood and digestive juices.

Upon witnessing this bloody scene, Maple Moon hurriedly turned off the mature content, and the scene became less gory.

She had previously been shocked by the sudden appearance of the beast and forgotten to fight back. She only managed to snap back to her senses after being swallowed by the beast and used her Grade B strength to easily eliminate it.

Maple Moon put her weapon away and was prepared to swim upward. All of a sudden, her radar detected an abnormal metal object that was inside the body of the beast.

"What did I discover?" Maple Moon's eyes shone. As a player who enjoyed storylines, she was an extremely curious individual, and her instinct told her that she had found something important.

After hesitating for half a second, she stopped swimming upward and flipped through the corpse of the beast while bearing with her disgust.

Dang!

A one-meter metal object was sucked into her palms by the magnetic force given out by her palms.

It looked like some form of a detection device and was extremely tattered. It had signs of being corroded all around it, with many craters on the surface of the device as though it was bitten by living beings.

_____________________

You have discovered an unknown detection device

Unknown Detection Device: This seems to be the wreckage of some galactic detection device. It is badly damaged, but the technology of the device has far exceeded the range of the planet's natives. It seems to be from another civilization and may have some hidden message within it. You can attempt to appraise it or give it to a special NPC in exchange for a reward. Or, you can attempt to repair it and activate the device. This will result in a special outcome. Please consider your choice carefully (Requires the ability of a Mechanic).

You have received 6 Exploration Points.

_____________________

"It really is a hidden mission!"

Maple Moon's eyes lit up, and the fear that she had felt was thrown to the back of her mind. She then toyed around with the unknown detection device with curiosity. She loved digging up such unknown storylines the most.

Without any hesitation, she immediately took the item back to the base. Without removing her armor, she hurriedly appraised the detection device. Her Mechanic ability had reached the prerequisite requirements, and the outcome of her appraisal popped up on the interface.

_____________________

Appraisal complete!

You have obtained [Broken Coordinate Marker]. This item is used to mark a coordinate in space.

Current status: Severe damage, system malfunction and all functions disabled.

_____________________

"This is some high-level tech." Maple Moon was surprised. This item had already reached the level of a Star System. Could this mean that Planet Pangurus had been discovered by some civilization before?

There was also the possibility that this marker had been destroyed in the universe and eventually drawn Planet Pangurus because of gravity. It then landed in the ocean and was swallowed by the oceanic beasts. If not, Planet Pangurus would have been visited by guests a long time ago.

Maple Moon fell into a dilemma. This marker was indeed valuable intelligence, and she would receive a reward if she handed it over to the army.

However, she could not reign in her curiosity, and she wanted to fix this marker to see what the 'special effect' was and what kind of people she would attract.

After hesitating for a moment, Maple Moon gritted her teeth, and her curiosity emerged victorious.

_____________________

You have used [Intermediate Repair] on the [Broken Coordinate Marker]!

Judging... Judgement success.

Your level, INT, Class knowledge, and skills have reached the prerequisite requirements

Repair progress 2%... 14%... 35%...

Repair complete. You have obtained [Barely Fixed Coordinate Marker]!

_____________________

Maple Moon was overjoyed and immediately activated the marker without any hesitation.

Di di...

The marker lit up and began sending out coordinates toward an unknown organization.

_____________________

You have triggered [Coordinate Marker of Unknown Origin]!

Mission Introduction: You have discovered a pretty high-tech coordinate marker on a native planet. You do not know who sent out this marker but chose to activate it. After the coordinates are sent out, it may attract an unknown organization.

Mission Requirements: Come into contact with the unknown organization.

Reward: 3,000,000 Experience, 70 Exploration Point, x1 [Bold Explorer] skill fragment (Requires 2 fragments to be combined)

[Bold Explorer]: Special skill. When exploring an unknown location and appraising an unknown object, you can use this skill to obtain some information. It can be used repeatedly on the same target. Cooldown: 7 days. Every time the skill is used, you will fall into a [Rash] state. -60% LUK, lasts for 14 days.

Remark: As long as you are bold, the universe is your home.

This mission is connected to the Flickering World Main Storyline Mission. You can report the situation to your faction and obtain the aid of an NPC faction (Strongly Recommended).

_____________________

"The reward is a skill fragment? Such a reward is pretty rare. I can seek help from the faction as well. Does this mean that the outcome of activating the marker is extremely severe?" Maple Moon was shocked.

Upon thinking about handing the marker over, the figure of her Army Commander floated up in her head.

...

"You discovered a coordinate marker of an advanced civilization on this planet?"

Looking at the coordinate marker in Maple Moon's hands, Han Xiao could not help but be surprised.

He had thought that Maple Moon was there to learn skills from him, not expecting her to bring him a hidden tool.

Only the dynasty was exploring this region, and this marker could only belong to one of the unknown native civilizations in the Flickering World. According to the technological skills within the marker, the origin of the marker should be a Star System level civilization.

Furthermore, this marker made use of an ordinary thruster technology to travel. Even if it traveled for a few hundred years, its speed would still be limited. This meant that the civilization that sent out this marker should be within the Star System.

However, Han Xiao could not remember any Star System civilizations around the southern region of the Garu Star Cluster in his previous life. The exploratory data of the Crimson Dynasty did not indicate any Star System civilization in the region. He also had not heard of such an incident from the NPCs in his previous life.

Could it be that the civilization that sent out this marker had already been destroyed and only their remains were left? That was a possibility as well.

However, the hidden mission also popped up on Han Xiao's interface when he received the marker, and the mission requirement suggests that the unknown civilization was still around.

In his previous life, the initial exploratory phase of the Flickering World was during the version update period, and the players only managed to piece together information of the initial exploratory phase by finding various records and stories. Could it be that this hidden storyline had not been found by the dynasty in his previous life?

Maple Moon did not know that Han Xiao could also accept the mission and was thinking about how she should explain to Han Xiao that this marker was still useful.

"Let me study this thing for a while," Han Xiao said at this moment. "I may be able to find something."

Upon hearing that, Maple Moon thought that she was handing over the mission object and did not object.

Upon witnessing Maple Moon leave, Han Xiao began to study the marker in his hands with his eyes glowing.

"I never expected to make such a discovery on Planet Pangurus. The ability of the players to find hidden missions is truly reliable." Han Xiao chuckled to himself.

The reward of the hidden mission had truly tempted him. [Bold Explorer] was an appraisal skill and reached the level of appraising the unknown. There were very few players who had such a skill in his previous life. Although it was not useful to combat, it was very useful to dig out hidden storylines.

However, he did not know how to obtain any additional skill fragments.

Although the skill was extremely limited, it was still useful to him. Not to mention anything else, he still did not have any progress on the strange data that EsGod had left behind. Aesop was not able to predict anything either. If he could obtain this skill, he may be able to find some clues.

"It is a pity that it isn't a complete skill but only a skill fragment," Han Xiao said with pity.

Shaking his head, Han Xiao entered the quantum network and began studying the marker. Since the marker also made use of quantum network technology, Han Xiao could use his Virtual Mechanic skill to trace the origin of the item.

The mission required him to come into contact with the unknown organization, and it seemed as though he had to wait for their appearance. However, there was a hidden trick within it.

The Flickering World was not like the explored universe, and there were no laws in place. The native civilizations were still in an era of darkness and did not know of each other's existence. Thus, the moment they discovered that the marker was activated, this would mean war for the civilization who sent it out.

Coming into contact with the marker was akin to being attacked by the other party.

As such, rather than waiting for the other party to find him, Han Xiao would prefer to take the initiative by sending his forces over. Since the mission only required him to come into contact with the other party, it would not matter who took the initiative.

After backtracking the roots of the marker through the quantum network for a while, Han Xiao opened his eyes abruptly. He then opened a star map and pointed at a location a couple of Star Zones away from Planet Pangurus.

"I found you."

Han Xiao's eyes narrowed. He remembered that there was no native civilization at this location in his previous life.

After thinking for a moment, Han Xiao snapped his fingers and Psionic Prime appeared before him.

"Master."

"I have a mission for you." Han Xiao said slowly, "Bring a few Mechanical lives and a mechanical army to find the fellows who sent out this coordinate marker. Subdue them if they attack you."

"Yes master."

Psionic Prime nodded and immediately left the room to organize his troops.

Because it was a few Star Zones away and would be a waste of time for him to go, Han Xiao did not plan to make a personal trip.

His Mechanical lives could now hold their own, and he could transmit his Mechanical Force to the mechanical soldiers not beside him through the [Quantum Infinite Distance Transmission Channel]. Thus, his mechanical army had the ability to set off on a long-distance expedition, and he would still have the combat strength of a Beyond Grade A Super even if it was a few light years away.

This was one of the reasons Beyond Grade A Mechanics were feared in the galaxy! The range of their ability was the most frightening among all the Classes!

Chapter 826: Great Cosmos Corps

At the same time, the location data sent out by the marker had reached a certain desolate planet a few Star Zones away through its quantum link.

A mountainous disc-shaped battleship was parked in a crater. It was completely metal gray colored, and its diameter was more than thirty miles. The material used was an ordinary alloy considered to be the most basic spaceship battleship material in the known universe. This disc-shaped battleship had anti-gravity suspension and highly condensed nuclear thrusters. Its hyperdrive technology was very elementary. If there were galactic residents there, they would know that the technology level of this battleship was somewhere between the level of a Star System civilization and a planet surface civilization.

The only technology worth mentioning was that it had quantum communication technology.

There were a large number of frozen sleeping capsules at the bottom of the cabin where countless ship members were sleeping in. Only a very few were awake and maintaining the functions of the spaceship from the bridge.

Dozens of creatures wearing simple battle suits were busy in front of the control desks. These creatures were rather short, with gray skin and six arms.

This time, an alert suddenly popped up on one of the control desks.

"Beep! Marker 0278 is activated. Location data received."

All the people in the room suddenly turned around and swarmed toward this control desk, speaking among themselves. Then, a tall creature that was clearly of a different species pushed the crowd aside and squeezed to the front of this control desk.

"Out of my way, let me take a look... Hehehe... Have we discovered another new planet?"

This tall creature was clearly their leader. He was close to three meters tall; the others around him were only as tall as his knees. He was wearing full metal armor that made clanking sounds as he walked. He looked absolutely barbaric, even more ferocious than the Beastmen, and did not match the aesthetic of most human shaped beings.

"Great Chieftain Kikiga, we lost contact with this marker a long time ago. Now that it is activated, it means that our marker has been discovered by an unknown intelligent species! They have repaired the marker!" One of the operators was rather nervous.

"Isn't that even better? We can even make them slaves and give them to the Great Emperor. The Great Emperor loves new species!" Kikiga laughed out loud.

"Gre—Great Chieftain, it's not that simple. The target this time is different from the races we have invaded in the past. The fact that they can repair the marker means that their technological level is close to ours. There are only a few in the entire universe who have this kind of technology! The target this time isn't going to be easy to deal with! The reason they repaired the marker might be to look for us."

"What, they dare look for us‽"

Kikiga's expression became fearsome. He said furiously, "What an ignorant bunch. Have they not heard of us, the Great Cosmos Corps? They want to track us? They must have a death wish!"

If Han Xiao was there, he would not be a stranger to the name 'Great Cosmos Corps'. This was a native organization of the Flickering World. It was once a wandering civilization that had lost its mother ship to a disaster. It was originally wandering in the center of the Garu Star Cluster looking for resources to sustain life.

When they started wandering, they searched for planets around them through markers and gradually discovered some undeveloped civilizations. Due to the complete lack of trust and means of communication, they eliminated all the civilizations they had met and robbed a ton of resources and technology. Gradually, they got used to this method of development and turned from a wandering civilization into a galactic pirate organization.

As most of the native civilizations in the Garu Star Cluster were very weak and had no contact with each other, this organization became unstoppable in the central area of the Star Cluster. Through robbing others, they had accumulated a ton of resources and manpower, and there were no longer any civilizations nearby that could match them. Hence, these people thought that they were the kings of this universe and called themselves the Great Cosmos Corps.

It was obvious how arrogant these people were just from this name they gave themselves.

Afterward, the Great Cosmos Corps started to explore toward further areas. Of course, with their technology, they had no way of figuring out the overall structure of the Star Cluster, so they were completely ignorant of what was in the unknown areas and could only slowly explore.

Although they had taken over many planets as their territory, they did not do a complete exploration of this Star System and lacked all kinds of fundamental facilities. They thought that they ruled over this area just because they had some of the planets under their control. Compared to the control the civilizations in the known universe had over their territory, these people were a complete mess.

This was a lawless Star Field that had yet to be explored, which was why special organizations like this had appeared. They had control over an area much larger than Star System civilizations, but they were weaker than the weakest Star System civilizations. Due to the lack of opponents, they felt very good about themselves.

Being 'strong' in their mind was only based on the standard of the natives.

In the previous life, the dynasty left very little information of this organization throughout the exploration of the Garu Star Cluster, and Han Xiao had quite a good laugh from reading it.

However, the 'hidden mission' status was quite misleading when Han Xiao discovered the marker. It made Han Xiao form a preconceived idea that this was from some mysterious civilization. Furthermore, in the dynasty's records in the previous life, it did not mention the Great Cosmos Corps appearing in the south border Star System of the Garu Star Cluster.

The dynasty only had very brief records of the Great Cosmos Corps, as this native organization was way too weak and made the most common and frequent mistake which natives made—being arrogant. There was nothing about this that was worth recording in the eyes of the dynasty. In his previous life, the dynasty carried out their exploration during the version update, and the players did not experience it. By the time they officially entered the Flickering World, the Great Cosmos Corps was long gone, and Han Xiao had only found out about them through the very brief record the dynasty had on them. It did not feel important, so Han Xiao did not have a deep impression of them.

Therefore, he did not think about it for the time being and did not know that this organization was the mission target. Nonetheless, even if he did know, it would not make a difference.

"I—I think it would still be better to report this to the Great Emperor," the operator said while shivering. "We might not be able to win with the forces here..."

"What did you say‽" Kikiga slammed the table with rage. He was testy and prone to anger.

"Don't be angry, Great Chieftain. The Great Emperor has made you responsible for this area. If we make our own move on something this significant, the Great Emperor will not be happy about it!"

Realizing that the Great Emperor might be angered by this, Kikiga shivered, and his rage disappeared. He then said with hesitation, "Then... let's report this to the Great Emperor."

The others hastily contacted the Great Emperor and held their breath. Very soon, the projection of a person appeared on the screen.

The person on the screen was a humanoid in dark purple armor and a bright-red half-shoulder cape, only showing his head. He had messy black long hair and pale skin, and the metal mask on the bottom half of his face covered his appearance. His eyes were filled with coldness. Thick, muscular, and enormous tentacles extended from behind him, covered in some armor as well, like multiple mechanical tails surrounding this person.

He sat on a metal throne of a battleship. Behind him was a metal wall with the logo of the Great Cosmos Corps and the skulls of many different beasts. This person was the leader of the Great Cosmos Corps, Atimo, who also called himself the Great Emperor of the Universe.

Kikiga immediately stood straight as he saw this person.

Atimo raised his eyelids and said with a cold tone, "You'd better have a reason for disturbing me."

Kikiga shivered. He had become one of the chieftains because of his exceptional combat capability. Despite being bad-tempered, he was afraid of Atimo from the bottom of his heart. Under the constant reminder of the operators, he finally completed reporting what had just happened and cautiously waited for a response.

"So, you were discovered by an unknown force with advanced technology?"

"Yes, what should we do?"

"Invade their planet, rob their technology, snatch their resources, and eliminate and enslave them," Atimo said with the same cold tone. "Do I still need to teach you these things?"

"Un—Understood." Kikiga hastily nodded.

After the communication ended, Kikiga breathed a sigh of relief. He then stared at the operators around him with rage and loudly yelled, "You heard it! The Great Emperor has told us to eliminate the enemies. Wake up all those who are asleep; we have a war to fight!"

Two days passed in a flash. Han Xiao's main fleet officially departed and left Planet Pangurus, only leaving some behind to mine the resources.

The next planet that Han Xiao was planning to personally explore was an average resource planet in the first Star Zone of the border Star System.

The famous planets in his memories were spread out in many areas. Compared to the entire Star Cluster, the first Star Zone was tiny. Other than Planet Pangurus, he had a rough image of about ten or so planets in the Star Zone, all of which he had personally visited before. Some of them were resource planets that he had visited to rob resources from other guilds, while others were functional planets such as stargate stations and supply stations of sorts.

The Black Star Army exploration team and the Senico exploration team's millions of spaceships split up. According to the current progress, it would take about seventeen to eighteen days to finish exploring all the planets in the first Star Zone. This meant that it would take about half a year to finish exploring this Star System, and most of that time would be spent on travelling.

After all, not every planet had natives, and it was easy to explore normal planets.

As for the Special Task Force, as they would be travelling nonstop in high-speed spaceships, they would be able to build a long distance stargate route in just four months. In this time, Han Xiao felt that he should be able to visit all the planets that he had a memory of in this Star System.

On the other side, a few battleships deviated from the others, carrying the mechanical troops that Han Xiao dispatched, and headed to the location of Kikiga and the others.

Inside the spaceship, rows of mechanical soldiers were on standby under Sparta's control. They were completely still.

Inside the cabin, however, there was a group that was completely different from the lifeless mechanical soldiers—they were the mechanical lives that Han Xiao had created.

"Guys, this is the first time the master has sent us out to a battle. We must not disappoint our master."

In the wide room, dozens of mechanical lives were either seated or standing, looking at Psionic Prime, who was speaking with a formal tone.

As soon as his sentence ended, a silver mechanical life who was leaning back on the sofa spoke with a simulated impatient tone.

"Humph, we're all first-generation children of the master. You were just born the earliest, yet you think of yourself as our leader?"

There were thousands of first-generation mechanical lives that Han Xiao created personally. Psionic Prime was their leader, but some mechanical lives were not satisfied with that.

Mechanical Lives had emotion modules. Due to different original models, they would shapeshift into a body shape of their own preference through nanotechnology.

"According to the bloodline relationship of flesh beings, I'm your older brother, Silver Flash," Psionic Prime said.

The mechanical life who spoke was called Silver Flash. He had always been envious of how Psionic Prime would always be on Han Xiao's side. Psionic Prime was just a Hovering Fissionist; the master's favorite should be him—a thick, long, and manly Planetary Obliteration Cannon!

"Fight! Fight! The winner gets to be the older brother!" A black-red mechanical life who was clearly shorter than everyone else jumped left and right and cheered. Its original model was a dark energy hovering artillery. Its name was Scarlet Flame.

"Stop messing around." Psionic Prime waved.

"No!" Silver Flash suddenly pounced at Psionic Prime, shattering the sofa below him.

Psionic Prime instantly split up from his human shape into multiple hovering guards, causing Silver Flash to go right through him and miss.

Pa!

With one hand pressed on the ground, Silver Flash's body spun as he launched a kick toward Psionic Prime. He was a Planetary Obliteration Cannon, so he did not dare fire inside the ship and could only use close-range combat techniques.

Two hovering guards suddenly assembled and turned into a palm, grabbing Silver Flash's leg. Then, Psionic Prime returned to his human form and threw Silver Flash right over his shoulder.

Bang!

The bulky mechanical body crashed onto the metal ground and made a dent.

"Still want to play?" Psionic Prime held tight onto Silver Flash's hand and emitted a restraining force field from his palm, preventing Silver Flash from escaping by nano-shapeshifting.

Silver Flash fell onto the ground. One of his legs was caught, and the other kept kicking at Psionic Prime like a child fighting, but his attacks were all dodged by Psionic Prime.

As the two mechanical lives fought, the room became a mess. The mechanical lives around quickly backed off and gave them space.

Mechanical lives had been sparring all the time inside Han Xiao's secondary dimension army base, so the others were all used to it.

"Are you guys not properly oiled? Come on!" Scarlet Flame cheered from the side.

"Don't destroy the spaceship! Go to the combat room if you want to fight!" a ranger mechanical life yelled.

At this time, all the mechanical lives' movement suddenly stopped. Sparta's cold voice appeared out of nowhere.

"The master has finally given you guys missions, and you're making such a mess‽ All of you, reflect on yourselves!"

Mechanical lives had free will, but Han Xiao's artificial intelligence had a higher control priority in their fundamental logic that was only lower than Han Xiao.

Usually, Han Xiao would let the mechanical lives move freely to maximize their growth. However, Sparta did not want to let these mechanical lives keep making a mess, so he took away the control these mechanical lives had of their body and made them walk back to the cabin and stand still.

However, although these mechanical lives could not control their bodies, their minds were still active, and they were still arguing through their network link.

"If this was an open area, you'd already have become a pile of trash!" Silver Flash yelled.

Psionic Prime just chuckled. "Hehe."

"It's all your fault," the ranger said. "None of us can move now!"

"Silver Flash... when we're done with the mission, I'm going to dismantle you and send you back to the master to be rebuilt!" Oathkeeper growled.

"You think I'm afraid of you? Let me fire at you if you have the guts! Let's see if you can even be rebuilt!"

Chapter 827: Black Star Army? Never Heard of It

After Han Xiao's fleet left Planet Pangurus, the guild players who stayed behind could not wait to make their moves.

The four largest Chinese guilds pretended not to be involved while secretly gathering the members of the other guilds who had stayed behind, including the guilds of the Thunderstorm club, Fanatics club, Rivervale club, and many more.

The number of members in these guilds who had stayed behind was around sixty to seventy each; they were mostly studio players who took on manual labor jobs from guilds and charged them a fee. They were more organized compared to normal guild players, who were much larger in terms of numbers.

Hundreds of players gathered and discussed the plan.

"The Russians and Australians have insufficient manpower. They left fewer than twenty people per club. There're a total of about a hundred people on each side."

"However, they're not splitting up, and the hundreds of them are mining together."

Although the Russians and Australians had established an agreement with the four largest Chinese clubs, the guild players who had stayed behind all stayed together to do mining. The Russians were led by the Power and Glory guild, and the Australians were led by the Kangaroo Boxing guild. They each gathered in one place of their own and had close to about a hundred people on each side, which was close to the number of people the top tier Chinese guilds had. It seemed that this was safer and would prevent them from being attacked.

However, never would they have thought that the Chinese top tier guilds would work together against them.

The Chinese guilds discussed for a while and decided with a plan. They had the absolute upper hand in terms of number, so they decided to split into two groups and attack the Russians and the Australians' resource points. The grouping was decided very soon, and they started the operation.

...

At the Kangaroo Boxing Guild's resource point, dozens of Australian players were hard at work in the mines, wearing the Worker Bee Armor, placing the resources into their armor, and transporting them back to the mini guild warehouse on the ground time after time.

There were many warehouses that belonged to the various Australian guilds, and there were patrolling studio players around. Although they moved as a group for safety, this did not mean that they were sharing resources. These warehouses were bought by the various guilds from the army using their own funds, and they were quite expensive. They were equivalent to their stronghold at the resource point.

At this time, groups of well-equipped first-tier guild players appeared in the patrolling players' sights and were charging right toward them from afar.

"Gather immediately! Our resource point is being attacked!"

These Australian club guilds hastily summoned those who were mining for resources, but it was too late. The close to three hundred first-tier guild players rushed right into this resource point.

The Australian players who rushed back from the mines clashed with those players instantly.

A scrimmage erupted in the blink of an eye!

Boom boom boom!

Pugilists blasted the backlines with energy flames, Espers threw out all sorts of colorful energy of different abilities, Mages constantly channeled spells, and Psychics nonstop used AOE psychic attacks...

The Mechanics made the greatest impact.

Version 3.0 was the version where Mechanics shone very brightly. This was because the Mechanic players would finally be able to learn the ability that would completely evolve their combat method in this version—Compression Technology.

Compressed orbs expanded on the battlefield one after another, turning into artilleries, mini mechanical soldiers, mechanical traps, and all kinds of equipment.

Be it financial power, combat capability, or manpower, the first-tier Chinese guilds had the complete upper hand and very quickly thrashed the Australian players. While they sent some people to the revive point to keep attacking, they started to attack the guild warehouses of the Australians and very soon destroyed all of them. The resources that the Australians had been collecting all this time were now robbed as loot.

The resource point became a mess. After they completely depleted the Australian players of their daily maximum revive count, the first-tier Chinese guild players retreated with the loot.

About a hundred souls hovered above the revive point and watched them leave with rage in their eyes.

Meanwhile, the Russians' resource point was treated equally.

...

"Our resource points were destroyed‽"

Inside a certain transport ship of the main fleet, Vodka was shocked to receive this news from the member who had stayed behind.

After hearing that the first-tier Chinese guilds were the ones who did this, he was furious. He immediately sent messages to the guild presidents of Long Sky and Dynasty and questioned them, "Why did you attack our resource point‽"

Jade Green Sky pretended to be confused. "What are you talking about? When did we do such a thing? You'd better have proof, or I'm suing you for slander."

"Just moments ago, the resource point we left on the planet was destroyed by your Chinese guilds members. The players were spawn-camped and finished their revive counts. They won't be able to revive in the next six in-game days. Why did those Chinese guild members attack us‽"

"Well, ask them, not like we're the ones who did it." Jade Green Sky held back his laughter.

"We buy equipment from you guys, and in exchange, you promised to provide protection to us," Vodka said furiously. "You've violated our agreement!"

Jade Green Sky knew exactly what tricks these foreign guilds had been pulling—these guilds bought equipment from them on the surface but secretly worked together with other Chinese players to secretly enjoy the full ten-percent discount.

Morning Snow Twilight Frost smiled faintly. "We did not know about this in advance. After all, those first-tier guilds have their own thoughts too. They're not working under us. We'll ask them about it. Don't worry, I'll try to convince these guilds."

"That'd be for the best." Vodka nodded.

As Vodka ended the communication, he was extremely displeased. These first-tier guilds working together against them was connected to the four largest Chinese clubs no matter how he looked at it. This might happen again in the future.

He contacted the captain of the people who stayed behind and said, "After you revive, I'll send some funds to you guys for you to buy some alarm devices in the army, such as automatic artilleries, traps, and laser formations. Deploy these around the new resource point, buy as many as possible, don't be afraid to spend... By the way, give up on your current location and look for a harsher location to mine resources."

On the other side, Morning Snow Twilight Frost and Jade Green Sky were discussing the matter as well.

"This attack will make them cautious and cause them to spend more money on unnecessary defense measures. These first-tier guilds never planned to attack them frequently, so we can just say that this is because we convinced these guilds and kept our promise. When these people build a new resource point and have recovered for some time, we shall organize an attack again. By then, there will be a new batch of resources stored in their warehouses, and it will all be robbed. As this goes on, the profit they gain from their resource points will be extremely limited. All we have to do is force them to turn this into a large guild war so that we can completely obliterate their guilds' core members with our numerical advantage."

"Cunning as always." Jade Green Sky gave him a thumbs up.

Morning Snow Twilight Frost shook his head. "Sadly, they did not send their professional players here, or we would have been able to help the club eliminate some opponents."

Pro players were the pillars of clubs, so clubs took the safety of the pro players very seriously. Of course, they did not dare send the character of their pro players to someone else's territory. One of the reasons the Chinese clubs were targeting the foreign guilds was also to protect their own pro players—if the foreign guilds built a stable foundation in their own territory, the chance of them causing the Chinese pro players trouble would not be negligible at all.

The others could come here from another Star Field, but they could not go to another Star Field, so the Chinese guilds were actually on the more passive side. This was why they had decided to work together to compete with the foreign guilds and guard their profit.

...

A few days later in another Star Zone, the Great Cosmos Corps fleet led by Kikiga was slowly heading toward the location of the marker. Other than the main ship, which was dozens of miles long, there were thirty or so guard battleships. All the warriors who were awoken were training. There were around a million people.

Inside the main ship, Kikiga rubbed his hands with anticipation—he loved plundering and was looking forward to the war.

"How long till we arrive at the marker's location?" Kikiga asked this question many times every single day.

"Chieftain, the location of the marker has been moving for the past few days. I think that this is the enemy's trick to confuse us, so we're now heading toward the location where the marker was activated first. It's not very far away," the team leader of the operators said with resignation. He had to repeat this many times every day.

"The faster the better. I can't wait," Kikiga said with a wild tone.

This time, one of the operators yelled, "Chieftain, three unknown targets are approaching us!"

"It's not meteoroids, right?" Kikiga was shocked.

In his mind, very few could travel in the universe like them, so his first thought was to assume that they were meteoroids.

"It doesn't look like it. They're flying toward us! Chieftain, I request to enter alert status!"

"Overreacting," Kikiga murmured and waved. "Alert then."

The fleet activated its various weapons very quickly and waited with focus.

Not long after, the three spaceships with Psionic Prime and the others on them slowly stopped before Kikiga and their fleet.

"Real spaceships?" Kikiga was shocked.

The operator quickly said, "Like I suspected, they can indeed track our marker and have very advanced technology. They can travel in the universe, too."

Kikiga sized the three spaceships up for a while before suddenly laughing.

"What are you afraid of? Look at those three spaceships. How strong can they be when they're so small?"

Indeed, the spaceships that Psionic Prime and the others were in looked tiny compared to the main ship of Kikiga's fleet.

To Kikiga, the size of spaceships was directly proportionate to the spaceships' power.

"Also, look, they only have three spaceships. We have more than ten times that number. We will be able to beat them with ease. What are you guys panicking for? Embarrassing." Kikiga shook his head.

The rest thought that what Kikiga said made sense and felt relieved.

"Chieftain, what should we do now?"

"Looking at their spaceship, it's clear they're from a small civilization that has just started to travel the universe and don't know what fear is," Kikiga replied, "which is why they dared track our signal. Humph, as seniors, we have to teach them a lesson and make them understand the taste of fear."

This time, an operator smiled and said, "Chieftain, they've sent us a message and said that they want to communicate with us."

Hearing this, everyone laughed and agreed with Kikiga—only a civilization that had just started exploring the universe would be this naive.

"What did they say?"

"Let me see... They said that they belong to the Black Star Army and told us to immediately deactivate our weapons and not resist..." This person burst into laughter before he finished the sentence.

As if the others were infected by him, almost everyone on the bridge burst into laughter. The room's atmosphere was filled with joy.

"Hahaha..." Kikiga could not stop laughing. "Quick, reply to them."

"What do we say?"

"Ask them if they have heard of us, the Great Cosmos Corps. Hahaha..." Kikiga was almost tearing up from laughing.

The Black Star Army? What sh*t is that? Never even heard of it, yet they think they're famous?

Don't they know that the Great Cosmos Corps is the ruler of the universe? Wanting us to stop resisting and give up... I've never heard such a funny joke.

Kikiga gasped for air and suppressed his laughter. "These arrogant natives really are the fountain of joy, always makes me laugh..."

Before he could finish, he almost burst out laughing again.

"Chieftain, should we attack?"

"Hmm, eliminate them... no, don't kill them. Capture them and give them to the Great Emperor. The Great Emperor will definitely think these guys are funny, too." Kikiga guffawed.

As everyone was laughing nonstop, the team captain of the operators felt his heart skip a beat as he noticed something that they had previously overlooked.

When they came into contact with natives in the past, there was no way to communicate with them as they had different languages.

These natives, despite meeting us for the first time... why do they know our language? Why are they able to communicate with us‽

He trembled. As he was about to report this abnormality, those three spaceships changed.

The cabin of those three spaceships opened, and black machinery gushed out. Suddenly, blue-gold lightning appeared out of nowhere and landed on every machine, causing a blinding surge of light.

"What are those?"

The smile on the faces of Kikiga and the others disappeared as they watched this with confusion.

The next moment, a silver beam of light instantly penetrated the shield of their main ship and its body, leaving a huge hole!

The 'tough' spaceship armor could not have been more fragile in the face of this energy beam!

Everyone was stunned. Before they could react, the violent trembling shook them onto the ground.

The deafening alarm rang instantly, and the lights inside the spaceship all turned red.

Woo!

"Alert! Alert! Shield broken, hull damage increasing, 7.8%... 8.6%... 10.3%... Please take measures as soon as possible! Please take measures as soon as possible!"

With one attack, the main ship's defense had been completely obliterated.

Kikiga did not even climb up. He sat on the ground, his eyes filled with disbelief, his face covered in despair.

What... just happened‽

Chapter 828: Player Military Operation

The battle between more than thirty battleships built with Star System grade technology and the mechanical lives that were receiving Han Xiao's Mechanical Force bonuses through [Quantum Infinite Distance Transmission Channel] ended with zero suspense.

The battle ended instantly—this Great Cosmos Corps fleet was wiped out without being able to fight back at all. The main ship became a firework in the universe.

Before the main ship exploded, having realized he was facing doom, Kikiga wanted to escape in an escape pod. However, the escape pod was blasted midway by Scarlet Flame. He initially wanted to flee from the enemies with his extraordinary combat capability but was completely destroyed by Psionic Prime in one kick and was captured.

Psionic Prime and the others obeyed the order with full loyalty, capturing more than a dozen upper echelons. As for the rest of the Great Cosmos Corps warriors, they became ash together with their spaceships.

Inside the spaceship, Kikiga and the group of operators were tied up by electromagnetic chains and lying on the ground. The shadow of the mechanical lives shrouded them and made them so nervous that they could hardly breath.

They looked at the tall and large mechanical lives around them and shivered. Mechanical Lives had no expressions, so they could not tell what these metal beings were thinking. They had no idea what would happen to them next.

Kikiga's face was stiff; he was still in disbelief.

His powerful fleet had been eliminated by these strange creatures so easily!

Plus, he was no match for these monsters at all.

The Great Cosmos Corps respected the strong. Some of its members were Supers. However, these people did not have any properly classified Super knowledge, so every Super was extremely rare in the Great Cosmos Corps and took on important positions. Kikiga, being one of them, had become the Chieftain of a division because of his combat capability.

He initially had a lot of confidence in his own strength, but Psionic Prime had completely evaporated that confidence and made him start doubting the meaning of life.

What monsters were those metal beings? He had never seen such lives throughout the years he had been robbing.

"W-what the hell are you‽" Kikiga was shivering.

"I'm Psionic Prime, the leader of the Black Star Army's machinery troops." Psionic Prime spoke with his completely emotionless electronic voice.

"Black Star Army..." This was the second time that Kikiga had heard this name today.

He thought they were just a bunch of natives when he heard it for the first time. Now, however, that belittlement disappeared together with his fleet, leaving him only panic and fear.

Kikiga swallowed his saliva. What was this 'Black Star Army'? How could they possibly be this strong? He had never heard of the name of this organization and felt that it was extremely mysterious.

Seeing that Kikiga was stunned and filled with terror, Psionic Prime tilted his head, raised his finger, and emitted a beam, forming a hologram in front of everyone.

On the screen, images and text descriptions displayed the history of the Black Star Army.

Phillip had invaded the enemy's spaceship long before the battle even started. The language of the Great Cosmos Corps had been recorded into the database beforehand, which was what allowed them to communicate in the first place. Other than language, the information stored in this fleet had also been duplicated. Their virtual technology was basically as good as non-existent in front of Phillip; he could do whatever he wanted.

"This is..." As the curtain began to unfold on the Black Star Army, Kikiga and the others' eyes and mouths were opened wide. The origin of the Black Star Army had shattered their world view.

Godora, DarkStar, Bloodshed Land, Purple Crystal Civilization, the Crimson Dynasty... There're so many organizations in the universe? Why have we never heard of them‽

Beyond Grade A? In Kikiga's impression, Atimo was the strongest person in this entire universe. He could not even imagine how anyone could possess strength far greater than Atimo.

Kikiga had initially fantasized that Atimo would lead his army and avenge them. However, having just seen the tip of the iceberg of the Black Star Army, he only had one thought toward Atimo.

Please don't come!

...

"They've captured them?"

Han Xiao received Psionic Prime's message while commanding his fleet in exploring another resource planet; he immediately browsed through the data copied by Phillip in the database.

After looking through, Han Xiao was surprised.

That's what I thought. There is indeed no hidden Star System civilization in this area. So, it turns out that it's those idiots from the Great Cosmos Corps. Apparently, they have a division here...

Han Xiao giggled in his mind.

So, the goal of this hidden mission is them. They did not meet the dynasty this time and met me instead... They're still quite unlucky.

The Great Cosmos Corps' territory was mainly located at the center of the Garu Star Cluster. According to the normal exploration progress, it would take a few years before anyone would arrive at that location. However, Han Xiao had now met them in advance.

After eliminating one of their fleets, they would definitely not let this end easily. Although these people would not be able to cause any problems for him or the dynasty, it was not his style to leave them be.

Han Xiao walked back and forth pondering with hands behind his back. Suddenly, his eyes sparkled.

That's right, these people have robbed many planets. They definitely have the data of those planets. Even if they've destroyed some of those planets, there will still be ruins that give Exploration Points. This intel is very valuable to the dynasty and can be considered an achievement.

If he obtained this information, the total Exploration Points of his main storyline mission would grow quite a lot, most likely an entire grade. Plus, this would be considered quite an achievement, and the dynasty would reward him for it, making his exploration progress look more successful than the Bloodshed Land's.

"This is quite a good opportunity." Although the Great Cosmos Corps was weak, the intelligence they had was useful.

He turned his communicator on and contacted the chief commander, Tarrokov, through Senico.

"Black Star, what's this about?" Tarrokov was a little shocked. Normal matters could all be discussed with Senico, yet Han Xiao had gone straight to him. Could he have met some kind of special situation?

"Chief commander, I have made a discovery," Han Xiao said slowly. "A few days ago, my army warriors discovered a damaged marker on Planet Pangurus..."

He roughly explained the situation and then emphasized, "According to the data, this organization robs others for a living and has been active in the center area of the Garu Star Cluster. They seem to have quite a large territory. The way I see it, the planetary information in their hands will be very useful to our exploration."

"I see..." Tarrokov contemplated a while before nodding. "If you're not mistaken, this will indeed give us a lot of information on multiple planets at once. This is quite a significant achievement. Did you skip Senico and came to me because you wanted to ask me to allow you to start a war?"

Han Xiao did not deny it.

In the laws stated by the dynasty, they had to take the peaceful approach when contacting the natives. In order to start a war with a Star System level native force, the dynasty had to permit it. If anyone eliminated natives for no reason, the dynasty would be displeased. After all, the Star Field belonged to the dynasty; its allies were just people helping in the mining process.

Therefore, the chief commander's approval was needed to eliminate the Great Cosmos Corps; only then would there be no negative effects.

Han Xiao did not feel any guilt over eliminating the Great Cosmos Corps. These people robbed others for a living and had enslaved dozens of native races. They were basically galactic pirates.

Tarrokov considered it for a while before speaking in a deep voice. "I will write an order and give it to the Black Star Army, representing that what you guys are doing is on my orders. I shall leave the task of gathering information to you. There's no need to spare these people."

"Okay." Han Xiao nodded.

"I will report the fact that the Black Star Army was the one that discovered this piece of intelligence. This is your achievement, so the merit naturally belongs to you." Tarrokov smiled and spoke in a friendly way.

After a pause, Tarrokov suddenly changed the topic and said with a meaningful tone, "Renault is in the middle of the three Star Clusters that will be explored in the first stage. Its geographical location is superior and looks like the richest. Therefore, the upper echelons of the dynasty are paying the most attention to the development of the Renault Star Cluster."

Why mention another Star Cluster suddenly? Isn't Renault the Bloodshed Land's exploration area? Han Xiao was stunned for a moment.

"As for the Garu Star Cluster," Tarrokov continued, "due to it having rather a large number of desolate universe belts, the upper echelons of the dynasty have the lowest expectations for it. This is also why fewer people chose to explore the Garu Star Cluster. However, if the exploration of Garu goes very well, it will be a pleasant surprise to the dynasty."

Han Xiao figured out what Tarrokov was trying to convey. Tarrokov was leaking a tiny bit of internal information of the dynasty and giving him a reminder.

The dynasty paid the most attention to Renault and had the highest expectations for it, which meant that the Bloodshed Land had to achieve more to meet their expectations. However, it would be a pleasant surprise as long as his exploration of Garu was not too horrible, so earning merit for him would be comparatively easier. There were both pros and cons.

Seeing that Han Xiao was pondering, Tarrokov smiled and moved away from this topic. Other than wanting to build a good relationship with Han Xiao, he reminded Han Xiao also to encourage the Black Star Army—this was one of his jobs as the chief commander.

After chatting casually for a while, they ended the communication. This time, a notification popped up on Han Xiao's interface.

[Coordinate Marker of Unknown Origin] complete!

You have received 3,000,000 EXP and 70 Individual Exploration Points.

You have received 1 [Bold Explorer] Ability Shard. 2 Shards are needed to fuse.

"With one shard, there's at least a start. I'll have to try to obtain the second shard."

Han Xiao was joyous. This was a very pleasant surprise. Maple Moon was really quite lucky.

This time, more notifications popped up on the interface.

You have triggered Faction Mission [Wipe Out the Great Cosmos Corps]!

Mission Introduction: The Great Cosmos Corps is a pillaging organization in the Garu Star Cluster, evil and lawless. I hereby request the Black Star Army to eliminate this organization—Dynasty Exploration Army Chief Commander Tarrokov.

Tip: This is a sub-mission of the [Flickering World]. Exploration Points will be rewarded.

Tip: This is a faction series mission. You can complete the following requirements during this mission.

Eliminate Enemies I: Kill 10 normal Great Cosmos Corps warriors. Rewards: 750,000 EXP and 3 Exploration Points.

Eliminate Enemies II: Kill 10 elite Great Cosmos Corps warriors. Rewards: 1,500,000 EXP and 6 Exploration Points.

Eliminate Enemies III: Kill 10 spaceship operators. Rewards: 2,000,000 EXP and 9 Exploration Points.

Destroy Ships I: Destroy 1 enemy guard battleship. Rewards: 3,600,000 EXP and 12 Exploration Points.

...

King Before Men I: Kill 1 high level combatant. Reward: 5,500,000 EXP and 25 Exploration Points.

King Before Men II: Kill 1 chieftain. Reward: 7,000,000 EXP and 30 Exploration Points.

King Before Men III: Kill 'Great Emperor' Atimo. Reward: 22,000,000 EXP and 60 Exploration Points.

When the mission ends, based on the number of targets completed, the rating and bonus rewards will be given.

Han Xiao figured that this Faction Mission was given to the entire Black Star Army, which meant that the other army players would be able to accept it as well.

Han Xiao was initially planning to send out his machinery troops to eliminate the Great Cosmos Corps, but he changed his mind.

Since the players were able to accept this mission, he would leave it to the players. Spending a little bit more time was not an issue. This Great Cosmos Corps was not especially powerful, so it was suitable for the players to deal with.

The average strength of the players had been gradually growing, so he planned to let just the players eliminate the Great Cosmos Corps. Other than providing spaceships, he was not planning to let any NPC take part in this operation.

This would be the first military operation with only players!

This way, the players would have a better experience in exploring the Flickering World. After all, compared to purely exploring, most players preferred fighting.

The Great Cosmos Corps people were all walking experience, so Han Xiao basically considered letting the players eliminate them as watering his leeks. It was still the early stage of Version 3.0, so there were no max level players yet.

Furthermore, after a war, the players would have to replenish their ammunition and repair their equipment, which would all cost money.

Han Xiao never ignored the ammunition business of the army, and he was going to make a fortune from this war.

I'll have to make the enemies gather and attack first so that it'll take less time...

Han Xiao contacted Phillip and spoke a few words to Psionic Prime.

...

Central area of the Garu Star Cluster, Great Cosmos Corps headquarters.

A deputy hastily came before Atimo's throne and said with a shivering voice, "Gr—Great Emperor, we've lost contact with Chieftain Kikiga's team!"

A glow of coldness flashed past Atimo's eyes. He said with a low voice, "What happened?"

"They were planning to invade the location of the marker but met the enemy's team midway and were eliminated..." this deputy said cautiously. "Those enemies call themselves the Black Star Army, and they've sent a message."

"Black Star Army..." Atimo frowned. "What did they say?"

The deputy played this message on the screen while shivering.

Psionic Prime appeared on the screen, and Kikiga was trembling on the ground beside his feet.

"I'm the leader of the mechanical army of the Black Star Army, Psionic Prime. Listen carefully, people of the Great Cosmos Corps. The Black Star Army will seize all your territory, kill all your warriors, and take away your everything. Tell your leader, Atimo, our army commander will drink wine from his skull."

The moment the sentence ended, Psionic Prime's arm turned into a blade flickering with psionic energy and slashed through Kikiga's neck.

Puchi!

Blood gushed out, Kikiga's head rolled on the floor, and his headless body fell on to the ground, still shivering.

Psionic Prime said with an emotionless tone, "Get ready for war!"

Then, the screen turned black, and the message came to an end.

Atimo was initially watching this recording with an indifferent face, but when Kikiga's head was chopped off right before his eyes, his eyes flickered a little.

"Great Emperor, this is a provocation... What should we do?"

Atimo stood up slowly.

"Gather all the fleets, combatants, and chieftains..." Atimo's tone was cold. "I will lead the charge this time!

"If they want war, I shall give them war!"

...

[Coordinate Marker of Unknown Origin] complete!

Maple Moon was farming dungeons with Bun-Hit-Dog and others and was fighting a boss when the mission completion notification suddenly popped up on her interface. She was shocked, and her movements stiffened for a moment.

"It's only been a few days, and the mission is already completed. I've not even done anything yet!"

Maple Moon was shocked.

She had turned over the marker to the army as suggested by the mission. It was clear that this was thanks to the faction.

Giving things to the army was indeed the right choice.

"Don't just stand there. Control the field!" Bun-Hit-Dog was being thrown around by the boss as he yelled.

Maple Moon completely ignored him, deep in thought.

She had been thinking for the past few days. The requirement of this mission was just to make contact with the unknown force, which meant that there would definitely be more to it. She immediately opened the faction mission list.

As she expected, there were indeed more missions and even large side missions distributed by the dynasty!

"Great Cosmos Corps, such a lame name... it's a pillaging organization. The mission requirement is to eliminate this organization. It seems like it's going to be a group mission. There will definitely be a lot of people participating."

Maple Moon pondered.

"He... lp... me..." The boss pressed Bun-Hit-Dog onto the ground and punched his face again and again. Bun-Hit-Dog could only yell out one syllable at a time during the gap of the punches. His call for help had a constant rhythm.

Finally, as his last bit of health disappeared, Bun-Hit-Dog turned into a white light and died.

Maple Moon finally regained her focus and looked up. She threw out a ton of compressed orbs, and machinery filled up the field.

The large number of machines drowned this boss. Not long after, the boss who had half health was defeated by Maple Moon alone.

After playing for three versions, she had realized that she was quite talented in this aspect, and her PVP skills had been becoming stronger and stronger. Furthermore, this version was the powerful period for the Mechanic class, so farming dungeons was much easier. Mechanics above level 100 were welcomed by most dungeon teams.

The group came out of the dungeon and returned to the army's battleship.

"Why were you distracted?" Bun-Hit-Dog complained. "I didn't actually have to use one revive count."

"Look at the faction mission."

Bun-Hit-Dog opened the faction interface and saw the [Wipe Out the Great Cosmos Corps] mission.

Surprised, he opened the forums and realized that the army's players were already overjoyed.

Although the exploration of the main storyline mission was filled with uncertainties and was quite interesting, the players spent most of their time in spaceships and hardly had any opportunities to fight.

Most players were itching for a brawl and could only enter dungeons. Now that there was an opportunity to fight in the main storyline mission, all the army players were excited.

Wiping out an entire organization sounded like quite a large mission.

Chapter 829: Black Star Army, Not Bad

In the Jeraton Star System of the Renault Star Cluster, the alliance exploration team of the Bloodshed Land and the Klent Kingdom was executing their plan step by step, slowly painting the gray areas on the star map green. The internal stargate network of the first Star Zone was gradually being built. The exploration of planets was completed one after another. Detailed data was added to the database. Tons of space buoys were left wherever they passed.

The exploration of the Bloodshed Land was smooth and peaceful. There were quite many resource planets in the Jeraton Star System, but they had yet to meet any native civilizations.

Heber had been very free in the past ten days or so. The large fleet was operating according to plan and did not need his command. Therefore, he found a Fixed Star to train his energy.

At a hot red Fixed Star in this Star Zone, Heber walked on the Fixed Star's surface. The energy of the Fixed Star within tens of miles from him formed a moving vortex, spinning around him. Under the stimulation of energy, his cells devoured the powerful radiation around him and turned it into his energy. White bright energy patches appeared on his skin.

"Hu..." Heber exhaled deeply.

He stomped the ground. The enormous strength turned into a rippling impact wave, and the energy vortex around him shattered instantly. Covered in thick energy flames, Heber broke away from the powerful gravitational pull of the Fixed Star and rocket up like a beam of light shooting into space. Very soon, he left the Fixed Star and returned to the waiting fleet.

Heber walked into the spaceship and casually wore his cape. He then took the communicator from his subordinate. It was a message from Klent.

"Your Excellency Tyrant, we have just received news that the chief commander has given an order to the Black Star Army to eliminate a native organization."

"Attacking a native organization?" Heber's footsteps paused. "The dynasty's exploration laws forbid casual use of violence."

"Our people on Planet Lighthouse have heard that the situation Black Star has met is special. That native organization is a pillager at the center of the Star Cluster. The Black Star Army's men discovered them coincidentally. The dynasty wants the planetary information this native organization has, so the chief commander allowed the Black Star Army to eliminate them."

Heber frowned slightly.

While they were progressing stably, the Black Star Army had already gone into the jungle‽

If the Black Star Army obtained the information the native organization had accumulated, it would be quite a significant achievement.

Initially, he had thought that the Star System they were exploring was richer and the results of their exploration would definitely exceed the Black Star Army's. Sadly, Black Star was a very lucky person.

Heber shook his head.

He did not want to see the Black Star Army achieve that, yet there was nothing he could do but watch. He could not help but sigh.

This time, the person from Klent said, "Your Excellency Tyrant, our commander has a daring idea..."

"Attack Black Star again?"

"That's right. We plan to..."

"Enough." Heber interrupted before he could finish. "I have made a ceasefire agreement with the Black Star Army. I don't want to mess with them now, and neither should you. This is meaningless."

He then hung up the communication.

The Klent Kingdom had yet to give up; they did not want to see their enemy, the Black Star Army, successfully make such an achievement. Heber did not want to be dragged down by Klent.

The commander sent by Klent this time had once been a radical supporter of the secret war, so he harbored a lot of hatred for Han Xiao. What he wanted to do was basically snatch away the Black Star Army's contributions and disrupt Black Star, which not only had a negligible chance of success in Heber's eyes but would also bring the dissatisfaction of Black Star and the dynasty. Furthermore, it would not impact the Black Star Army much, if at all. It was not worth the risk.

In the Flickering World, Heber really was not willing to fight with Black Star. With such a huge cake, it would be best to just explore his own area. If he and the Black Star Army caused trouble for each other, it would only benefit the other dynasty allies who came to explore in the future.

...

In Han Xiao's previous life, when the players entered the Flickering World in Version 4.0, the exploration was already complete for many Star Clusters. Tons of exterior forces entered and fought each other, so the players had plenty of opportunities to fight. The situation was different now.

It was now only Version 3.0. Because of Han Xiao, the players were able to get involved in the Flickering World storyline one version earlier, which also meant that the environment would be different. At the early stage of the exploration, there were only the dynasty and its allies, who were all on the same side. Therefore, the players lacked the fighting storyline and had few chances to battle.

Therefore, when the [Wipe Out the Great Cosmos Corps] appeared, all the players who were exploring the Flickering World with the Black Star Army took part in this group operation. This mission did not have a maximum participant limit, so most players decided to accept the mission.

Han Xiao was happy with this. As the players were currently in different exploration teams and were quite divided, he casually arranged thousands of spaceships to gather these players into an expedition fleet.

As it would take quite some time to reach the center area of the Garu Star Cluster, Han Xiao was not planning to have the players wait in the spaceships—that would be a waste of quality labor. He planned to let this expedition group explore the planets on the way to maximize efficiency.

To make the return of the players easier, they also had to build stargates on the way.

This way, the exploration plan of the Black Star Army shifted as well. The large team slowly explored the border Star System, the first Special Task Force led by Hadavy were building a route from the south of the Star Cluster to the east, and the expedition team were building the route from the south of the Star Cluster to the center.

As the army's men were split into three groups, Han Xiao told Sylvia, who was in the Shattered Star Ring headquarters, to quickly dispatch the second fleet to make up for the manpower.

After growing for two versions, the players now had Grade B strength. Millions of army players were considered quite powerful. Han Xiao was not worried.

As versions updated, the players became stronger. They would gradually be noticed by the entire universe.

After sending out the player expedition team, Han Xiao left them alone. He explored resource planets one after another according to the plan while expanding his machinery while he had the time.

As two more Star Zones were completely explored, one month passed peacefully.

On this day, Han Xiao finally received Phillip's report that the player expedition team had finally met with the Great Cosmos Corps' reconnaissance troops.

...

The team that met the reconnaissance troops was a player team that was deploying space buoys. It was just a small recon ship with around three hundred players, while the opponent had three battleships.

The battle erupted instantly. The moment this reconnaissance team discovered these players, they rushed forward without a word, planning to capture the enemies and interrogate them for intel about the Black Star Army.

Shots landed on the shield of this mini recon ship, causing chain exploration, while the flickering shield was unaffected.

"Alert! The spaceship is being attacked. Remaining shield energy 97.1%... 99.7%... charge complete. Estimating threat level... estimation complete. the enemy's firepower is unable to penetrate the shield. Threat level extremely low."

The hundreds of players inside the spaceship exchanged looks.

The Black Star Army's spaceships used the complete Star System technology, and some even had Star Cluster standards, such as the energy core, weapon, and shield. Comparatively, the Great Cosmos Corps' spaceships were too behind. Without an enormous quantity difference, there was no way they would be of any threat to the Black Star Army's spaceships.

Close range combat was exactly what the players wanted. As the three enemy recon ships approached and were about to connect their cabins, more than ten charge cabins shot out from the side of this mini recon ship, 'biting' into the three enemy spaceships.

The players inside the charge cabin swarmed out and started a slaughter inside the enemy ships. These players were mostly above level 100, while the people on the enemy ships were ordinary people.

Not long after, the hundreds of players wiped out the enemies inside these ships and seized the three spaceships.

On the other side, Atimo received this news as well.

However, he did not receive the video information that the recon group was supposed to send. The strength of the Black Star Army was still unknown to him.

"Before losing contact, the reconnaissance group only sent back the fact that they had met enemies, and the link was broken right after. We don't know the process of them fighting their enemies," the deputy said with confusion.

"Like with Kikiga..." Atimo narrowed his eyes, and a rare tint of concern flashed past his eyes. "The enemy's quantum technology might far exceed ours."

Before the battle erupted, Phillip had invaded the enemy's artificial intelligence and forcefully blocked the opponent's communication, like when Kikiga met Psionic Prime. Therefore, Atimo still did not know how many spaceships and men the Black Star Army had.

On the other hand, Phillip knew where the Atimo's troops were and was ordering the expedition team to head directly toward that direction.

No matter the war, the importance of intelligence could never be ignored. The virtual technology of the army was far superior, and the Great Cosmos Corps was basically blind in comparison.

Ever since he began ruling the 'universe', Atimo had never met an enemy that had made him feel any sense of pressure. However, this Black Star Army that appeared out of nowhere had shaken his confidence.

This might be the strongest opponent he had ever met.

"Black Star Army, not bad," Atimo said with a firm tone. "I can call you the strongest opponent. However, facing my fleet, your end will be no different from the others!"

Atimo was extremely confident. He had brought all his spaceships, a total of a hundred thousand battleships!

This was the fleet he had accumulated throughout the years, and this was what gave him confidence to rule over the 'universe'.

From his perspective, such an enormous fleet could wipe out any enemy.

Chapter 830: Surrounding Calamity Grade

After meeting the reconnaissance troops, the expedition force reorganized their troops and adjusted their direction toward Atimo's fleet. At the same time, Atimo's fleet also headed toward the reconnaissance troops, and both parties were approaching each other with the gap between them decreasing rapidly.

After spending two days in hyperdrive, both troops finally met in one of the regions of the universe.

"We finally found our enemy." The players in the expedition troops looked out at the large fleet of battleships outside the window and all grew excited.

The players split up into parties, and the various large guilds were no exception. The various professional teams formed their own parties, and the core members of the guilds formed a protective layer around the professional players. This was not to protect them but to help their own team snatch for the boss.

[Wipe Out the Great Cosmos Corps] was a faction mission, and there were many mission requirements. The requirements that gave the best rewards included killing the combat troops of the enemy and their leaders. However, there was a limited number to go around to kill.

That was especially so for the 'Great Emperor' Atimo, of whom there was only one. It was not a single player mission but only allowed a single party to share the reward. Every club wanted to help their own professional players obtain the highest reward.

The players of Dynasty, Temple of God, Long Sky, and Fried Eggplants with Fish were in their respective teams, and the three pillars of Long Sky were currently discussing their strategy.

Sleepy Winter stroked his chin and said, "According to the levels of the rewards, the enemy leader Atimo should have the combat capability of a Grade A Super. We can only use numbers to crush him."

"If this is the case," Twinkle Fried Rice said, "the party that makes the first move will be in the greatest danger. If we want to snatch the kill, it would be better for us to deal damage silently by the side and let others attract the aggro of the boss. Only the party with the highest damage output will obtain the reward. If we end up getting killed by the boss, it would take far too much time to run back after reviving. We can only output damage if we are still alive."

Hao Tian nodded and said, "That's right."

On another spaceship, Frenzied Sword also formed a party with his team and even brought Maple Moon along. They had a pretty good relationship.

Frenzied Sword looked outside the window at the rows of battleships lined up nicely. It was obvious that the guilds were all gathering together, and there was a stark difference between them and the ordinary players. Upon seeing that, Frenzied Sword shook his head and said, "With so many guilds trying to snatch the boss, I think that we don't have much hope of succeeding."

"As long as we don't die," said Rivervale's vice captain, Evil Sword, "we may not lose out in terms of damage output. Such a boss will not only stand there for us to kill. The party that outputs the most damage will also face the largest threat and attract the most aggro from the boss. We may have a chance to survive until the very end if that is the case."

All the players had some experience and knew that it was extremely difficult to deal with the bosses in 'Galaxy'. To an ordinary player, the situation of the battle was changing every second, and it was rare for a single person to control the aggro of the boss. Instead, the person with the highest damage output would be the target of the boss, and the battle scene was extremely realistic.

Thus, it was extremely easy for the aggro to go out of control when fighting the boss, and they needed to react quickly whatever happened.

Maple Moon sat by the side with a smile on her face, and she felt a sense of satisfaction in her heart.

It could be said that this large-scale war had been started by her single handedly. She was the one who had triggered the storyline and caused this expedition mission. Thus, she had a strong sense of achievement and was feeling extremely satisfied in her heart.

Because she was the one who triggered this mission, she had an additional mission compared to the other players. She would be able to gain a bonus reward after the Great Cosmos Corps was wiped out, which included a large amount of experience, Exploration Points, 300 Crimson Dynasty Contribution Points, and 1,000 Black Star Army Contribution Points.

This was probably the reward for handing the mission tool over to the dynasty.

The reward from this mission was extremely plentiful, and after some calculations, Maple Moon felt that it was possible for her to become the highest leveled player after the mission.

Among the Russian and Australian groups, Vodka and Captain Old Henry were also thinking of snatching the boss.

Although the professional players of their own club did not follow them over, if they could prevent the Chinese professional players from snatching the boss' reward, it would be akin to helping their own professional players. Although the Russian and Australian players had suffered some losses on Planet Pangurus, their responsibility was still present, and they were not willing to let the Chinese players enjoy all the benefits before their eyes.

At the same time, Atimo was also observing the Black Star Army fleet.

"The enemy only has ten thousand battleships, and we have the absolute advantage in numbers," the vice commander said.

Atimo nodded slowly. He had a hundred thousand battleships, a full ten times more than the enemy.

However, Atimo was still shocked that the Black Star Army could have a full ten thousand battleships. In his memory, every battleship required a large amount of resources and time to construct. The most powerful race that he had met only had a few hundred battleships.

He had originally thought that the quantum technology of the Black Star Army was the only advantage that they had, but never had he expected that the fleet of the Black Star Army would not be weak either.

"No wonder they locked down the news. They didn't want me to find out that they had such a large fleet and wanted to catch me off guard." Atimo felt a sense of lingering fear.

To gather a full ten thousand battleships, the other party must have sent out all their forces. Thankfully, he had also brought out his entire fleet. If he had only sent out a few divisions as usual, he would definitely have been in trouble.

Indeed, it was the right choice for him to take action personally.

Atimo's eyes glowed, and he said slowly, "I want to talk to the other party's leader."

In his eyes, this was an all-out war between both parties. The commander of the Black Star Army was an extremely mysterious figure and had never shown himself. Atimo wanted to see what kind of a figure the leader of the Black Star Army was. He actually had ten thousand battleships under his command, and Atimo felt that such an individual had the right to talk to him.

After a moment, the vice commander stammered, "The other party rejected our request... they sa... said..."

"What did they say?" Atimo's eyes narrowed.

"They said that you do not have the right to speak to their Army Commander."

Atimo burst into laughter and was not angered at all.

I do not have the rights? Who else would have more rights than me‽

Forget it, since they are going to die in a short while, there isn't a need to be so calculative.

Atimo shook his head and lost all interest in contacting the other party. He then said slowly, "Attack, wipe them all out!"

With the order being given, the hundred thousand battleships opened fire in unison.

Atimo thought that he would witness the scene of the enemy being severely crippled by the firepower of his fleet. However, the scene that unfolded had truly shocked him.

As the flames of the cannon fire receded, not a single one of the enemy's ten thousand battleships was destroyed. Although the enemy was lower in numbers, they wanted to surround his fleet instead!

The next moment, the ten thousand enemy battleships sped up, and because their speed was far superior to his Great Cosmos Corps' battleships, Atimo's troops were unable to react in time. The ten thousand enemy battleships had broken through their formation and engaged in closed range battle with them. This was the battle method that players enjoyed the most, and they were not willing to use their battleships to wipe out the enemy since they would not be able to gain experience this way.

The players boarded the enemy battleships with the charge cabin and massacred the members of the enemy battleships.

The enemy's fire was unable to break through the shields of the army, and the players charged into the encirclement of the enemy excitedly with a single thought in their mind.

My peerless blade shall dance within the enemy ranks!

The majority of the players had not enjoyed such a pleasure of their faction having absolute technological superiority and being able to freely slaughter the enemy.

Ten thousand battleships charged right into the core of the enemy fleet and were completely unstoppable as they ripped through the enemy's formation.

In the flagship, Atimo stood up abruptly and ripped off the mask on his face. His expression had changed greatly, and a look of disbelief could be seen.

Their weapons were completely useless against the enemy!

One report after another was sent over, and he lost twenty thousand battleships in just a short moment. However, not even a single enemy battleship had been destroyed!

"This is impossible! How can there be such a large technological gap! How can they all be Supers‽"

Atimo no longer had his previous cool and confidence, having realized that he had struck a metal plate. The enemy was a civilization that was even more advanced than his and could easily wipe them out!

He had roamed unhindered in this region of the universe for far too long and had not met an opponent capable of posing him a threat for far too long. He had already forgotten what it meant to feel fear and respect. However, the scene of his battleships being destroyed one by one had once again triggered the sense of fear in his heart as he began to tremble uncontrollably.

He could see the future of his fleet being completely wiped out.

Atimo suddenly thought about the matters from a long time ago. At that time, the Great Cosmos Corps was only an ordinary drifting civilization with a few spaceships. They were extremely weak and could only explore the universe carefully. They overcame obstacles one after another and gradually became stronger and stronger. However, he had actually lost this sense of wariness that allowed him to survive in the universe for such a long time.

If he had not been so rash and made proper plans before the start of the battle...

If he had not been so arrogant and sent out scouts to find more information...

If he had not been so quick to anger and easily provoked by the Black Star Army...

Perhaps the outcome would have been different.

However, he didn't know that this was his own wishful thinking. In front of absolute strength and intelligence advantage, it would be impossible for him to have the initiative in his hands. His fate was already sealed a long time ago.

Currently, it was useless for Atimo to regret. The excited players were killing to their heart's content and destroying Atimo's fleet.

The overwhelming strength of the enemy destroyed the morale of Atimo's forces, and no one wanted to remain behind to be massacred. They all began to escape, and the huge fleet scattered in all directions.

"Retreat! Quickly retreat!" Atimo snapped back to reality and issued an order.

Very quickly, the flagship and surrounding frigates turned around and joined in the escaping army.

The Great Cosmos Corps came with valor but escaped with their tails between their legs. It had only been twenty minutes since their arrival on the battlefield.

The various large guilds abandoned the escaping battleships and chased after the enemy's flagship. They all wanted to snatch the head of the boss, and the ordinary players went to chase after the escaping battleships.

Phillip had already locked onto the location of all the troops through the quantum network, and even if the enemies escaped, the players would still chase after them in the future.

Before the start of the battle, Phillip had infiltrated the database of the main flagship and made a copy of all the information within the Great Cosmos Corps' database. This included information about all the planets that they had robbed over the past years. The information that the dynasty wanted was already in their hands, and the only thing left to do was to uproot the enemy. Phillip could only provide some help from the side, and the rest would be left to the players.

Very quickly, the players caught up to Atimo's flagship, and he only had a few hundred frigates around him.

Phillip controlled Atimo's flagship from afar and forced it to land on a desolate planet nearby. The players chased after Atimo and surrounded him.

In the center of a circular mountain range, the gigantic flagship stuck out of the ground with black smoke billowing from it.

This was Atimo's spaceship, and Phillip had very considerately turned off the engine of the spaceship so that they could save some energy when landing.

Ka ka ka!

Many human figures then walked out from the wreckage of the battleships, and the armor that they were wearing helped them withstand the impact of the crash. However, the crash had still killed the majority of the ordinary crew, and less than ten percent of them were still alive.

Atimo also walked out from the wreckage, holding onto his head. Even with his strength, he was dazed after the crash, and his entire body was aching. Upon looking at the pathetic scene for his eyes, Atimo could not help but fall into a daze.

Right at this moment, the sound of gushing wind could be heard, and the battleships of the Black Star Army landed around the circular mountain range.

Atimo raised his head, and there were numerous human figures standing all around the mountain range. These were the players who were trying to kill him, and a greedy look could be seen in their eyes.

There were more than three hundred thousand players present, including the various large guilds.

"It's impossible to escape..."

Atimo was a proud person, and he could not help but feel a sense of anger upon witnessing the scene before his eyes.

"Want to kill me? Come on!" The next moment, Atimo let out a crazed roar, and the ten or so mechanical arms behind him opened like a peacock's plume. At the same time, yellow laser beams were shot out from the arms in all directions with a stunning firing rate. This was his personal equipment, which was used to aid his Esper Ability.

His Esper Ability was to shoot out laser beams from his body, and the attack would change depending on which part of his body the laser was shot out from. For example, the attack would be an energy blast if he used his palms and an accurate laser beam if he used his fingers.

When fighting in close combat, his fists could also be covered with energy blasts, and he could form a shield if he released energy from his entire body. This was truly a jack of all trades ability.

Atimo was the most powerful individual in the Great Cosmos Corps, and his Calamity Grade Esper Ability allowed his laser attacks to be more powerful than normal energy weapons. It could be said that he was a human artillery tower.

His arrogance also stemmed from the confidence that he had in his strength. Among the natives of the Flickering World, it was extremely rare to reach the Calamity Grade, and he had never met an opponent. He had once wiped out the race of an entire planet singlehandedly.

Although he was surrounded, Atimo did not fall into despair. He had a great deal of confidence in his own strength, and despite all the enemies before him being Supers, he did not treat them as his opponents at all.

He might be able to find a path to survival if he was able to kill all of them!

Thinking about that, Atimo burst forth with murderous intent and attacked crazily.

Pew pew pew!

The laser beams came flying toward the players, and the players all began avoiding the attacks. As the laser beams struck the ground, craters that were over ten meters in diameter exploded all around. If a level 100 paper player was struck by the laser beam, although it would not be able to one-shot the player, the player would only be left with a silver of health.

He was a Calamity Grade Super indeed! Many of the players felt nervous.

This was the first time that they had surrounded a Calamity Grade character without the aid of an NPC.

Everyone did not have much confidence in their hearts. They had met many elite Calamity Grade Supers in the secret war that were all capable of killing them in a single hit. The players did not know if their level was enough to kill a Calamity Grade Super with a human wave tactic.

"The battle has started!"

However, the players did not hesitate and jumped off from the cliffs to begin their attacks.

They would soon find out whether or not they could win.

Since they could not die anyway, they might as well just charge forward!

Chapter 831: First Kill

When Atimo's fleet was wiped out, Han Xiao, who was currently slacking off in the Garu Star Cluster, received a report from Phillip. The information collated by the Great Cosmos Corps had been sent over to him.

"Let me see my reward..." Han Xiao began to look through the information excitedly.

The Great Cosmos Corps had discovered many different planets over the past few years and a few Star Systems scattered all around the Garu Star Cluster.

A portion of these planets had natives living on them, but these natives were all enslaved by the Great Cosmos Corps. The information in the Great Cosmos Corps' database was not just words but also included some videos of the entire process of capturing a new planet.

Shaking his head, Han Xiao contacted the chief commander, Tarrokov.

"The information from the Great Cosmos Corps is in my hands. I will send a copy to you."

"Good job." Tarrokov briefly looked through the document and said with a smile, "The dynasty will take note of your contribution."

Before Han Xiao could say anything, a notification popped up on his interface.

You have submitted [Great Cosmos Corps Exploratory Information]!

+1,500 the Crimson Dynasty Contribution Points.

+550 Exploration Points.

[Flickering World—The First Phase] rating increased

The Flickering World mission was a faction mission, and the exploration of Garu was the first phase. All the players would share the mission rating, and the mission rating would be dependent on the Exploration Points.

After a month of exploration, everyone's mission rating was originally D-, but everyone's rating had increased to grade D.

Although it did not seem like much, this was a S+ grade mission, and every small increase in the rating would take a very long time. The increase would also become more difficult toward the end.

However, the 1,500 the Crimson Dynasty Contribution Point was the reward that he was the most excited about. He had spent 6,000 Contribution Points on the Ultimate Knowledge [Mechanical Life Tinder], and he still had just over 2,000 Contribution Points left.

Having obtained 1,500 Contribution Points in one go, he only needed slightly more than 2,000 points to exchange for a new Ultimate Knowledge. Because of his status, the price of an Ultimate Knowledge was discounted. In his previous life, players needed 12,000 Contribution Points to purchase one.

However, ordinary players could obtain a rank when they joined the Crimson Dynasty and do missions to increase their rank. The higher their rank, the greater the discount that they could enjoy. However, even the maximum discount that they could obtain did not reach his fifty percent discount.

The hidden mission that Maple Moon had discovered gave him great reward, and Han Xiao was truly overjoyed.

He definitely had to reward such a capable player greatly so that the other players would be encouraged to dig out other hidden missions.

As he was checking the interface, Tarrokov did not stop talking. "This report will save us a great deal of manpower. I will get people to enter the information into a star map. Since you have already sent people to wipe out the Great Cosmos Corps, you can temporarily take over their territory. You can also leave some manpower to mine for resources in the center of Garu."

"Alright." Han Xiao smiled. This was also his motive.

Compared to the Star Systems in the periphery, the center of a Star Cluster was the most prosperous region. In order to wipe out the Great Cosmos Corps, his expedition forces had the perfect excuse to set up a long-distance travel route, and he would be able to enter the center of the Star Cluster in the future directly. This way, he would be able to discover all the famous planets and fill up his warehouse secretly.

As long as he discovered a territory first, the other allies of the dynasty who joined in later would not be able to snatch it from him. If he could take the most prosperous region of the Star Cluster, he would be able to earn the most from this mission.

Furthermore, now that he had already made a long-distance trip once, the others would not be suspicious of him if he ran to the east secretly to find the Universal Treasure.

Tarrokov then said that he would report the matter to the dynasty and let the dynasty reward him with resources and manpower.

After chatting for a while more, they hung up.

Han Xiao then connected to Phillip's view, and he could see the battle between the players and Atimo, which was a few Star Systems away.

...

Boom!

Explosions were never-ending!

The flood of players charged toward Atimo, who was in the center.

Atimo fought valiantly and weaved around the crowd to avoid all the attacks while launching laser beams from every part of his body. He was like a walking artillery tower, shooting at the crowd in all directions.

Beams of light shot through the crowded battlefield, and explosions could be seen all around, sending many human figures covered in shield lights flying.

The battle had already been going on for a long while, and the battlefield was covered in a myriad of colors from the various abilities of the players. Atimo had no less than thirty negative statuses on him. Although these statuses did not last long, the sheer number of players he faced meant that the statuses kept refreshing.

With the huge gap in their levels, Atimo had the advantage in speed, and the players were not able to lock onto him or stabilize the aggro. It was akin to the players of the different regions facing Atimo's attacks at random. As long as they met Atimo, the players who had only just reached Grade B were not able to tank the damage.

Players were usually in parties that only consisted of a few dozen players at the very most in the dungeons, and this was the first time that they had fought a boss with so many players together. Every party wanted to output as much damage as they could, and they were not afraid of friendly fire. As such, the battlefield was extremely chaotic.

The difficulty of this battle was much higher than what the players had expected, and all the tactics that they had thought of beforehand were completely useless. They could only react to the situation on the spot.

However, the players did not know that the pressure that Atimo was enduring was many times greater than theirs.

Atimo weaved through the crowd and wanted to use the crowd as his human shield and make the players cautious about friendly fire, thus reducing the intensity of the attacks. However, he was shocked to realize that this bunch of people could not have cared less about the deaths of their comrades and would go all out even if it meant the death of their comrades.

Even the cold Atimo could not help but be startled by the players. Even though he did not have any way to escape and the other party already had the upper hand, they still engaged in such a cruel method, disregarding the number of casualties!

This was far too cold blooded. The Black Star Army was actually so unscrupulous in their means!

Since the players were not afraid of their deaths, his strategy was completely useless. Atimo could only endure the firepower coming from all directions and had to exhaust energy to maintain his shield.

The attacks of the players were only at the Grade B level, but Atimo did not dare use his body to tank the collective damage of all the players. After all, he did not have a powerful physique.

His shield was unable to block out all the damage, especially the Psychic attacks that came from time to time, which gave him a huge headache. Most of the negative statuses inflicted on him were from the Psychic attacks.

Atimo also had plenty of injuries all over his body, and his health was slowly decreasing. He did not have a powerful recovery capability, so his recovery speed could not keep up even if he used his energy to stimulate the recovery of his cells.

Furthermore, with his energy being depleted so quickly, Atimo felt that it was becoming more and more impossible for him to kill all the enemies.

Although Atimo felt this way, he would not surrender as long as he had the slightest bit of hope.

Even if I can't escape, I have to deal the greatest amount of damage that I can! Atimo thought to himself.

Even if he died, he wanted to bite off a huge piece of flesh from the Black Star Army. Since these enemies were so crazy in their attacks, he would be able to cause the maximum amount of damage to his enemies.

Atimo's body flashed, and he appeared in another region. All of a sudden, a cracking sound could be heard under his feet as he stepped into a series of mechanical traps. The powerful magnetic force tied his body down and slowed his movements greatly.

"Everyone, come over! I caught him!" one of the players cried out.

The players in the surroundings immediately unleashed all their firepower on Atimo.

Atimo let out a low growl, and his energy shield glowed brightly. The bullets rained down on his shield, and sparks could be seen bursting all around.

Boom!

Energy beams shot out in all directions, and the artillery towers that were near him exploded.

Following which, he stomped on the ground and destroyed the mechanical traps under his feet, obtaining freedom. Just when Atimo wanted to retreat, he suddenly felt a wave of dizziness, and more than ten Psychics around him each greeted him with a mental attack.

In the momentary delay, a large group of Pugilists took the opportunity to charge forward, and their flaming fists crashed down on Atimo's shield.

Boom boom boom!

The shield began flickering, and Atimo gritted his teeth. He then waved his arm, and an energy whip shot out and swept all the incoming Pugilists away.

Fighting on the ground was extremely disadvantageous to him, so Atimo tried to take flight again. However, he had only flown a few meters into the air before feeling a powerful sense of obstruction, which slowed his movements down greatly.

Raising his head to look up, there were countless magical formations floating in the sky to prevent him from flying.

It was impossible for Grade B Mages to stop him even if they stacked their formations, but it would take a long time for Atimo to weave through the anti-flying region. He did not dare do that as it would turn him into a live target.

Furthermore, even if he was able to fly, the enemy could still chase after him if he did not wipe them out. He did not think that his own flying speed was faster than a spaceship, and he would not be able to escape since he was stuck on the planet.

Both parties were locked in a long battle, and Atimo could feel a sense of fatigue.

He could not remember how many he had killed already. It could be tens of thousands, and the friendly fire among the enemy had probably killed even more people than him.

"A bunch of maniacs!" Atimo spat out a mouthful of spittle and dragged his heavy body to continue fighting.

His energy was already running out, and his body felt heavier and heavier by the second.

"It seems I don't stand a chance..." Atimo's heart sank, and he became even more ferocious.

At least the enemy suffered more casualties! He had to drag as many people to die with him as possible!

At this moment, Atimo avoided another wave of fire and looked around to observe the densely packed enemy around him. All of a sudden, he felt something extremely strange about the battle.

After fighting for such a long time, he should have killed many enemies, and the enemies obviously did not have any reinforcements. Why did it seem that the number of enemies had not changed at all‽

Atimo was stunned.

In his world view, death was certain, and there was no such thing as revival. Thus, he did not pay close attention to the number of enemies that he had to face. Furthermore, the battlefield was extremely chaotic, and there were thousands and thousands of enemies. He did not have the time to recognize the faces of every individual. Together with the fact that he was trapped in a dangerous situation, he only managed to notice that something was wrong.

After realizing this, Atimo began to observe the people around him carefully, and his expression changed greatly.

"This bunch of people... are actually undying‽"

Atimo's expression changed drastically, and he had a look of disbelief on his face. A deep sense of despair filled his heart and spread out to his entire body.

No wonder... No wonder they don't care about the fatalities. It turns out that this group of people don't even know the concept of death...

He had thought that he was causing severe damage to the enemy, but it turned out that it was only a naïve thought. His own retaliation was a pointless struggle.

If it was only because he had to face a large number of enemies, Atimo would still have had the desire to fight them to the death. But after discovering that the enemy could still revive, Atimo's mental state completely collapsed. He fell into complete despair, and his will to fight completely disappeared.

"Argh!" Atimo's final trace of hope was destroyed, and he let out a roar to the heavens. He then burst forth with all his remaining strength without reserving the slightest bit of energy.

Boom!

More than ten thick pillars of lights swept throughout the battlefield, and all those who came into contact with one were instantly killed. Just this attack alone had wiped out more than ten thousand players.

"Take note! Everyone drop! This should be the final phase of the boss. We are going to enter the final struggle!"

All the parties hurriedly dropped to the ground, and the pillar of light floated past their heads. However, the burning energy source still caused some damage to them.

The light pillars disappeared quickly, and Atimo's body shook unsteadily from side to side as though he would fall over at any moment.

Bang!

A cannonball sent Atimo crashing to the ground. As all the players witnessed this scene, they hurriedly got up and began spamming all their attacks at Atimo.

Atimo, who had lost his will to fight back, was like a doll for everyone to snatch. His limbs were quickly torn apart, and his body was tortured by the players. His eyes gradually became unfocused, and the players around him were like demons in his eyes.

Before his death, Atimo suddenly imagined the faces of all the players becoming his face.

He suddenly thought about his many years of robbing and pillaging.

Could this be his retribution?

Puchi!

The next moment, his head was ripped off by someone, and his sight turned gray.

"Hahaha! The reward for killing him is ours!" a player from Dynasty cheered.

Second Prince then waved Atimo's head excitedly, and King Admiral shook his head by the side.

"Tsk, it actually belongs to Dynasty."

"I died three times but didn't even manage to touch a single hair on his body. What a loss."

"Why don't we get rid of some over here?"

The professional players of the other teams looked at Dynasty greedily.

Vodka and Captain Old Henry were disappointed that the reward of the boss had been snatched by the large clubs. Dynasty would probably be a powerful enemy again during the upcoming Pro League.

During the battle previously, they had aimed their attacks at the Chinese players and wanted to pretend that it was accidental friendly fire. However, they also realized that they had suffered from an unusually large amount of friendly fire, and each of them had died an average of three times. They were probably the targets of the Chinese players as well.

Although the ordinary players did not receive the reward, they were still extremely excited.

Atimo was the first Calamity Grade Super that had died by their hands!

This was the first Calamity Grade kill for the players!

On the other side, Han Xiao had also received a report from Phillip and heaved a sigh of relief.

"They finally killed a Calamity Grade..."

If it was a Calamity Grade like Ember, it would have been impossible for the players to kill him regardless of how many times they revived.

However, Atimo did not have such a perverse ability and was only an ordinary Calamity Grade Super. Phillip had caused the spaceship to crash, but the players had their spaceships to chase after him. Thus, Atimo did not have any route of retreat and had no choice but to face the players. Since the players had the strength of a Grade B Super, their strength had achieved a qualitative change, and Atimo could only die with regrets.

In Han Xiao's eyes, this event would be a milestone that belonged to the players, and it was also the turning point for the players' thoughts.

In his previous life, the players had only managed to get rid of a Calamity Grade Super during Version 4.0. After that, the players knew that they could have the strength of an ordinary Calamity Grade Super, and their mental state had a subtle change. They became even more confident in themselves... and more death seeking.

This was something that could not be avoided as the players were extremely opinionated. However, this influence was limited at the moment. Han Xiao's personal combat strength and organization were sufficient to suppress the little demons in all the players.

He had intentionally allowed the players to deal with Atimo so that they could get rid of a Calamity Grade Super as members of the Black Star Army. If they did not have Phillip's help, they would not have been able to stop Atimo from escaping, and it would have been impossible for them to kill the first Calamity Grade boss.

As such, this first kill was the fruit of the players' effort and also the strength of the faction. As long as the players understood this, their sense of belonging to the faction would only increase.

Furthermore, this first kill was a milestone event and a combined activity of the army. Through this incident, this would tie even more players to the army.

Chapter 832: [Merit Seeker]

After getting rid of Atimo, the [Wipe Out the Great Cosmos Corps] mission did not end immediately, and there were still other players chasing after the other members of the Great Cosmos Corps who had escaped.

With the battle ending, the hundreds of thousands of players checked their interface and saw a notification.

The Black Star Army has submitted [Great Cosmos Corps Exploratory Information]!

[Flickering World—The First Phase] rating increased.

Through the Flickering World Main Storyline Mission, Han Xiao was not the only one who received this notification, and the players also received it.

This was the army helping them to increase their benefits.

The players were all overjoyed, and the accumulated Exploration Points should be enough to let their Mission Rating increase from D to C after this mission.

Apart from the players, no living beings were left behind on the battlefield. The players then entered the wreckage of the different battleships in search of their spoils of war. Although the technological standard of the Great Cosmos Corps was far from that of the Black Star Army, the players would never leave empty handed and swept across the battlefield like a swarm of locusts, taking everything that was valuable away.

The circular mountain range was left with craters all around and the wreckages of the different battleships sticking out from the ground. The players boarded the spaceships and left the planet, leaving behind the mess of their battle and a ground full of corpses that none of them could be bothered to deal with.

...

On the forums, the players who participated in the battle to kill Atimo began to show off their achievement. As the first Calamity Grade Super that they had killed, it was an extremely memorable event. There were some who had immediately recorded the event in the Galaxy Chronicles.

'In year 705 of the Galaxy Calendar, we completed the first kill of Atimo.'

All of them were naturally proud of their achievement. It has already been three versions, and they had first seen a Calamity Grade Super in Version 2.0. During Version 3.0, they had personally participated in battles with Calamity Grade Supers, and the strength of the Calamity Grade had already been imprinted into their hearts. At this moment, they had finally gotten rid of one by themselves.

Even though they had surrounded their enemy with well over a hundred thousand people, their enemy was a native, and they had only succeeded because the army blocked their enemy's escape route—the players were still extremely excited.

Since a long time ago, many had analyzed that as long as there were no major changes to the various grades, the players would become more and more important in the galaxy as their levels increased. This first kill was evidence that supported this theory.

As such, many players looked forward to the next version.

Perhaps we can also have a fist fight with Heber and kick Psyker around some day.

It was a pity Han Xiao did not know of the dreams of these players. If he did, he would definitely not allow them to continue enjoying their dreams and show them that their dreams were completely empty.

The one who took the reward for the kill was Dynasty. As a famous Chinese guild, the players were not too surprised that they were able to get the kill. In fact, the Chinese players would not be surprised if it was anyone of the four great guilds that got the kill. However, if it was any other guild or an ordinary player who got the kill, the players would then think that it was dog-sh*t luck.

Looking at Dynasty showing off their reward for the kill, all the players could only watch with envy with the other guilds being the ones who were the most envious.

This was the first kill for a Calamity Grade Super. The reward aside, the fame brought about by this first kill was what the guilds sought the most. This would be the glory of the guild that they could use to attract other members. Even if the other guilds could kill a few Calamity Grade Supers after this, the meaning would be completely different from a first kill.

Second Prince was the one who completed the final attack, and he posted the pictures of the kill happily on the forums. He could not help but boast about his achievement.

Although he was a professional player, he had never bothered about his own personal image. As the number two player in Dynasty, he had always wanted to overthrow King Admiral and gave off the impression of someone both mischievous and arrogant.

However, after Maple Moon revealed her own mission under the urging of Frenzied Sword, all the players' attention was immediately drawn over to her.

Maple Moon revealed how she had discovered the coordinate marker and her own personal mission.

All the players had assumed that attacking the Great Cosmos Corps was an order from the dynasty; they only realized that this entire mission was a storyline created by a single player after seeing her thread!

To them, this was the largest influence that the players had on the army!

"Oh my goodness, this was actually a player-triggered hidden mission‽"

"Maple Moon? This name sounds pretty familiar... Eh? Isn't she the one who followed our Army Commander since very early on in the first version?"

"To think that she was actually able to discover such a hidden mission. What good luck she has."

Many players became extremely envious of Maple Moon. She had remained extremely quiet throughout the past two versions, and she had stunned the entire world with her actions in one fell swoop.

In Han Xiao's previous life, Maple Moon had been extremely famous for digging out hidden storylines. She had gradually become famous in Version 3.0 and emerged as a black horse in the third Pro League. This was not too strange as there were black horses every year, with the third Pro League having the most. Version 3.0 was the time for the Mechanics to rise and, almost 80% of the black horses were the Mechanics who had an extremely awkward position in the first two seasons.

The rewards of her solo mission were extremely plentiful, and it was even more than the reward to kill Atimo. Thus, the players on the forums all had their eyes turn green with envy. She did not even need to kill the boss and could get a reward even greater than killing the boss just by slacking off by the side! This was too good a deal!

Second Prince also stopped boasting and joined the envious army. Compared to the other aloof professional players, he was extremely active and enjoyed playing together with the ordinary players.

However, Maple Moon's thread also contained the reward that Black Star gave to her through the faction interface.

You have triggered Faction Mission [Black Star's Generosity]

Mission complete!

Due to your contribution, your faction [Black Star Army] has rewarded you for your exploration.

+10 Favorability with Black Star

You have received 25,000,000 Experience, 200,000 Enas, and 2,000 Black Star Army Contribution Points.

Your army rank increased by one grade.

You have received a new title: [Merit Seeker]

Merit Seeker: A glorious title in the Black Star Army. You can receive materials, resources, or equipment of no more than 500 Enas daily for free and 1,000 army Contribution Points every month. Any member of the army who provides special information can receive this title (Only limited to the Flickering World mission).

Looking at the reward that the army gave to Maple Moon, the players could not help but drool.

My goodness, the army's reward is even more fantastic.

Two hundred thousand Enas was no small sum, and there was the unique army title. The effect of this title was just too tempting. Five hundred Enas of resources for free every day. This was 10,500 in a month and 180,000 in a year! The long-term benefits of such a title were truly amazing, and it was akin to earning money just by sitting at home!

It had always been them spending money in the army, and this was the first time that they had seen someone taking money from the army.

Han Xiao's objective of issuing such a mission was very obvious.

Do you see that? That is the treatment of a meritorious subject!

Even though both were army titles, [Secret Warrior] and [Merit Seeker] were extremely different. The former was given to everyone who participated in the secret war whereas Maple Moon was the only one who had the latter.

This also verified one of the players' guesses. As long as the method was right, they could directly affect the actions of the entire faction. Many people could not help but be excited at this revelation.

Through Maple Moon's thread, many players understood how they could replicate this incident. The only way for them to do so would be to search for hidden missions and hand them over to the army!

"Since the army is exploring the Flickering World, we should be able to gain the [Merit Seeker] title as long as we find some hidden information similar to the Great Cosmos Corps, right?"

"This is definitely the case! The army has such a title to encourage us to dig out hidden missions for sure!"

With Maple Moon as an example, all the players became excited, and their passion to search for hidden missions was ignited.

...

Looking at the drooling players on the forums, Han Xiao could not help but chuckle to himself.

He had given Maple Moon a title that had both glory and benefits so that the other players would be encouraged to find more hidden missions and hand them over to him.

After all, it was the player's specialty to find hidden missions, and they might be able to find the second fragment of the [Bold Explorer] skill.

Apart from this, he also intended to groom Maple Moon. This lady was a character who had risen to prominence in Version 3.0 in his previous life. As the trainer of the Mechanic class, if the Mechanics were able to obtain a good result during the upcoming Pro League, it would give him more opportunities to bluff... ahem... attract new players to choose the Mechanic Class. This way, he would have more crops to harvest.

Maple Moon was the black horse in this Pro League, and Han Xiao did not mind letting this black horse become blacker. With so many rewards, Maple Moon would probably be the first player to reach the maximum level.

The other players were still chasing the remnants of the Great Cosmos Corps and taking over the territories of the Great Cosmos Corps according to the data. Since nothing else would go wrong, Han Xiao left the rest to the players, and he no longer paid attention to it.

Looking around, apart from the various operators, the only two Officers in the room were Feidin and Aurora.

Aurora was currently seated in front of a control panel with her head crooked as though she was about to fall asleep. She did not need to manage the autopilot, and she was already drifting off to dreamland. On the other side, Feidin sat on the sofa and had his eyes shut in meditation. Who knew if he was training his mental force or bickering with Chen Xing in his head?

The other Black Star Guards spent most of their time in the combat room under the lead of Hila. The exploration had already been going on for more than a month, and after the initial excitement during the starting phase, the others could not be bothered to monitor the progress carefully every day. Hila truly could not stand slacking off beside Han Xiao every day and thus dragged the other Black Star Guards to train bitterly with her.

"A woman with the motivation to improve is still pretty attractive." Han Xiao shook his head and entered the quantum network to contact Planet Aquamarine.

The Black Star Army had already set up a quantum network in the Dawn Star Cluster, and he was able to communicate with the Shattered Star Ring through his army's channel. He did not have to go through the Crimson Dynasty as a middleman anymore.

Floating Dragon had remained at Planet Aquamarine for more than a month, and Han Xiao's main purpose of contacting Planet Aquamarine was to ask them about Floating Dragon's situation.

Not too long later, Bennett came online. After a period of not contacting Bennett, his voice suddenly seemed full of energy.

Bennett reported the recent situation. Floating Dragon had begun their expansion over the past month, and a large number of people and financial groups had flooded over because of Floating Dragon's name. Because of this, Planet Aquamarine had received new opportunities for growth.

With Planet Aquamarine's current development speed, Bennett felt that he would be able to move his plan of having colonial planets forward by a few decades. While this was not an easy task to a native civilization like theirs, it would be much easier for them to do so with the aid of so many galactic organizations.

With Floating Dragon's protection, the immigrants of the colonial planets would be protected, and Bennett planned to use five years to digest the benefits brought about by Floating Dragon before officially starting his plan to expand outward. He called it the five-year plan, and Han Xiao was truly shocked when he heard it.

After reporting the development of Planet Aquamarine, Bennett suddenly mentioned something else.

"With regards to the extremist group of the Star Pupil Holy Race attacking Planet Aquamarine, I have already gathered the necessary evidence and am planning to mention it during the upcoming Civilization Conference..."

"Not bad. We must make good use of our status." Han Xiao nodded. Since Psyker's race had made a mistake, there was nothing wrong with making the leader take the blame for it.

"I will join in the meeting through a holographic projection. Black Star, would it be convenient for you to join in the meeting as well?"

Psyker was a Beyond Grade A figure after all, and Bennett felt that his status was not sufficient to deal with Psyker. Since Black Star was the representative of Planet Aquamarine, it was normal for him to participate in the meeting too.

"Me? Haha, of course it's convenient. I have been extremely free recently." Han Xiao chuckled.

Joining the meeting personally did not sound too bad. He would be able to personally witness Psyker's expression.

Chapter 833: Shattered Star Ring Civilization Conference

Shattered Star Ring Civilization Conference was the Civilization Conference that was set up by the seven large Star Cluster civilizations in the Shattered Star Ring. The motive of the conference was to make it easier to manage the Star Field. The three Universal Civilizations usually would not interfere with the everyday affairs of the Star Field, and the Star Cluster civilizations were usually the ones to deal with the day to day issues.

The managers of the Shattered Star Ring were the seven Star Cluster civilizations and they were in charge of mediating the conflicts of the various Star System civilizations. Although their motive was to help everyone resolve their conflicts, the Civilization Conference was usually just a debate session where all the civilizations would make use of this opportunity to argue about almost everything and anything. However, they had rarely solved any problems.

During the secret war that had occurred not too long ago, even Purple Crystal and Klent, who were supposed to be the judges, had personally fought each other, and the usefulness of the Civilization Conference could easily be seen.

After all, the Shattered Star Ring was the border of the discovered universe, and chaos lingered in the region. A very long time ago, the various civilizations would send their envoys to participate in the conference personally, but after the seven Star Cluster civilizations could not stand the brawls that were happening during the conference, they changed the meeting method to using holographic projections.

Since everyone was only a projection, it was impossible for them to break out into a fight.

In any case, the Civilization Conference was a few days away, and this would be the first time that Planet Aquamarine had joined the conference.

Usually, only Star System level civilizations would have the right to enter the conference, but Han Xiao had made a deal with the various Star Cluster civilizations to let Planet Aquamarine have the rights to enter the conference. Planet Aquamarine was also the only civilization to enter the conference at the level of a surface civilization.

A few days later, the meeting was held as per usual, and Han Xiao received a notice from Purple Crystal. He then logged in to his own holographic projection account and joined the meeting.

Buzz...

An electrical buzzing sound could be heard, and Han Xiao felt a blinding light flash in his face. The next moment, he could share the view of his holographic projection, and the scene of the conference was in his eyes.

A circular meeting venue appeared before his eyes, and it looked a little like the structure of a colosseum. The black colored chairs were arranged neatly in a circular formation with the chairs in the middle being the lowest. The chairs gradually increased in height as it got to the outside like a staircase.

Surrounding the meeting venue was the starry sky of the universe, and the shrunken down star map of the Shattered Star Ring formed the backdrop of the room.

Han Xiao lowered his head and realized that his projection was already seated down on his own seat with Bennett being seated next to him. A golden 'Planet Aquamarine' sign was placed on the table in front of them, and both of their seats were located at quite a high point. They could see the entire venue, and the various representatives from the other civilizations were slowly coming online. The representatives from the different civilizations were seated a distance away from each other, and they were not squeezed together.

"This is the venue for the Shattered Star Ring Civilization Conference..." Bennett let out a sigh of admiration, and he turned around to greet Han Xiao. "Black Star, you are finally online."

"The meeting hadn't started yet. I came too early."

Han Xiao then looked down, and his gaze swept past the center of the venue. The representatives of the seven Star Cluster civilizations were already online, and they were waiting for the representatives of the other civilizations to appear.

Han Xiao then turned around and asked, "How long have you been here?"

"I was the earliest batch to be here," Bennett said. "This is my first time joining a meeting of such a level, and I am a little nervous, so I came earlier to take a look."

He naturally would not be nervous because of the majestic setting but only felt the pressure of having the responsibilities of Planet Aquamarine on his shoulders.

Han Xiao smiled. This is my first time witnessing the Civilization Conference as well.

All the famous civilizations in the Star Field were gathered in a single hall, and most of the players did not have the opportunity to join such a meeting in his previous life, including him.

"Black Star, thank you," Bennett suddenly said with a solemn tone. "If not for you, it'd probably take a few centuries or millenniums for Planet Aquamarine to have a seat in this place."

"You don't need to stand on ceremony. We are only each taking our own needs." Han Xiao blatantly pointed out that he was only doing so for benefits. He then patted Bennett on the shoulder instinctively, but his palm passed through Bennett's shoulders. He had forgotten that both of them were only holographic projections at this moment.

Bennett nodded and did not say anything else. He would not reduce his gratitude toward Han Xiao just because of Han Xiao's words. He had been through many things in life and understood this simple logic—an individual's motive was not as important as their actions.

While both of them were chatting, many representatives from the other civilizations also noticed Han Xiao's presence and looked over with complicated gazes.

In the venue, Planet Aquamarine was an oddball, and Han Xiao had a cooperative relationship with many of the civilizations present. All the civilizations were aware of how Han Xiao had helped Planet Aquamarine join the Civilization Conference, and they could not help but be envious of Planet Aquamarine's natural advantage.

They had the protection of the Beyond Grade A Black Star and were now the main camp of Floating Dragon. Just why did such a small planet have such good luck?

But despite their envy and jealousy, it was undeniable that Planet Aquamarine only managed to gain a seat there because of their own abilities. The civilizations present would not look down on Planet Aquamarine at all.

Not too long later, everyone finally arrived, and the chattering subsided.

At this moment, the representative from one of the Star Clusters stood up, and his voice was projected through the amplifiers.

"I am very happy to meet so many familiar friends today. Hmm, compared to the previous meeting, the number of people present hasn't decreased. It seems like the security of the Shattered Star Ring has improved..."

Everyone had a cold expression on their face. This joke was truly too cold and not funny at all.

"Perhaps everyone has noticed that we have a new member in our midst." The representative then looked toward Han Xiao and briefly introduced him. "Planet Aquamarine civilization, Aquamarine Federation, representative of his civilization... His Excellency Black Star."

Everyone then looked over and nodded respectfully.

Han Xiao waved his hands and looked around. As he saw Psyker who was seated in the seat for the Star Pupil Holy Race, he raised his hand to wave.

Psyker pretended not to see a thing and remained expressionless.

"His Excellency Black Star is someone that we are all familiar with, so there's no need for me to give an introduction. Since everyone is present, let's start the meeting and discuss the first matter..."

Following which, the various delegates began to raise the issues that they had already prepared. The majority of these issues were trade conflicts, border conflicts, foreign affairs conflicts, and other problems that were nothing new.

The representatives chosen by the civilizations were all extremely eloquent, and every single proposal could be argued for over half a day before coming to a conclusion that the matter had to be delayed to a later date.

The process was long and cumbersome, but Bennett sat up straight to study every detail of the meeting to gain experience.

Han Xiao had already begun daydreaming a long time ago.

After waiting for a long time, the ones queuing in front of them had finally said their piece, and it was now their turn.

"Proposal number CL7984D66 from the Planet Aquamarine. Please give a brief description of the proposal," the Purple Crystal representative said with a smile.

Bennett stood up slowly and began reading the material that he had prepared beforehand. He briefly explained the actions of the Avitan Souls extremists, and his voice reverberated in the meeting venue.

Following which, he looked at Psyker and said with a deep voice, "We discovered psionic explosives in the spaceship of these extremists, and the strength of these explosives was sufficient to destroy Planet Aquamarine. For such high-grade military weapons to appear in the hands of the extremists, we have reason to believe that these weapons came from the hands of the Star Pupil Holy Race, and the actions of these extremists were instructed by the Star Pupil Holy Race. Planet Aquamarine feels that the Star Pupil Holy Race wishes to go against the [Treaty of Cosmic Civilizations (Seventh Revision)] and wipe out a civilization protected by the treaty..."

The sponsor of Avitan Souls was actually an opponent of the Star Pupil Holy Race, a Star Cluster civilization called Talos. However, Bennett had insisted that the sponsor was the Star Pupil Holy Race so that Psyker would take the blame for the matter.

An odd look could be seen on the faces of everyone present. They were all experienced individuals and knew that it was impossible for Psyker to have done something like this.

A surface civilization that was accepted into the conference by exception actually pouring dirty water on a Beyond Grade A during their first meeting? They were far too bold. If only they could also have a Beyond Grade A Super as their backer. That way, they would be able to do whatever they wished.

The seven Star Cluster civilizations then exchanged glances, and six of them looked at the one of the representatives. He was the representative of the Talos Civilization.

The representative of Talos then looked at Psyker and asked with a smile that did not seem like a smile, "Representative of the Star Pupil Holy Race, what do you have to say?"

"They are maligning me." Psyker had a calm look on his face and replied slowly. "I would never go against the treaty and have no reason to attack Planet Aquamarine. Those extremists weren't following my orders."

"How do you explain this incident?"

"If I were to make a conjecture, this should be the actual reason. Planet Avitan suffered from an ambush recently, and the Evolution Cube was lost during the process. Black Star then managed to snatch the Evolution Cube in the end..."

As he said that, Psyker glared at Han Xiao coldly before continuing. "Because of the ambush, a portion of the survivors of Planet Avitan became extremists who wanted to take revenge. In the eyes of the Star Pupil Holy Race, the Evolution Cube is our national treasure, and Black Star snatched our national treasure away. Thus, the extremist group blamed the matter on him, and this matter is their personal action. It has nothing to do with the officials of the Star Pupil Holy Race. If Planet Aquamarine insists that I am the culprit behind this matter, please provide proper evidence."

Han Xiao chuckled and said, "Dead men tell no tales. Do you wish to absolve yourself from guilt with just a few words?"

"Ah, likewise to you. Since dead men tell no tales, you are also trying to frame me with a few illogical arguments," Psyker said coldly.

The Talos representative then said, "Let us place this matter aside for now. Regardless of whether the Star Pupil Holy Race ordered the assault, the attackers were indeed from your race. Am I right?"

Psyker took a deep breath and nodded. "Although they are from our race, we..."

The Talos representative interrupted Psyker. "You don't need to say anything else. The Star Pupil Holy Race is extremely different from other races. Your race should be a highly united one, and the presence of an extremist group is a result of your mismanagement."

"... This is my internal affair, and I will personally disband the extremist group called Avitan Souls. None of you have the right to intervene in anything else," Psyker said with a frosty tone.

"If you need, we can send some forces to help you wipe out the extremist force as a friendly neighbor."

"... That's not necessary." Psyker was shocked. Who would not know what your intention is? You dare mention such a matter in front of so many people? Don't you feel any shame?

The Talos representative then chuckled and got back to the main topic. "Let's talk about your measures to rectify your mistake in the future. We are now discussing your responsibility. This extremist group is from your race, and they were using their identities as citizens of the Star Pupil Holy Race when carrying out the attack. I believe that the Star Pupil Holy Race should take responsibility for this incident."

In truth, regardless of whether they were from the same race or citizens of the race, these were not important factors at all. However, the Talos representative wanted to target the Star Pupil Holy Race by harping on about this matter.

He was not the only one who did so in fact.

"I think so too," the Purple Crystal representative said.

"I agree." The representatives from a few other Star Clusters also nodded.

Purple Crystal was speaking on behalf of Planet Aquamarine because of Han Xiao, and the other Star Cluster civilizations only wanted to deal a blow to the Star Pupil Holy Race.

Because the Star Pupil Holy Race had the support of the Arcane Church, their development was extremely rapid, and they had a chance to become the eighth Star Cluster civilization. The others were not willing to allow someone else to share benefits with them.

As such, all of them stood on the same side and made use of this opportunity to create trouble for the Star Pupil Holy Race.

The other representatives remained silent at this moment as they understood what was going on.

Who asked the members of your race to try and destroy another planet and even leave evidence behind?

If someone wanted to blow up their mother planet, they would also blame the masters for not reining in the crazy dogs properly.

All of a sudden, Psyker became the target of everyone's criticism, and even Bennett was shocked by the scene. He had originally thought that he would just engage in a small squabble with Psyker but never expected so many people to speak on his behalf. He could not help but look at Han Xiao.

Han Xiao smiled, having expected such a scene. He knew that exposing this matter would give the other Star Cluster Civilizations an opportunity to exploit. The Shattered Star Ring had already been split up by the seven Star Cluster Civilizations, and they were not willing to allow a new member to share the pie with them. As such, even if he did not have any evidence, they would side with him.

Psyker's face was extremely ugly. Psyker naturally understood the logic of 'giving a dog a bad name then hanging him', but he truly did not have sufficient grounds to fight back. The other party was the victim, and he was indeed in the wrong.

He could not help but curse the Avitan Souls. Those brats did not think about the trouble that their actions would cause to the civilization and had dragged him down to take the rap for them. It was truly a waste to allow them to evolve back then.

"How do you guys want to deal with this matter?" Psyker said with frustration.

The Talos representative then said, "I think that you need to make a public apology to Planet Aquamarine and provide them with some compensation."

"Compensation and an apology? Impossible," Psyker said with a deep voice. "I can make a donation at most."

A donation and compensation had completely different meanings.

As the leader of a civilization, he was the image of the Star Pupil Holy Race, and he had to consider many different things. It was impossible for him to make a public apology just because of the actions of an extremist group. It was just like how Godora would never apologize because of DarkStar's actions. Furthermore, Psyker was a Beyond Grade A Super, and doing so would harm his prestige. Thus, he could not lower his head so easily.

Bennett then snapped back to his senses and said under Han Xiao's instructions, "Planet Aquamarine strongly condemns the Star Pupil Holy Race for their actions and does not accept such an insincere conclusion."

"Then there isn't a need to continue talking about this."

Psyker looked at Han Xiao coldly and suddenly went offline.

The Star Pupil Holy Race had the backing of the Arcane Church, and the Civilization Conference had a limited restriction on them. It was impossible for the Civilization Conference to force him to lower his head. At the same time, Psyker could not do as he wished and would also suffer some losses.

After this incident, it would be far more difficult for the Star Pupil Holy Race to seek cooperation. He had lost the Evolution Cube, and the support of the Arcane Church would also decrease. As such, this storm was extremely disadvantageous to their development.

Furthermore, Talos would make use of this opportunity to publicize this matter and sway public opinion against the Star Pupil Holy Race.

In Psyker's eyes, the culprit of all this was Han Xiao. If not for Han Xiao being insistent on making him take the blame, the situation would not have progressed like that.

Psyker's enmity toward Han Xiao increased to the next level.

On Han Xiao's side, his interface gave him a notification. His favorability with the Star Pupil Holy Race had fallen by 800 points and was now -1,250 points. Their relationship went from [Hostile] to [Enemies].

Psyker was indeed infuriated. Han Xiao shook his head. Planet Aquamarine was his 'mother planet', and it was impossible for him to swallow such a grievance without doing anything. Since Psyker and the Arcane Church would not let go of the Evolution Cube, they were destined to be enemies, and he would not mind their enmity being deeper.

If Planet Aquamarine was really destroyed, Psyker still would not apologize or pay any compensation. He might even gloat at his demise. However, there was no right or wrong to him, and Han Xiao did not think that Psyker's actions were wrong.

"I wonder how he will retaliate..." Han Xiao pondered to himself.

Planet Aquamarine was protected by the Peace Treaty, and Psyker would not take action against anyone else. If Psyker wanted to fight back, Psyker would definitely have his sights set on Han Xiao.

Aesop said that the Arcane Church would send people after him, and Psyker would definitely be a member of the party since he was able to lock onto his position.

Han Xiao decided to let the main camp keep a look out for Psyker's movements as it was akin to monitoring the Arcane Church's actions.

At the same time, on the mother planet of the Star Pupil Holy Race. Psyker disconnected from the meeting venue, and his expression was extremely ugly.

After thinking for a while, Psyker sent a message to the Arcane Church.

"I will agree to that matter."

The Arcane Church had given him a mission recently, and Psyker had been thinking about it. He had only made a decision at that moment.

Psyker's cold expression could be seen on the screen of the communicator.

"Black Star, you should stay in the Flickering World and never return."

Chapter 834: Arcane Church's Trace

Leaving the conference halfway was obviously extremely disrespectful to the other members present, but the seven Star Cluster civilizations and the other members weren't too bothered. The Star Pupil Holy Race had become the public enemy, and Psyker was only using his actions to show his dissatisfaction. He would still come online obediently during the next meeting.

Since their target was gone, this proposal could only be postponed to a later date, and Bennett sat back down.

The meeting continued, and the next proposal was raised. The atmosphere of the meeting had become more peaceful.

All the other proposals after this did not have anything to do with him anymore, so Han Xiao temporarily cut off from the viewpoint of the projection and began browsing the forums.

After another long wait, the meeting on the first day was finally over. Every time a Civilization Conference was held, they would have to meet for a few days before being able to discuss all the accumulated proposals. Han Xiao only intended to show his face for the first day, and he would not need to be present for all the other meetings. Bennett alone would be enough.

Disconnecting from the long-range holographic projection, Han Xiao closed the forums and thought to himself, The Star Pupil Holy Race was criticized by Planet Aquamarine, but the future matters will have nothing to do with Planet Aquamarine.

Since nothing had actually happened, it would be impossible for them to actually do anything to Psyker. Han Xiao was not counting on the Star Pupil Holy Race providing compensation or a donation. The influence of Planet Aquamarine was still too weak, and even after criticizing them, Psyker would not be too affected by it.

After this matter was mentioned, the ones who would cause trouble for Psyker would not be Planet Aquamarine but the Talos Civilization.

The Talos Civilization secretly sponsored Avitan Souls so that those extremists would create trouble for the Star Pupil Holy Race. Although they did not instruct Avitan Souls to attack Planet Aquamarine, this unexpected situation was to their advantage, and they could make use of this matter to create trouble.

Han Xiao got Bennett to criticize Psyker to give the Talos Civilization an excuse, and the Talos Civilization understood his intentions. They had wanted to deal with the Star Pupil Holy Race a long time ago, and standing up for Planet Aquamarine could also win them Han Xiao's favor.

Thus, Planet Aquamarine did not have to do anything after the first day and only had to watch from the side.

Han Xiao then contacted Ames and asked her about Floating Dragon's situation.

Both of them talked for half an hour before hanging up.

Walking to the 3D star map, Han Xiao looked at the map of the Garu Star Cluster. The explored green region was still extremely small, and it looked like two toothpicks sticking out from a green blob. These two 'toothpicks' were the two long distance routes that were currently under construction.

"Hadavy's Special Task Force needs another three months before they can complete the long distance stargate..." Han Xiao stroked his chin and pondered to himself.

According to his plan, the Special Task Force arriving at the east of the Garu Star Cluster would be the first phase.

According to his understanding of the Garu Star Cluster, there should not be another huge storm like the Great Cosmos Corps again, and they would have a calm exploration until they had explored about eighty percent of the Star Systems.

Time flew by.

Three months later, in the Crimson Dynasty Ruler's office, Urranrell currently had a report in her hands, and she was reprimanding one of the upper echelons with a stern voice.

"The Federation of Light is moving sneakily and has entered our territory. How are you going to take care of this matter? Just watch from the side and let them do as they please? I asked you to keep guard, not retreat all the way! Come up with a plan immediately!"

"Let me think, let me think..."

Urranrell's eyes were extremely stern. The exploration of the Flickering World had only been going on for a few months, and the Federation of Light could no longer sit still. They had begun applying pressure on the dynasty from the economic, political, and military side. They were prepared to snatch benefits from the dynasty while the dynasty's attention was fixed on exploring the new Star Field.

This was only the beginning. The dynasty would definitely invest even more manpower and resources in the exploration, and the Federation of Light would increase the intensity of their operations to make things difficult for the dynasty.

Although this situation was within Urranrell's expectations, it was something avoidable. Both the Federation of Light and the Crimson Dynasty were at the same level, and their strength was equal. It was extremely difficult for everything to go smoothly and perfectly. If the dynasty wanted to have some reward, they needed to pay the appropriate price. Urranrell had already prepared herself mentally for this.

Beep beep.

The internal comms line rang.

"Your Excellency, the Chief Commander of the exploration army Tarrokov is on the line."

Urranrell then waved her hand and got the official in front of her to leave. The official felt as though he was pardoned of his crime and hurriedly left the office. Only Urranrell remained in the room.

"Patch it through." Urranrell nodded.

The next moment, Tarrokov's figure appeared inside the room, and he gave a military salute to Urranrell.

"Tarrokov, how is the progress for the exploration of the Flickering World?"

The exploration of the Flickering World was of strategic importance to the Crimson Dynasty, and Urranrell was extremely concerned about the situation.

"The information has already been sent to you, and I am here to give you a brief report..."

Tarrokov then began explaining.

Urranrell glanced at the report while looking at the information and nodded.

"In summary, Renault and Crown are being explored by the forces of the dynasty and Klent. Our progress is only average. On the contrary, the Black Star Army, which chose the Garu Star Cluster, has discovered a large number of resource rich planets over the past four months and even took over the territory of a local organization, saving us a great deal of effort. Furthermore, the Black Star Army didn't bother about their own losses and are constructing a long distance stargate for the convenience of future exploration squads," Tarrokov said.

Urranrell placed down the information in her hands and said with a satisfied look, "Not bad. He is a reliable ally."

With a basis of comparison, she was extremely satisfied with Han Xiao's efficiency.

"The Black Star Army is an ally worthy of grooming. We should increase our support for them in all aspects."

Although Tarrokov seemed to have received some benefits from the Black Star Army and always spoke highly of them, Urranrell was not bothered about the details as long as the Black Star Army produced results.

"Apart from this, I have something else to report," Tarrokov suddenly said with a deep voice. "We've noticed traces of stowaways."

The stowaways that he referred to were those who secretly entered the Flickering World without approval from the dynasty.

Urranrell's eyes narrowed. "Are you sure they aren't natives?"

Tarrokov shook his head and said, "Although I do not have much evidence, our troops stationed in the universe belt between the Shattered Star Ring and Flickering World discovered traces of warp speed hyperdrive by an unknown force. Their technological capabilities have obviously reached the level of a Star Cluster, and they should be arriving in the Flickering World very soon. Some others may have already arrived at the Flickering World before this but weren't discovered by us."

"The Federation of Light and Arcane Church have indeed taken action," Urranrell said.

"I think that they will avoid the first three Star Clusters that we have chosen and explore the Star Clusters located deep within the Star Field," Tarrokov said. "They want to swallow our Star Field on the sly and avoid coming into contact with us."

"You're right," Urranrell said slowly. "Send out our forces to patrol the universe belt between the Shattered Star Ring and Flickering World. Destroy any stargates built by the enemy that you can find."

Those stowaways were probably planning to create their own secret stargate to connect the Flickering World to the outside so that they could send a large troop quickly in the future. The hidden stargates would usually be hidden within the universe belt between the two Star Fields.

The Crimson Dynasty had publicly forbidden other organizations from privately setting up their own stargate because of such a consideration. The most effective way to deal with stowaways would be to destroy their stargates and ensure that the control of the stargates remained firmly in the dynasty's hands.

The only way to maximize the dynasty's benefits was to ensure a monopoly on transportation.

Tarrokov shook his head in response. "We will need more manpower."

"I know." Urranrell nodded. "I will deploy more troops to head to the Flickering World. It is also time for our second batch of allies to move out."

At the same time, an Arcane Church fleet had secretly arrived at the border of the Flickering World.

"We've finally arrived! Contact the branch division. Have they chosen a location in the desolate universe belt?"

"Reporting to the captain, the location has been decided, and they are only waiting for us."

They required two stargates to form a new path, and stowaway troops would usually split up into two groups. One group would choose a location for their secret stargate, and this would be the 'entrance'.

The troops that arrived at the Flickering World would then build the 'exit'.

"Very good. Make sure that we avoid all the detectors of the Crimson Dynasty. Go around the Dawn Star Cluster and head to the desolate universe belt near the Garu Star Cluster to construct a stargate. We will also build a temporary base."

The Arcane Church also wanted to set their sights on the Flickering World, but this was a long-term job. At the same time, the Arcane Church was even more interested in the Evolution Cube.

They had chosen to set up a stargate near the Garu Star Cluster so that it would be easy for them to store their army.

It would only be convenient for them to send out Beyond Grade A Supers after constructing their stargates. After all, an expert of such a level would not be willing to spend a few months slowly crossing the desolate universe belt.

Black Star had already proven himself to be someone extremely difficult to deal with. In order to guarantee their success, the Arcane Church had sent out more than one or two Beyond Grade A Supers.

Of course, the three Universal Civilizations kept an eye on each other's Beyond Grade A combatants, and the moment any one of them displayed any strange movements, the other two parties would be alerted.

If they wanted to allow their Beyond Grade A Supers to move sneakily, they needed to find a reason to fool others.

Chapter 835: Four Months

Ever since the players took over the remaining territories of the Great Cosmos Corps and set up a long distance stargate, Han Xiao had led his forces to the middle region of the star map. The famous planets within the center region of the Star Cluster were much greater, and their quality was higher.

One of these planets was called Planet Shining Gold, which had been extremely prosperous in Han Xiao's previous life. It was one of the first-rate planets that the dynasty had in the Garu Star Cluster and was an iconic planet of the Flickering World. There was also Planet Auspicious Forest, which was a transit station within the Garu Star Cluster. During its most prosperous time, it had over five hundred stargate entrances and was the heart of the Star Cluster.

Apart from this, Han Xiao had also occupied many resource rich planets that were famous for producing various valuable resources.

In his previous life, these famous planets had an important status in the Garu Star Cluster, and the dynasty might take back these planets after opening up the Flickering World to the public. But during the exploration period, these planets were all the territory of the Black Star Army, and the Black Star Army had the right to enjoy the special produce of these planets.

The exploration had already been going on for four months, and the progress of the various exploration squads was similar. The Bloodshed Land had taken a steady approach in their exploration and had almost completed the exploration of the Jeraton Star System. Although they had pretty decent rewards, the outcome was within the dynasty's expectations, and it would not cause too big a storm. In comparison, even though Han Xiao's exploration squad had taken the approach of spreading out their forces, which resulted in taking a longer time to explore a single Star System, Han Xiao had managed to provide the dynasty with quite a number of surprises because he had managed to find a large number of famous planets from his previous life.

Because of this, the dynasty increased their support for him as well.

Han Xiao had heard rumors about the Klent exploration team mimicking his method and sending out troops to the planets of the other regions. However, it was a pity that they were not familiar with the situation on the other planets and did not have good results.

Over the past four months, the benefits of the Flickering World had begun to show. The rewards that the Black Star Army received from the Flickering World almost rivaled the combined total of the other armies.

As more and more planets were explored, their rewards continued to snowball.

Countless uninhabited planets were waiting to be excavated. If not, why would they say that the Flickering World was a huge opportunity?

The gains of the army soared rapidly, and after the exploration team sent these earnings back to the main camp in the Shattered Star Ring, Sylvia began to expand the army even further under Han Xiao's instructions. They attracted more new members and increased the scale of their training camp.

On the players' side, as the resource rich planets increased in numbers, the guilds also ran out of manpower and could only selectively choose the planets to mine on. The best resource rich planets were naturally taken by the four great guilds and the others by the first-rate guilds. The Australian and Russian guilds were bullied badly and no longer wished to play on the same planet as any of the powerful Chinese guilds. Thus, they chose a few lousier resource rich planets and competed with the second-rate Chinese guilds instead.

Over the past four months, the average level of the players had gone up a great deal, and Maple Moon, who had received bountiful rewards from the hidden mission, was the highest leveled player. She was already at level 113 and only needed seven more levels to reach the max level.

With Maple Moon as an example, all the players searched for hidden missions like crazy, and there were a few who had indeed managed to find some. However, it was a pity that there was no reward for the second [Bold Explorer] skill fragment.

Han Xiao had not remained idle over the past four months either. The experience punishment of the Evolution Cube would end in eight months, so he was not in a rush to level up.

Apart from monitoring the progress of the exploration and scrolling through the forums, Han Xiao spent most of his time in his workshop, expanding his mechanical army.

Currently, his mechanical army had already exceeded ten million soldiers in number, and their attributes were extremely powerful. Under the boost of his mechanical force, this army of his had the strength to wipe out a weaker Star System Civilization.

Among the five main classes, the destructiveness of a Mechanic was the greatest toward a civilization. The other four classes were more suitable to fight a single target, and only a powerful Beyond Grade A Mechanic had the ability to fight a large-scale galactic war.

Han Xiao was currently standing in front of the 3D star map, waiting for a special piece of news.

Today was a special day as the Special Task Force that Hadavy was leading would complete the construction of the long distance stargate. He was waiting for Hadavy's word.

But before news from Hadavy could arrive, Tarrokov contacted him.

Beep beep!

Han Xiao looked at his communicator and could only pick up the call with resignation.

"Chief commander, what's the matter?"

"I need to inform you about something. We found traces of stowaways."

"Stowaways? They should be from the organizations who ignored the dynasty's warning and want to have a share of the Flickering World, right?"

This was something that the players found out from the background description in his previous life. This matter happened during the version update period, and the players did not participate in the event. When the players joined in, the Flickering World had already opened to the outside world, and the other organizations were allowed to enter the Flickering World.

In the dynasty's records, they had fought a long battle with the stowaways. The Star Field was far too big, and there were too many regions to explore. As such, the dynasty was not able to completely uproot the stowaways. Even if they could get rid of one batch, another batch would arrive very quickly.

Tarrokov nodded and said, "It should be the forces of some super Star Cluster civilizations. You should keep an eye out for them and report to me if you find any stowaways. We must find their secret stargates, and we will request aid from your troops if necessary."

"Okay."

A new mission immediately popped up on Han Xiao's interface.

_____________________

You have triggered [Stowaways' Clue] (Repeatable)!

Mission Introduction: A new Star Field is a treasure trove, and every organization wants a share of it. No one is willing to see the Crimson Dynasty swallow all the benefits alone, and even if the Flickering World is the Crimson Dynasty's territory in name, it is impossible to stop their greed. As one of the dynasty's allies, the stowaways' infiltration is also an opportunity for you. The dynasty needs your help.

Mission Requirements: Hand in all information related to stowaways, kill a batch of stowaways, or destroy the secret stargates.

Reward: 2,000,000 – 50,000,000 Experience and 50 – 700 the Crimson Dynasty Contribution Points

Remark: This is a branch mission of the [Flickering World].

_____________________

This was a repeatable mission, and he would receive a reward every time he dealt with stowaways. The rewards were only so-so, but Han Xiao was the most interested in the dynasty Contribution Points.

However, stowaways were stealthy in their actions and extremely difficult to find. Han Xiao can only try his luck. Furthermore, the stowaways were not natives, and if they set up a secret stargate, it would only be possible to destroy the stargate with a battle.

Han Xiao only intended to provide the clues and was not planning to pick a fight with the super Star Cluster civilizations. However, the dynasty were not afraid of offending them and would be the most suitable party to do so.

"The Arcane Church should also be included among the stowaways..."

Aesop had prophesied that the Arcane Church would bring him danger in the Flickering World, and Han Xiao was concerned about it.

If the Arcane Church wanted to deal with me, they would definitely have to send a large force. Because they'll need to build up their forces, they won't take action soon. However, I'd better remain vigilant during this period, Han Xiao thought to himself.

Psyker was able to locate him, and the Arcane Church would definitely get Psyker to join them. Thus, observing Psyker's whereabouts would be the most direct way to find out when the Arcane Church was planning to attack.

It was a pity that the [Observer's Mark] that he had placed on Psyker's body had already been removed. If not, things would have been much easier for him. Although Psyker was not able to remove it on his own, he could feel that he was being spied on. Psyker had already found out that he was the culprit, and it was impossible for Psyker to ignore the matter after a good half a year. Psyker must have gotten someone from the Arcane Church to get rid of the [Observer's Mark] for him. After all, Austin was not the only Beyond Grade A Mage.

Han Xiao conveyed his worries to Tarrokov, and Tarrokov replied with a smile as though he had already expected it.

"The dynasty has also considered the possibility that the Arcane Church will try to snatch the Evolution Cube when you are in the Flickering World. Thus, the dynasty will keep a close eye on the movements of the Beyond Grade A Supers of the Arcane Church. Furthermore, Her Excellency has already sent out a second wave of troops to the Flickering World, which includes many of the dynasty's allies. We will also send out a Beyond Grade A Super that is a direct subordinate of the dynasty to follow you and protect you temporarily."

The second batch of allies... it seems like the competition is here.

On account of the Evolution Cube, the dynasty sent manpower to protect him. However, Han Xiao knew that the dynasty would prefer him to not run around with the Evolution Cube.

After retrieving that ownerless Universal Treasure, I shall return to Planet Lighthouse for a period of time...

Since he knew that the enemy wanted to deal with him, Han Xiao decided to be on the safer side. After all, the Arcane Church was not that easy to deal with.

Thus, it would be best for him to remain on the dynasty's outpost, Planet Lighthouse, rather than running all around. Furthermore, he would still be present in the Flickering World and could continue to monitor the progress of the exploration.

"Please thank Ruler Urranrell for me." Han Xiao was caught up in his thoughts but did not forget to be polite.

"Haha, the Ruler recently checked on our progress, and she is extremely satisfied with you," Tarrokov said with a smile.

After having a casual chat for a while, Han Xiao hung up.

Right at this moment, Hadavy finally sent news.

After waiting for four months, the stargate was finally complete!

"Good job!"

Han Xiao was overjoyed. With this passageway, Han Xiao could finally obtain the ownerless Universal Treasure.

Hadavy had also displayed his dissatisfaction in his message. He had not sparred with Han Xiao for four months and was extremely dissatisfied. He wanted to immediately return to Han Xiao's side so that he could be beaten up by Han Xiao. Being in a good mood, Han Xiao immediately promised to beat Hadavy up three times a day and fulfil his wishes.

Han Xiao immediately ordered the fleet to change direction and head toward the stargate.

This news was quickly spread to Senico. However, he was already used to Black Star moving around without any set pattern and did not have any suspicions.

Chapter 837: The Last Witness

Hidden mission... Han Xiao was stunned for a moment. When he then saw the mission reward, surprise appeared on his face. The second [Bold Explorer] Ability Shard‽

Han Xiao immediately turned to look at Feidin, who had all his attention on the Yasre Civilization recording. He gripped his shoulders and shook him vigorously.

"Wha... what are you doing?" Feidin stared at the overjoyed Han Xiao with a puzzled look on his face.

"You, amazing!"

Han Xiao was ecstatic. In his eyes, it was as if Feidin was emitting holy light from all over his body.

There was a slim chance that hidden missions would reward [Bold Explorer] Ability Shards. Over the past few months, the players had discovered quite a number of hidden missions and shared them with him. However, he had never triggered this reward—the goddess of luck loathed him as usual.

With Feidin along with him, the goddess of luck basically deliberately lifted her dress to show Feidin the holy light.

Han Xiao could not help but sigh in his mind. Overflowing charm, exceptional luck, a wife who he could sleep with in his mind, and the goddess of luck willing to be his mistress. Feidin was probably the biggest winner in life throughout the Black Star Army.

Although Nero also had the Advanced Luck Glow...

He was not handsome enough!

"You're still the most reliable." Han Xiao patted Feidin's shoulder heavily with satisfaction on his face.

Feidin's face was filled with question marks.

Seeing that everyone was looking at him with confusion, Han Xiao calmed himself down, coughed, and explained, "This civilization used its holy relic to build this kind of special amber. No one else other than us has visited this planet ever since. This means that this holy relic will be ours. I'm guessing that this is going to be another Universal Treasure."

The others did not know that Han Xiao had come to this planet with a clear goal. They nodded and suspected nothing.

Han Xiao told the machines to search and found the database. Phillip copied all the data inside and finally deciphered the language of the Yasre Civilization.

Having updated the language packs of the translator, they returned to the black disc again and rewatched the recording. This time, they understood what it was about.

"I'm the leader of the Yasreans. Lucky visitors, when you see this recording, we might have already gone extinct. No matter who you are, please watch this recording till the end..."

The mission introduction on the interface had already explained the rough situation, so Han Xiao just filled in the details by watching it again.

The recording talked about the situation of the Yasre Civilization, which was within their expectations. At the end of the recording, the Yasrean hoped that the visitor could complete two things. One was to undo the effects of the Spacetime Amber, and the Yasreans shared their knowledge of the Spacetime Amber to make things easier. However, they had very limited knowledge about this extraterrestrial object that exceeded their understanding.

The second thing was for the visitor to preserve the information about the Yasre Civilization if the Yasreans were extinct so that the traces of their existence would remain.

The group of them had been traveling the universe for many years and were used to the end of civilizations long ago. This was what the universe was; new species were born, and old species went extinct every second. If they would easily be affected every time, they would have no time to do anything else.

However, every civilization was a miracle of life, so they would still respect the final wishes of a civilization when necessary.

Before that, Han Xiao had to first do what he had gone there to do.

With the translation, he knew the location of the Spacetime Amber. Han Xiao told the machines to bring out all of the ambers from every ruins and gather at the location of the Spacetime Amber.

Not long after, they landed at the ruins where the Spacetime Amber was.

Following the images, Han Xiao came to an empty room in the middle of this ruins' central sanctuary. A mural entered his sights. It was about eight meters tall and thirty meters wide. The drawings were about the history of the Yasreans.

One of the images was a meteor-like black stone falling down from the clouds, with a group of tiny people below looking up. Han Xiao hovered up and came before this painting. He extended his hand and touched the meteor on this drawing.

His palm pressed onto the wall, and energy blew away the thick accumulated layer of dust.

Hu!

The dust was blown away.

Han Xiao pressed down heavily and cracked the meteor drawing open. Stones fell onto the ground.

Ka!

He dug out a dim white crystal from behind the wall, which had the same shape as the meteor in the painting.

Looking at the white crystal in his hands, Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

This ordinary looking crystal was the core of the Spacetime Amber. The Yasreans had hidden it in this mural.

You have received [Spacetime Amber].

Spacetime Amber: A Space Wonder object with an unknown origin. It can freeze spacetime and form a solid layer with the appearance of amber around all kinds of things. Energy cost depends on the size of the amber formed. Current Energy Value: 0

"I got it." Han Xiao was thrilled.

This was the easiest to obtain Universal Treasure for him. After all, no one else knew about this thing's existence other than him.

As he landed on the ground, the others surrounded him and sized the Spacetime Amber up with curiosity.

"This is the holy relic that can create amber that can block all kinds of attacks?" Hila sized the Spacetime Amber up. "Why does it not have any energy reaction at all?"

"This thing needs to be charged to be used," Han Xiao explained. He then shot out a powerful flow of energy into the Spacetime Amber in his hands.

Boom!

An invisible impact wave exploded from Han Xiao's body like a tornado. This was the aura that Han Xiao emitted when he released his energy at the maximum capacity.

The Mechanical Force flew into the Spacetime Amber as the dim Spacetime Amber started to gradually light up.

In the past four months, Han Xiao had completed the [Heber Stellar Furnace Cultivation] training. Having spent 3.9 billion EXP, his maximum energy had increased by more than 17,000, which was quite worth it for him.

The Spacetime Amber was like a bottomless pit that could devour an infinite amount of energy. Its energy value slowly grew.

Using the Spacetime Amber required a large amount of energy, but to a Mechanic who had mastered the psionic energy, there was more than enough energy.

Han Xiao thought about it and stopped using his own energy. He took out a few psionic reactors as batteries and linked them with the Spacetime Amber to keep charging it. It seemed like there was no limit to the amount of energy the Spacetime Amber could contain, so he did not worry about overcharging it.

After charging it, the Spacetime Amber finally showed an energy reaction.

With the Spacetime Amber in his hands, Han Xiao could feel the energy inside it. The method to use the Spacetime Amber was very simple; he just had to guide energy within it.

The way the Yasre Civilization used it was quite rough and did not have much to learn from, but Han Xiao recalled the better ways to use it, which the owners of the Spacetime Amber in his previous life had used. He could build a device that had the same frequency as the Spacetime Amber and put the Spacetime Amber in it. He could then connect to the device with Nerves Connection, so he would be able to control the Spacetime Amber with his mind and with greater accuracy.

Han Xiao would be able to easily build such a device, but now was not the time. He was not in a hurry to test the Spacetime Amber's powers, so he decided to complete the hidden mission first.

The group of them walked out of the central sanctuary of the ruins. All of the Yasreans' ambers were moved into those ruins. There were so many of them that they could not see the end of it.

Han Xiao came before a Yasrean and slashed the amber's surface with the Spacetime Amber. The Spacetime Amber cut the translucent amber open with ease.

The Spacetime Amber could freely penetrate the amber created from itself and would not be affected by the frozen spacetime.

Pa!

Like a bubble, this piece of amber dissipated in the air. The Yasrean inside collapsed onto the ground.

Aurora hastily helped him up and said with joy, "There are vital signs. He's still alive."

"His soul has died. Although his body is still alive, he's a living dead man." Hila shook her head.

Unlike Aurora, she could sense the soul of lives, and she knew that the body of this Yasrean was just an empty shell despite it being still alive.

Han Xiao scanned through it. Due to the Spacetime Amber, the body of this Yasrean was maintained at the state it was in before being frozen. Although its brain had stopped working, it did not show any signs of deterioration and was still very much alive like his body. This meant that this person's brain was frozen as well. However, if one's brain was frozen too, there should not be any brain activity at all.

He made a speculation. Since one's body energy would not be used in the amber, maybe it was their soul energy that supported their brain activity. This meant that soul energy being depleted was what caused their mind to die off. The stronger the individual, the more soul energy they had, so they could last longer.

That's not impossible.

Having thought of the origin of the Spacetime Amber, Han Xiao did not think that this was a strange phenomenon.

The effect of the Spacetime Amber came from the Esper Ability of one of the Primordial Ones, whose Esper Ability was 'Spacetime Freeze', which was on the Super High Risk Esper Ability List.

Most of the abilities on the Super High Risk Esper Ability List had existed before, and this Primordial One was the first Esper who was discovered to be able to freeze space and time.

Such abilities were exceedingly rare. It was also a high-level forbidden technique in the Mage class.

Back then, this Primordial One was under the command of an advanced civilization and was killed in action. He had a Primordial One friend whose ability was to modify the properties of objects. That person turned his body into a crystal that would never rot and let it wander the universe as a form of burial. However, somehow, while wandering the universe, this crystal underwent a change that no one knew the cause of. It not only preserved the Primordial One's ability to freeze spacetime, but its ability mutated too and became a Space Wonder. This was the origin of the Spacetime Amber, which the players only found out about in the later versions.

Pulling his thoughts back, Han Xiao used the Spacetime Amber to release all the Yasreans.

After checking through, none of their souls were still alive.

"Sigh, they're all dead." Feidin shook his head.

Han Xiao initially had a little bit of hope, thinking that maybe there would be a protagonist type character among the Yasreans who would make it. Sadly, there were none. In the face of time, it seemed like no one could escape death.

Seeing this, although they were used to seeing the ends of civilizations, they all had no mood to chat and kept silent.

You have released all the Yasreans from the effects of the Spacetime Amber!

[Traces of Existence] Completed!

You have received 1,500,000,000 EXP and 780 Exploration Points.

You have received 1 Random Reward.

You have received 1 Legendary Point.

[Planet Legendary Point (Yasreans)—The Last Witness]: You witnessed the last moment of Yasreans with your own eyes. A civilization's last sign of life vanished right before your eyes. Maybe, in the end, everything vanishes with time, but at least they existed.

Han Xiao sighed. "Phillip, move these bodies onto the ship. Cremate them and release them in the universe."

Feidin looked over. "Are you not preserving specimens using the Spacetime Amber?"

"Their souls dissipated with their civilization. Their bodies should be released too."

Han Xiao had already scanned the bodies of the Yasreans, and there was nothing special. Furthermore, the Spacetime Amber had yet to be shown to the world, so he wanted to keep it as a trump card and not leave any clues behind.

He still remembered that he was a member of the Spacetime Research Council, which preserved the data of all the civilizations that had disappeared throughout history and shared this knowledge with others, so more people would know about these civilizations that had once existed in the universe.

Giving the data to the Spacetime Research Council was probably the best ending for this civilization.

"Master, hum... Do you want me to upload the data of the Yasre Civilization to the Spacetime Research Council database?"

"Upload it."

Han Xiao nodded. He temporarily hid away the data regarding the Spacetime Amber.

With the Spacetime Amber in his hands, they returned to the fleet and headed back.

Inside different spaceships, the bodies of the Yasreans were cremated one after another and then poured into the universe. The fleet dragged along a tail of ash as it departed.

As the fleet entered hyperdrive, Han Xiao rejected Hadavy's request to spar for the time being and locked himself up in the machinery modification room. He planned to first build the portable device of the Spacetime Amber.

As the devices were connected to the Spacetime Amber and detecting its perimeters, Han Xiao stood aside and looked at it.

"This is the second Universal Treasure I have obtained, which means it's a new trump card. The Evolution Cube can make genes evolve, and the Spacetime Amber can freeze spacetime..."

The Evolution Cube could be used for networking, and the Spacetime Amber... could perhaps be used as a tool of intimidation.

This time, Han Xiao suddenly had a flash of insight.

Since the Spacetime Amber could block the transmit of energy, if he covered the Evolution Cube with amber... did that mean Psyker would not be able to sense it?

"Makes sense. Anyway, I don't use the Evolution Cube all the time, and I can unseal it when I need to. But I'm not sure if this will stop Psyker from wanting to take it back... I know the Arcane Church most likely won't give up."

He planned to first give the Spacetime Amber a portable device and then test if this idea would work. After all, building a small device would only take him a few minutes.

Han Xiao temporarily placed this matter aside. He opened the interface and looked at his ability list.

With the two Ability Shards of the [Bold Explorer], this ability was activated. He could activate it when exploring the unknown or studying objects, which would give him partial information of these things.

Cooldown is seven days, and the side effect is decreased Luck for fourteen days. Hehe, not like that makes a difference.

Any side effects that were related to Luck were meaningless to him!

Han Xiao smiled with pride.

Wait a minute, this isn't something to be proud of!

Han Xiao looked at the side.

He decided to use the effect of this ability on the Spacetime Amber.

He knew the origin of the Spacetime Amber, so he could use it to see the accuracy of this ability.

Chapter 838: Inheritance of a Primordial One and Test

You have used ability [Bold Explorer] on [Spacetime Amber]!

You have received the following information...

Everything in his sights suddenly shattered into pieces. His vision was pulled away, and he flew out of the Star System and the Star Field. As if he rode the river of time on an amber boat, he started seeing images of the past.

The next moment, his vision suddenly pulled in like he was falling from the sky. The pieces reformed into an image in front of him—it was a person.

A video started playing before his eyes. This person was on a planet. Beside him were countless enemies, and above him were fleets that shrouded the entire sky. With every movement this person made, an impact wave of energy emitted from his body and froze spacetime, freezing countless spaceships and Supers.

The images were as if Han Xiao was there when it happened. He knew that the person in the image was the Primordial One who became the Spacetime Amber, and these images were the past of the Spacetime Amber.

"I see. So, this ability's method of relaying information is to let me see some images directly. That's quite similar to the Destiny's Child Character Summon Card I once had."

Very soon, this Primordial One met a strong opponent. This time, the image of the battle fast forwarded and skipped the details of the battle, arriving at the results—the consciousness of this Primordial One was heavily damaged, his soul was shattering, and he was at the doorstep of death.

Another Beyond Grade A friend of his arrived and guarded him while retreating.

This time, this Primordial One whose consciousness was already blurry suddenly grabbed onto the shoulder of his friend.

"I'm done for. Don't let my body fall into the hands of the enemies."

"Okay."

The expression of his friend was hidden behind his armor as he pressed onto the body of this Primordial One without hesitation and activated his ability.

This Primordial One lowered all his defenses and did not resist at all. His body crystalized at a visible rate, gradually shrinking into a palm-sized crystal, and was thrown into the cosmic space by his friend.

At this time, the images stopped, and Han Xiao regained his focus.

"Hmm, although I knew about this long ago, if I didn't know, this would basically have uncovered the origin of the Spacetime Amber. That's quite an important piece of information. The ability's effect is quite good."

Han Xiao nodded. This effect was suitable for finding out hidden factors and could even be used multiple times on the same target, each time supposedly getting different pieces of information. If used enough times, there would be a high chance of finding out all the information about an unknown object or matter.

As for the sixty-percent Luck decrease for fourteen days, Han Xiao ignored it completely. His Luck was only one to start with, and it would never become negative, so it made absolutely no difference.

Since the test results were accurate, Han Xiao planned to use this on that set of wormhole data EsGod wanted after the cooldown ended. If he was not able to figure it out the first time, he would use it multiple times until he did.

At this time, a notification popped up on the interface and broke Han Xiao's train of thought.

You have triggered the Hidden Chain Mission [Inheritance of a Primordial One—Spacetime Freezer].

Mission Introduction: Through some means, you came to know that it turns out the Spacetime Amber is the remnant of a Beyond Grade A. He is one of the Primordial Ones—Spacetime Freezer. You have received his inheritance. If you can fulfil his wishes, you will have a deeper understanding of the Spacetime Amber.

Round One Mission Requirements: Find out the wishes of the Spacetime Freezer.

Reward: +1 Soul Connection with the Spacetime Amber

Han Xiao was puzzled.

What the hell is this mission? I have never even heard of it before!

How was this hidden mission triggered? Oh, I get it.

Han Xiao figured out very soon after being surprised for a while.

Although he had known about the origin of the Spacetime Amber since long ago, personal memories had zero influence on the interface. Only when he obtained information through his actions would the interface recognize that as him fulfilling the prerequisite of the hidden mission.

By using [Bold Explorer] and seeing the images about the origin of the Spacetime Amber, he had triggered the mission.

In his previous life, no player had ever obtained the Spacetime Amber, so of course, no one knew that this mission existed. He was the first person to ever trigger this mission.

As for the Soul Connection, Han Xiao knew what it was. It was more common among Mages and Psychics, and it could be understood as the affinity with a certain object. For example, the higher the Soul Connection one had with a certain item, the more powerful that item would be when that person used it, and the easier it would be for that person to control that item.

There was an example right under his nose—Psyker and the Evolution Cube. Having controlled the Evolution Cube for such a long time, Psyker had planted a deep psychic mark on the Evolution Cube long ago and could receive benefits from the Evolution Cube that strengthened his psychic power. This was because Psyker's Soul Connection with the Evolution Cube was very high.

In Han Xiao's previous life, this function only became available in the later versions, and only some special equipment or items had Soul Connections. However, this was not absolute. If a player had a normal object on them all the time, they might still be able to create a Soul Connection with that item.

"I'm not a Psychic nor Mage, so god knows when I would have formed a Soul Connection with this thing. This mission skipped the hardest part for me. From a certain perspective, the Spacetime Amber is basically the body of that Primordial One. The fact that completing his wishes increases my Soul Connection with the Spacetime Amber might mean that I'm more accepted by his body. Hahaha."

Han Xiao grinned and opened the interface. There was now also a new field under the item description of the Spacetime Amber.

Spacetime Amber Soul Connection: 0/5

With such a reward, Han Xiao was more willing to complete this mission.

Although the Primordial Ones were from a very long time ago, as the first batch of Beyond Grade As, information about them was quite rich. Many institutions were passionate about studying them. Spacetime Freezer was not someone unknown, so it was easy to obtain information about him.

As for the wishes of Spacetime Freezer, Han Xiao was not worried about not being able to find out. According to the way the interface worked, he did not really have to study the life of Spacetime Freezer. As long as he had actions of browsing through data about Spacetime Freezer, the interface should treat it as him completing the requirement and give him the next round's mission requirements.

While he told Phillip to research online, Han Xiao also started to build a simple control device for the Spacetime Amber.

As long as he could establish a Soul Connection with the Spacetime Amber, not only would he be able to receive benefits from this Universal Treasure, but he would also most likely be able to control the Spacetime Amber with his mind. However, he had yet to receive the reward, so he needed a mechanical device to use the Spacetime Amber.

Han Xiao finished building it very quickly.

The Spacetime Amber was covered in a black, spherical device. This device could activate the energy of the Spacetime Amber and allow Han Xiao to control it with his mind. At the same time, it also had functions of a hovering guard such as flight, shield, and others.

With a thought in Han Xiao's mind, he controlled the Spacetime Amber to hover and activated the device.

Clank!

A small hole cracked open on the spherical device. The next moment, invisible energy shot out from the hole and started to change the properties of an area of space. The area of influence slowly expanded. When Han Xiao stopped the energy output of the Spacetime Amber, only then was this area solidified into amber.

"The output of the Spacetime Amber seems to be fixed, and the speed of creating amber is quite slow. At this speed, it would take many minutes to create the amount of amber needed to cover a two-meter-tall creature. Plus, the area only turns into amber when the energy output is cut off."

After some thought, Han Xiao called Psionic Prime out to do tests and very soon received multiple test results.

When Psionic Prime was completely covered, he was unable to move, his signals were cut off, he could not communicate with the outside world, and Phillip could not send him orders.

Han Xiao also tried to only cover a part of Psionic Prime's body to see if he could cut off Psionic Prime's control of those parts. However, this failed. Apparently, during the process of solidifying spacetime, the edge had to be unobstructed. If it was obstructed by a physical object, the amber would not form. This was really similar to blowing bubbles.

"Therefore, in order to freeze a target, the only way is to completely cover it..."

Han Xiao caressed his chin and had an idea. Since the Spacetime Amber could block all kinds of energy and redirect them away, it could be used as a special kind of external armor.

The only problem was that he could not shape the amber to his will for the time being. The amber he created would only be spherical.

Furthermore, the Spacetime Amber would only cause the energy to slip away but not block it. In order to make it useful on his armor, he had to use it over large areas. Since he could not manipulate its shape, he could not achieve something like that yet. Maybe he would only be able to after establishing a Soul Connection with the Spacetime Amber.

Nonetheless, Han Xiao still had a way. He planned to create some amber spheres larger than himself. Then he would use devices with nano-shapeshifting functions to cover these amber spheres. When attacked, he could use those amber spheres as a barrier, which might be even stronger than his tank talents.

"That can be considered a special means of defense."

No wonder so many people had fought for this Universal Treasure in his previous life.

Although the Spacetime Amber was not originally a combat tool, as long as he used it properly, it could still have astonishing effects. Its impact on battles was even larger than the Evolution Cube.

After he finished testing the Spacetime Amber's effects, he then used it to seal the Evolution Cube.

...

At the same time, on the Star Pupil Holy Race Mother Planet...

"Black Star!"

Outside the room, two guards were startled by the sudden furious yell of their leader and exchanged looks.

Inside the room, Psyker's face was filled with rage and shock.

All along, despite having lost the Evolution Cube, Psyker did not look anxious. This was because of his deep connection with the Evolution Cube. Even though the Evolution Cube was not in his hands, the marker that he had on the Evolution Cube still strengthened his psychic power all the time.

It was like Black Star had only stolen the Evolution Cube's body but not its heart, and Psyker knew the Evolution Cube still loved him.

As he could always locate the Evolution Cube, Psyker felt like the situation was still in his control.

However, moments earlier, Psyker had shockingly discovered that his senses for the Evolution Cube had vanished without a trace!

To him, this was as if his wife who had only been enduring the enemy in order to survive had suddenly developed feelings for the enemy and lost feelings for him.

All Psyker could feel was rage in all five of his hearts and a greener than ever emotion.

Chapter 839: Change and Superstition

"How did Black Star block my psychic senses of the Evolution Cube?"

Beep beep!

While Psyker was shocked and bewildered, his communicator suddenly rang. As he took it out and looked at it. His pupils constricted, and he clenched his teeth.

It was a call from Black Star!

"Hello, hello, is this Psyker?" Han Xiao appeared on the screen.

"Black Star! What did you do‽" Psyker yelled.

Seeing this, Han Xiao pretended to be shocked and replied, "Yo, I haven't seen you in some time. When did your skin become so green?"

After some mocking, seeing that Psyker's face was filled with rage, Han Xiao chuckled and immediately hung up the communication without waiting for Psyker's reply.

In order to test out the effect, Han Xiao had made a call to Psyker. Having heard Psyker's tone, he knew that it had worked. Therefore, he had nothing more to say to Old Psy and hung up immediately.

Originally, Psyker's link to the Evolution Cube had been a hidden threat. Now, he had finally gotten rid of this advantage Psyker had on him. Han Xiao felt much more secured.

The Arcane Church had no intelligence network in the Flickering World, so they would have to rely on Psyker's link to the Evolution Cube to track him if they wanted to attack him. And now, the Arcane Church no longer had that.

Part of the Arcane Church's strong desire for the Evolution Cube came from how Psyker was able to locate the Evolution Cube, as they thought they had a good chance to snatch it back. Once they lost that, they would have to carefully reconsider if they wanted to take the Evolution Cube back.

Although he had decided to stay in Planet Lighthouse and lie low for some time, there was no way for him to keep hiding. Furthermore, the Arcane Church definitely would not think that the dynasty did not speculate their intentions. If there were really no chances of sneak attacking, it was not impossible for them to directly attack Planet Lighthouse.

Due to the exploration of a new Star Field, the dynasty was currently in a weaker state among the three civilizations, and the other two had always been looking for opportunities. It was totally possible for the Arcane Church to start a direct conflict with the dynasty. Although the chances of the Arcane Church using such an aggressive plan were not high given their style, Han Xiao did not completely exclude this possibility.

After all, he had changed the storyline. Compared to the same time period in his previous life, the relationship between organizations had changed subtly. Even he did not know how far the Arcane Church would go to obtain the Evolution Cube.

If he could make the Arcane Church give up this time, he would not have to be on the passive side in the future.

As for whether Psyker would still follow the Arcane Church to make a move on him, Han Xiao was not worried. Even just to find out why his senses were blocked, Psyker would certainly come. Evolution Cube had belonged to Psyker, so the Arcane Church would not leave its formal owner out of it. Therefore, he could still indirectly find out about the Arcane Church's movements through paying attention to Psyker's whereabouts.

"You..." Psyker was just about to question when he realized the call had ended. The anger was stuck in his throat and made his blood boil.

Psyker paused. He then contacted the upper echelons of the Arcane Church with a long face.

"There's been a change. I can no longer locate Black Star."

"What?" The upper echelons of the Arcane Church were shocked. "The operation plan has already been decided. For such an accident to happen now... Since we no longer know Black Star's accurate location, we will have to change our operation plan."

The Arcane Church's original plan was to discreetly gather an overwhelming Beyond Grade A force and have them secretly go to the Flickering World, sneak up on Black Star when he was out exploring, and kill him at once. The crux for this plan to work was the fact that Psyker could locate Han Xiao.

Psyker had never had a problem locating Black Star, but Black Star had managed to suddenly cut Psyker's senses off at such a crucial moment, and this disrupted the Arcane Church's plan.

Originally, they planned to have a group of Beyond Grade As attack Black Star when he was alone, so they could eliminate Black Star in a short time and immediately return to the Shattered Star Ring afterward through their secret stargate.

Since they could not directly locate Black Star, they might have to give up on killing Black Star and capture Black Star instead so that they could interrogate him about the location of the Evolution Cube. This meant that their Beyond Grade As would need to spend a very long time in the Flickering World.

In that new Star Field, the Arcane Church basically had no backup at all. Every second those Beyond Grade As remained there, their risks would increase. If their secret stargate was discovered and destroyed by the dynasty during their operation, those Beyond Grade As would have no way to leave the Flickering World and would be trapped there till their doom.

"I need to report this to the Pope and the Bishops to let them decide," this upper echelon said.

Due to this change, the risk of this operation had increased tremendously, so it was no longer a decision he could make.

Nonetheless, he was secretly glad that this had happened before the operation started. For the time being, their team was still secretly on the way to the Garu Star Cluster and had yet to build the exit of the stargate, and the Beyond Grade As of the Arcane Church were still standing by. There was still room to make changes to the plan.

"Okay," Psyker replied with resignation. Despite being more impatient than ever, he knew that there was no way he would be able to order the Arcane Church around.

Through the stargates, it only took Han Xiao a few days of beating up Hadavy for his fleet to return to Planet Lighthouse in the Dawn Star Cluster.

Tarrokov had already spoken to Han Xiao and knew that Han Xiao would be lying low on Planet Lighthouse for a while. He welcomed Han Xiao personally with his people at the dock.

The fleet landed, and Han Xiao disembarked from his spaceship with his officers, meeting Tarrokov.

"Chief commander."

"Your Excellency Black Star."

After a handshake and a greeting, the two of them headed toward the base of the Planet Lighthouse in a vehicle and started chatting.

"Who's in the second batch that will be taking part in the exploration?" Han Xiao asked casually.

Tarrokov gave him a knowing expression before pressing on his bracelet, which projected the information of eleven organizations.

Han Xiao glanced through and nodded in his mind. He knew these organizations. They were all renowned organizations of the different Star Fields. There were Beyond Grade A allied organizations. There were also Star Cluster civilizations like Klent, and they all were on the dynasty's side.

"Constellation Corridor's Arcane Institute, Primeval Star River's Pyre Demon Tribe, Blackhole Edge's Dragonblood Nation, Sea of Star Spirits' City of the Giant Fleet... A total of four Beyond Grade A organizations. Yo, three of them are familiar faces."

During his trip to the dynasty's mother planet a few months ago, Han Xiao had come to know seven Beyond Grade A Dynasty allies—three of whom had joined this exploration.

The leader of the Arcane Institute was a member of the universe-renowned elderly celebrity group—a member of the Ancient Ones, Ravenlaude.

The leader of the Pyre Demon Tribe was an old friend, Beyoni, who had fought EsGod alongside him. The leader of the City of the Giant Fleet was also someone he had met before. He was a Beyond Grade A Mechanic.

The only person he had never met before was the leader of the Dragonblood Nation, Milizaus. This guy was one of the three strongest National Pillars, someone on the same level as 'Dark Lord' Clotti, and the strongest individual in this exploration team.

Among the four of them, Han Xiao paid more attention to Ravenlaude—the area this guy would be exploring was the same as him, the Garu Star Cluster. He was a direct competitor. Also, Ravenlaude was the first owner of the Spacetime Amber in his previous life.

Of course, this time, Han Xiao had gotten it first, and Ravenlaude had missed the opportunity.

Han Xiao thought for a while and asked, "The dynasty said they will send one Beyond Grade A directly under them to protect me from the Arcane Church's possible sudden attack. Who will that be?"

Tarrokov waved and said, "The plan has changed. Milizaus and Beyoni have personally requested to protect you. This is a better option."

Han Xiao was stunned for a moment. Then it occurred to him, and he smiled.

"They must have said their terms."

"Yes." Tarrokov smiled too. "They want to exchange this for a chance at using the Evolution Cube."

Han Xiao had expressed his stand long ago—he would not let the other dynasty allies use the Evolution Cube for free. If they wanted to use it, they had to give something in exchange. Therefore, Milizaus and Beyoni both wanted to make a deal with Han Xiao.

"What do you think? Do you agree with their terms?"

Han Xiao considered for a while before nodding. "Sure."

This meant that he would have one more person to help him than previously planned and a much stronger one. Therefore, he had no objections. He could even use this opportunity to network a little.

He recalled that the Dragonblood Nation's faction specialty was all kinds of dragonblood potions that would increase one's attributes permanently. He was thinking that he might be able to obtain some of it this time. Han Xiao's goal was not high at all; a mere few hundred tons would be enough.

The second batch of the exploration team took different routes. The quicker ones would only take around ten days to arrive, and the slower ones might need a month. However, they had already gathered their teams, so that would not cause any unnecessary delays.

Having travelled all the way to the base, Han Xiao and his officers settled down in their residence that had been arranged for them long ago.

For the time he would be staying there, he would temporarily stop going out and only remotely command the Black Star Army to do their exploration. There was no need for him to be there personally for the usual exploration.

In a desolate universe belt of the Central Galaxy, the enormous Fallen Ark fleet was slowly moving in the cosmic space like a sea made of battleships.

"The Arcane Church said the operation is going to be delayed?"

Having been awoken, EsGod narrowed his eyes as he heard Fakisen's report.

"Reason?"

"The Arcane Church said there was a problem with the building of the secret stargate, and the Crimson Dynasty has sent out a second batch of the exploration team. Therefore, the risk of the operation has increased, and they need to adjust the plan. They told us to be patient and continue waiting," Fakisen reported.

EsGod slowly nodded.

"Then let's do as they asked."

"One more thing," Fakisen said. "The Arcane Church said that there might be a possibility of directly attacking, so they hope that we can send out more fleets if that happens."

"So, they want us to send out more men to reduce their losses due to higher risks... Their style is becoming more and more similar to that of the Federation of Light." EsGod's tone was cold and indifferent. "Agree to it."

As long as he could obtain the Evolution Cube, the casualties of his subordinates did not matter to him at all.

As he had been tricked by Black Star using a fake Evolution Cube the last time, EsGod wanted to work with the Arcane Church by using the Arcane Church as the middleman to borrow Psyker's psychic locating ability, so he would not make the same mistake again.

This was an important factor in their cooperation.

However, Psyker could no longer use his psychic power to locate the Evolution Cube, and if EsGod came to know about this, he would most likely reconsider their partnership.

Although the Arcane Church had yet to make a new plan, they did not want EsGod to back away from this operation. Therefore, they purposely kept the information about Psyker no longer being able to locate the Evolution Cube a secret from EsGod and found another logical reason to explain the delay of the operation.

Due to the deep hatred Psyker had for EsGod for what happened to Planet Avitan, of course, the Arcane Church did not tell Psyker that EsGod was part of this operation too.

Therefore, EsGod did not know about what had happened with Psyker and waited for the operation to start.

After staying for two days on Planet Lighthouse, Han Xiao had already finished looking through all the information about Spacetime Freezer that had been collected by Phillip.

As expected, when he was done, a notification popped up on the interface. The first round of the mission was an easy one.

Having received the reward, his Soul Connection with the Spacetime Amber increased by one. Han Xiao could immediately feel the difference.

Somehow, he could feel that his soul had established a link with the Spacetime Amber. He no longer needed any supportive device and could now directly control the Spacetime Amber with his mind.

At the same time, a special energy flowed into his body through the Soul Connection that made him feel warm all over. Han Xiao exhaled with comfort.

This energy only disappeared after a while. Han Xiao instantly felt that this energy had enhanced his body to a certain extent. He opened the interface to look at the notification.

You have established a Soul Connection with [Spacetime Amber].

Current Soul Connection Level: 1/5

[Spacetime Amber]

Grade: Gold

Item Type: Universal Treasure

You have received the buff [Blessing of the Spacetime Amber].

[Blessing of the Spacetime Amber (Lv.1)]: +10% Maximum Energy, +50 STR, +50 DEX, +50 END, +100 INT, +25 MYS, +25 CHA, +50% Basic Space Resistance, +20% Basic Psychological Resistance. The effect of all your spacetime related abilities are increased by 12% – 24%.

Buff Duration: Fixed

"It's just level one, and the effect is already this good." Han Xiao's eyes lit up.

Just like how the Evolution Cube strengthened Psyker's psychic power, when he made a Soul Connection with the Spacetime Amber, he became stronger.

Han Xiao took out the Spacetime Amber and tried to use it. He realized that the energy output was higher, and the speed of creating amber increased significantly for about twenty to thirty percent.

"Looks like the stronger the Soul Connection, the faster I'm able to create amber with this thing."

Han Xiao looked at the second round of the mission, which also increased the Soul Connection. The mission requirement was to find the whereabouts of Spacetime Freezer's race and make contact with his descendants who had carried on his legacy.

"Er... this requirement..."

Han Xiao had a strange expression on his face.

It was not that he could not find the descendants of Spacetime Freezer, but they were too easy to find.

He had already finished reading all the data regarding Spacetime Freezer. He knew that this guy's race still existed and had always been under the civilization that Spacetime Freezer had once belonged to.

The only problem was... basically every descendant race of a Beyond Grade A had extraordinary talents and a very high percentage of Supers. They were always seen as an important resource by the civilizations and were protected heavily to produce warriors.

Spacetime Freezer's descendant race was also protected by the civilization that they belonged to and were practically not allowed to make any contact with outsiders.

This civilization had survived in the exploration era and had become an astronomical force.

It was one of the three universal civilizations—the Federation of Light!

If I, a Beyond Grade A on the Dynasty's side suddenly, run to the Federation of Light's territory...

Do I have to sneak in again? If I get found out this time, I'm probably going to be surrounded and beaten to death in the Federation of Light's territory...

Han Xiao's lips twitched. He was in the Flickering World and did not have time to leave, so it was clear that he would not be able to complete the second round of the mission any time soon. Therefore, he put it aside for the time being.

Anyway, he had the treasure in his hands, so he was in no hurry. He had something else to do.

Seven days had already passed since the last time he used [Bold Explorer]. The cooldown had ended.

This ability was like some sort of crystal ball magic, superstitious in every way. However, after testing it out, its effect was exceptional.

Han Xiao brought up the set of wormhole data that EsGod wanted and grinned slightly.

"I can finally uncover the secret in this set of data!"

Although he had already shared this set of data with the dynasty, and the dynasty's Science Institute would most likely decipher it in the future to obtain accurate clues...

Today, he decided to believe in superstition.

Chapter 840: The Biggest Butterfly Effect!

With the notification of [Bold Explorer] being activated popping up on the interface, Han Xiao's sights were filled with another illusion. Knowing how this ability worked, he focused on what he was seeing.

Two people appeared in the illusions, surrounded by messy black and blue space energy, like they were inside a wormhole path.

These two people were familiar. One was his past self, and the other was the EsGod doppelganger.

This set of wormhole data came from the wormhole that EsGod doppelganger had entered back when the two of them first fought. These were the images from that time.

As the scene played on, his past self fled from the wormhole following the original event, while Han Xiao's vision was locked onto the EsGod doppelganger, watching it flow between the streams of space energy.

"Come on." Han Xiao was excited.

When he banished the EsGod doppelganger, he had no idea what happened to it. Now, it seemed like he would finally learn about what happened to the EsGod doppelganger on the other side of the wormhole that made EsGod care so much about this set of data.

The next moment, EsGod finally passed through the tunnel and was spat out by the wormhole, appearing in a pitch black cosmic space.

Having realized that Han Xiao was not going there either, the EsGod doppelganger in the images looked a little angry, knowing that it had been tricked. It stopped for a while but then suddenly continuously teleported in one direction. Han Xiao's vision followed it throughout.

Not long after, the EsGod suddenly stopped. A strange planet appeared in front of it. Above the atmosphere of this planet, there were multiple wormholes. Roots of enormous plants extended from within and connected to the planet surface. Waves of energy were flowing up the roots from the surface, like it was absorbing the nutrients of this planet.

"This is..." Han Xiao's pupils instantly constricted as he was astounded.

He had never expected to see this thing here!

Before he had time to think, a sudden change happened!

Out of nowhere, multiple black space cracks opened beside the EsGod doppelganger. More than ten thin, long roots launched out from within like vines and wrapped around the EsGod doppelganger completely.

At this time, the illusions disappeared, and the images stopped. Han Xiao's vision returned to normal.

"Sh*t, why did it stop there?"

Han Xiao almost cussed. He was just paying full attention to what would happen to the EsGod doppelganger next, and it ended there‽

So upsetting!

Han Xiao took a deep breath and recalled what he had just seen. His expression was grave.

If this piece of information was shown to anyone other than him, people would only feel it was weird and had no value. In fact, in this entire universe, he was probably the only one that knew what this information signified.

He might very well be the only person that knew what these roots were. They came from the universal civilization that carried out a large-scale invasion in the later versions in his previous life—the World Tree Civilization!

"There are still many versions till the World Tree Civilization version. Why is it appearing at this stage?" Han Xiao subconsciously bit his fingernails. His expression was extremely grave.

He finally understood. It turned out that this set of wormhole data connected to the World Tree Civilization's territory, and the EsGod doppelganger went there out of pure coincidence!

The World Tree Civilization was located in the unexplored universe that was extremely far from the known universe. The three civilizations and the World Tree Civilization were both unaware of each other's existence. To a powerful civilization, exploring unknown areas was a must, so their meeting would happen sooner or later. In the later versions in his previous life, the World Tree Civilization discovered the existence of the three civilizations and decided to invade in the end. Just like that, an astronomically huge universal war erupted.

However, at this stage, the two sides should not have had any contact at all!

"Without me, the DarkStar leader would not have brought along an EsGod doppelganger to attack me, and EsGod would not have met the World Tree Civilization. Sh*t, this might be the biggest butterfly effect I have ever caused..."

Han Xiao's expression was grave.

The footage he had just watched contained a lot of information.

He knew that the World Tree Civilization was a civilization with a very special structure. The World Tree was equivalent to their Universal Treasure, and a Universal Treasure of the highest grade at that. It was worshipped and nourished by the entire civilization, at the same time bringing incomparable benefits to the civilization.

The World Tree's roots were in another dimension and had very sharp senses for energy, which was what led to it discovering the EsGod doppelganger. Although he did not know what happened to the EsGod doppelganger next, it was clear that he did something, given how persistent he was about this set of wormhole data. The two of them must have made contact!

"EsGod probably wants this set of data so he can find out the exact location of the World Tree Civilization. He said that's the hope for his evolution. Was this *sshole deluded by the World Tree Civilization and now wants to be their guide‽"

Having thought of this possibility, Han Xiao's expression changed.

If the World Tree Civilization discovered the location of the three civilizations because of the EsGod doppelganger's visit, the World Tree Civilization's invasion might erupt in advance. That would be a disaster to the entire known universe!

If the war with the World Tree Civilization happened before it should, the storyline he was familiar with would be completely gone. The advantage he had of knowing things before others would be almost useless, and at the same time, he would lose the precious time to increase his strength.

Although he was already Beyond Grade A, in such a gigantic galactical war that matched the exploration era war, even Beyond Grade As would not be able to ensure their own survival.

After all, there were way too many Beyond Grade As who died in this war in his previous life.

"Luckily, that's just one of EsGod's doppelgangers. With his personality, he might not have told anyone about it at all..."

This guy wanted to find the location of the World Tree Civilization and not wait for their arrival, which meant that EsGod might not have exposed any information of the known universe.

With the current situation, the only thing Han Xiao could do was pray that EsGod did not tell the World Tree Civilization about the existence of the three civilizations.

However, if EsGod was allowed to keep studying this set of data, he would have results sooner or later and drag everyone into the flames of war. No one would be able to exclude themselves.

This was a ticking time bomb that could not be ignored!

"I can't let him keep studying it..." Han Xiao clenched his teeth.

To this moment, he had only fought EsGod twice. Although they were enemies, he knew that he would not be able to do anything to EsGod for the time being.

Today, however, for the first time, a clear and straightforward murderous intent for EsGod was born in Han Xiao's mind. He wanted to kill him as soon as possible!

"Given the fact that EsGod can survive between the gaps of the three civilizations, looking for the dynasty's help would most likely be useless. I also don't have any way to prove the existence of the World Tree Civilization, so the dynasty will not insist on getting rid of EsGod..."

The information obtained through [Bold Explorer] could not be displayed to anyone else but him. Even if he told the dynasty what he had seen, there was no way the dynasty would believe the existence of the World Tree Civilization. The only way to make the dynasty believe it was to interrogate EsGod, the witness.

However, in order to interrogate, they had to at least capture him; he would not deliberately share this information otherwise.

Han Xiao frowned. He realized that there was not much exterior help he could obtain on this matter.

Unless... the dynasty had also completed studying this set of data and somehow discovered the World Tree Civilization without being discovered themselves. In that case, in order to keep the existence of their known universe a secret, the dynasty would have a strong reason to eliminate EsGod.

"Tough, the requirements are too difficult. Although the dynasty have the experience of the exploration era and know to hide themselves from unfamiliar entities, with the currently existing laws, the dynasty might actively make contact." Han Xiao shook his head in resignation. If he had known that this set of wormhole data led to the World Tree Civilization, he would have never given it to the dynasty to study. There were too many uncontrollable factors. If anything went wrong, the universal war that should only happen in the later versions would have a very high chance of erupting in advance.

"I'm the only one that knows about this now, and it's too difficult to solve this problem properly just by myself..."

Han Xiao was feeling low.

"Dealing with EsGod has to be done much sooner than I planned to. I'm not strong enough yet to fight EsGod alone... Sigh, the EXP penalty period is so long..."

After staying for more than half a month on Planet Lighthouse, the new exploration teams finally arrived at the Flickering World from afar.

Tarrokov met with the leaders of those new exploration teams in the base. Han Xiao came to meet with the members of this second batch of the exploration teams, planning to show his face and make new friends.

Inside the meeting room, the people swarmed in and instantly saw Tarrokov, who was waiting there. They then looked to the side and saw Han Xiao.

"Greetings, Chief Commander Tarrokov, Your Excellency Black Star."

The commanders of these Star Cluster civilization exploration teams there were all familiar with this new dynasty ally who possessed the Evolution Cube. They looked at Han Xiao with curiosity, and Han Xiao nodded back at them.

"Haha, we meet again." Beyoni laughed. "I heard the Arcane Church is planning to attack you. Looks like you need my help."

Suddenly, someone beside cut in and said, "Our help."

Han Xiao turned and sized this person up. The voice came from an illuminating energy body with a human shape. Bright red energy flowed through this person like liquid flames. He had no mouth or nose, only a pair of bright golden dragon eyes.

"You are..." Han Xiao was stunned about the fact that he did not recognize this person.

"Milizaus," this energy body said with a calm tone. "Don't be surprised. This is just an energy apparition. My main body did not land here."

Having his confusion resolved, Han Xiao shook hands with this energy apparition. "It's an honor to meet you, king of the Dragonblood Nation, leader of the Starry Spiritual Dragon Race."

At the same time, he secretly entered the quantum network vision and looked at the exterior atmosphere of Planet Lighthouse through the surveillance devices of the base.

A gigantic dragon with the size of almost a main ship was floating in the upper atmosphere. A long beard hung from its head, and diamond shaped dragon scales covered its body. Even the smallest scale was a few meters long. The body of the dragon had a mixed color of silver, purple, and green, as if bright star light was flowing between the gaps of the dragon scales. Although it was huge, it still looked agile with its streamlined body.

This was a Starry Spiritual Dragon. Even within the same race, this size was still impressive. This was indeed Milizaus' main body—he was a non-humanoid intelligent species.

The Starry Spiritual Dragon Race was a descendant race of a Beyond Grade A Magic Azure Dragon. They were born with a talent for magic. Although their reproduction capabilities were not high, an adult Starry Spiritual Dragon would have the power of a Grade B at least. The percentage of Calamity Grades in their race was exceptionally high.

Milizaus was the second Beyond Grade A in this descendant race. He was a unique giant dragon Mage. He had both the specialties of a normal Mage and a circuit mage and could learn all kinds of spells. However, when using the legacy spells of the dragon race, its power would be greatly enhanced. Currently, Milizaus was the leader of this entire descendant race; his position was somewhat similar to Manison, who led the Mechanical Race.

Furthermore, as dragons were long-lived, Milizaus was also a member of the Ancient Ones. He indeed was the Ancient One Dynasty ally other than Ravenlaude.

The Ancient Ones were a very loose group, so his standpoint with Ravenlaude was different. To some extent, one could even say their relationship was not exactly good. Ravenlaude was a Mage too, but their beliefs in magic conflicted.

Obviously, Milizaus had already become a new species and was no longer a pure Starry Spiritual Dragon. Due to how large his main body was, he usually used an energy apparition to communicate with others.

"I've heard a lot about you, the undying Black Star." Milizaus' voice was ancient and husky, but his personality was quite cheerful and not as cold as Clotti's. This was mainly because they were both Beyond Grade As, so they could communicate on equal grounds.

"With me here, you don't have to worry about the Arcane Church. They might not dare to act anymore seeing that I'm here."

"Haha, then I will have to prepare the Evolution Cube for you." Han Xiao chuckled. "By the way, are you interested in making another deal with me? It's also related to the Evolution Cube."

"Oh?" Milizaus was interested. "You know me well. Sure, when we're done with the meeting, let's have a proper chat."

Ravenlaude glanced at Han Xiao with a faint sneer. He then nodded at him as a form of greeting and sat down with the others without saying anything.

Due to Aesop, Ravenlaude did not want to be too close to Black Star. As a Mage, he was not too interested in the Evolution Cube. Furthermore, both of them were exploring the Garu Star Cluster, so they were competitors. Factoring all that in, Ravenlaude did not want the relationship between the two of them to go any further—he was not someone who liked to do networking.

Chapter 841: The Approaching Storm

Once everyone was seated, the meeting started. Tarrokov explained the current exploration situation.

After listening for a while, Ravenlaude was overjoyed. He was going to explore the Garu Star Cluster, and the long distance stargates built by the Black Star Army gave him many more choices, which was beneficial for him.

Who knows what Black Star was thinking? Ravenlaude gloated in his mind.

For someone like Heber who explored the Renault Star Cluster step by step, the exploration teams that came after would have no choice but to slowly hyperdrive over the already explored areas. The Black Star Army, however, did not seem to care about their own gains at all. They were basically setting themselves aflame to warm the ones who came after. How selfless of them!

The mockery in Ravenlaude's eyes increased even more as he glanced at Han Xiao.

Having noticed Ravenlaude's gaze, Han Xiao turned and smiled at him, also with mockery in his eyes.

Although the long distance stargates would undoubtedly make Ravenlaude's exploration easier, the biggest reward, the Spacetime Amber, was already in his hands.

Furthermore, Han Xiao had already occupied all the known rich planets from his previous life, and there were very few quality planets left for Ravenlaude. Of course, Ravenlaude had no idea.

As their eyes clashed, it was as if they made a silent exchange, both having deep meaning in their eyes.

Hehe, you've made such a loss, Ravenlaude seemed to say.

Tsk tsk, you have no idea what you've lost, Han Xiao mocked back.

The meeting ended very quickly, and the people left one after another. As the first batch of the exploration teams including Han Xiao and Heber had already built the stargates, the second batch of the exploration could reach their respective Star Clusters immediately and had no reason to waste time on Planet Lighthouse. They departed very soon.

Milizaus and Beyoni's teams left as well, while they themselves stayed and accompanied Han Xiao as temporary guards of the Evolution Cube.

As Beyond Grade As of the dynasty, neither of them minded bonding with their colleague, Black Star.

Inside a wide room, the three of them sat opposite each other. Three glasses of hot and red liquid were on the table. This was a specialty that Beyoni had brought from his home. It was said to be a special drink that the Pyre Demon Tribe loved.

Han Xiao took a large sip. It had a thick and dense texture, extremely hot and spicy, and rolled down his throat like flames. His stomach felt warm, and a bunch of '-0's popped up on his head.

"Not bad, what is this?" Han Xiao asked.

"Hehe, this is lava from the Land of the Fire Core, mixed with condensed alcohol. It tastes quite good, right?"

Damn it, you actually gave me lava to drink... Han Xiao's mouth twitched.

Land of the Fire Core was the only Universal Treasure the Pyre Demon Tribe had. It seemed to be something that could speed up the growth of young Pyre Demons. Han Xiao recalled that the Extinguish Army always wanted to destroy it.

After some hesitation, Han Xiao did not put the glass down in the end and took another sip.

"... Another round."

It really tasted quite good.

He had already stayed in a Fixed Star before, so drinking some lava was nothing.

Milizaus looked at the cup in front of him and wondered if he should drink it since this was just his energy apparition. He shook his head and asked, "Black Star, what was the deal you spoke of earlier?"

Han Xiao put the glass down and said with a smile, "The Dragonblood Nation's many kinds of Dragonblood Potions are renowned across the universe. I want to exchange the allocation of the Evolution Cube for Dragonblood Potions. You're the leader of the Starry Spiritual Dragon Race, so I suppose you want some of your exceptional people to evolve, right?"

Milizaus pondered for a while and nodded. "Sure, how are we exchanging specifically?"

The Dragonblood Potions were a specialty meant for selling to start with, so of course, Milizaus was not going to reject it. The Dragonblood Nation consisted of hybrid dragons that he created with Dragonblood. It was merely an armed force under his race. The Starry Spiritual Dragon Race was what was important to him.

"Two tons of common Dragonblood Potions plus a hundred kilograms of Condensed Dragonblood Potions in exchange for a hundred Evolution Cube allocations."

Milizaus was stunned in place.

Tons?

The Dragonblood Potions are usually sold in bottles you *sshole!

"It takes more than ten tons of Dragonblood from Grade C individuals to produce one ton of Dragonblood Potions, and the Condensed Dragonblood Potion requires much more," Milizaus said with a displeased tone. "Why don't I just give you a few dragons and you can drain blood from them yourself, huh?"

Han Xiao pondered with a serious face. "That's not unacceptable..."

"You're way too greedy!" Milizaus said angrily.

"I'm not asking you to purchase all the allocations at once. You can do it slowly." Han Xiao chuckled. Friendship was one thing, and greed in business was another.

Of course, he would not be able to finish such a large amount of Dragonblood Potions. They were mainly going to be used to strengthen capable officers and sold to players at high prices.

Selling specialties from other factions to expand the Black Star Army's range of products and indirectly increase the faction's appeal had already become Han Xiao's habit.

Milizaus was speechless. Although we have large sizes and a lot of blood, you can't just drain the hell out of our blood!

"If you have worries, I can let your people experience the actual effect of the Evolution Cube once for free," said Han Xiao.

"Sure, let's find an empty space. I'll call a dragon here." Milizaus nodded.

Han Xiao looked at Beyoni, and Beyoni said that he had no objections—he wanted to see its effects as well.

The three of them left the room and came to a wide metal field.

Han Xiao looked up and saw an enormous dragon descending.

Whoosh!

With its wings stirring up howling winds, this Starry Spiritual Dragon landed on the field with a loud bang, and the ground slightly trembled.

Han Xiao sized it up. This enormous dragon's body was long and streamlined. It was about a thousand meters long. It had two pairs of broad wings on its back and a pair of dragon claws below its body at the front, middle, and back, three pairs in total. It stared at the three of them with its cold golden dragon eyes.

This was a normal Starry Spiritual Dragon. Compared to Milizaus, its size was not as big. This Starry Spiritual Dragon did not have a habit of running around naked. Most of its body was covered in specially made black heavy metal armor.

Its armor was even equipped with mechanical weapons, such as artilleries and battleship shields. It was basically fully armed. Such a heavily-armed enormous dragon could basically be seen as a battleship. The machinery and its body formed a bulky sense of beauty.

Its armor and its body also had a lot of magic circuits on them that were illuminated. They were clearly Enchants.

"This is one of my Armed Dragon Guards. Let him try the effects of the Evolution Cube first," Milizaus said. As a Beyond Grade A, he also had his own elite team. The Armed Dragon Guards were just like Austin's Forbidden Sorcerers.

Wow, this guy looks really cool... Han Xiao's eyes were flashing. This style of large creature armed completely with machinery was perfect for his taste.

Temporarily unsealing the Evolution Cube, Han Xiao activated it. Black Evolution Energy poured out and covered this Armed Dragon Guard, forming a black cocoon.

Ka ka...

Not long after, the black cocoon shattered like a newborn coming out of its shell. Under the sharp senses of three Beyond Grade As, the aura of this Armed Dragon Guard became considerably stronger. Its size was visibly larger, and its heavy armor became a little tight on its body.

Roar!

This Armed Dragon Guard looked up and roared, emitting bright silvery-purple dragon breath that expanded like a sea of light and shattered like fireworks in the sky.

"Looks quite effective." Beyoni was a little jealous. If he could let the females of the Pyre Demon Tribe receive such enhancements, they would be able to endure more of his hot essence, which would definitely be beneficial in the reproduction of his descendant race.

Milizaus was also satisfied.

"Alright then, I accept this price. I shall first buy... two thousand allocations."

"How is two thousand enough? The population of the Starry Spiritual Dragon is not high, sure, but there should at least be a million dragons. Come on, buy more." Han Xiao tried tempting him.

Milizaus snorted. "I'll think about it in the future."

If he bought tens of thousands of allocations at once, his Starry Spiritual Dragon Race would have to change their name to the Anemic Dragon Race.

"I have another request." Han Xiao chuckled. He sized the Armed Dragon Guard up and said, "I think that you Starry Spiritual Dragons are quite magnificent..."

"What do you want now?" Milizaus was alarmed.

"Do you mind if I recruit a few Starry Spiritual Dragons as my allies..."

"Don't even think about it!" Milizaus was so angry that he could barely maintain his energy apparition.

Allies? You think I did not see the overflowing desire in your eyes? You want my people to be your mount, don't you‽ Outrageous, you might as well mount me!

Milizaus had read about Han Xiao before coming and knew about how thick skinned he was. However, after actual contact, the thickness of Han Xiao's skin still exceeded his expectations. Never mind him raising the price so directly, he even wanted to mount his dragon offspring right in front of him. How could there be such a shameless Beyond Grade A!

However, Milizaus did not dislike it and somewhat liked Black Star's style. Most of the Beyond Grade As in the universe took their image very seriously and always maintained a cold attitude as if they were afraid others did not know how important they were. He was quite happy to meet someone with a different demeanor.

Having lived for so long, one would either become careless about everything or develop more interests in new and fresh things. In this respect, Milizaus shared quite a lot of common traits with Aesop.

On the Arcane Church's mother planet, inside a large temple, the Bishops sat around the round table, discussing the Evolution Cube.

Dispatching so many Beyond Grade As at once was no small matter. It required decisions from the highest members of the Arcane Church. However, due to what had happened with Psyker, the opinions of the Main Church were divided.

"We should give up this plan!" a bishop said calmly. "We have lost the ability to locate the Evolution Cube and now are stuck. According to the latest intel, the dynasty has noticed our intentions. Black Star has returned to Planet Lighthouse and is hiding behind multiple layers of protection. The dynasty even gave him two bodyguards, 'Incineration' Beyoni and 'Dragon King' Milizaus. If we continue with the plan, we will be facing three of the Crimson Dynasty high level combatants, and that's considered direct conflict, which goes against our original intentions.

"The security around Planet Lighthouse is tight. As soon as our secret fleet appears near it, it will be discovered by the dynasty. By then, we will have to face the garrison of Planet Lighthouse, who are fully war-prepared. The risk is too high."

The others looked at him silently.

"More importantly, without the ability to locate the Evolution Cube, if Black Star hides it, we will have no way of finding it. Capturing Black Star is an extremely difficult task. The reward is not worth the risk. We..." After a pause, this bishop sighed and said, "We should give up the Evolution Cube."

The others could not object. They subconsciously looked at the main seat. That was supposed to be the seat of the pope. It was not occupied now, but they knew that the pope had been listening to the discussions.

The discussion had come to a stalemate. It was all up to the pope's decision.

After waiting for a while, a 3D projection suddenly appeared above the round table. There were a few sentences. It was the pope's reply.

"First, God has said that the Evolution Cube is still with Black Star.

"Second, change the plan and directly attack Planet Lighthouse.

"Third, new mission target, Milizaus. The [Ten Thousand Deity Scepter] can be used to kill him.

"Fourth, the Federation of Light has agreed to provide assistance."

Chapter 842: Enemy Whereabouts

Within a certain desolate universe belt in the Flickering World, a secret stargate station was hidden behind a desolate planet. It was the stronghold of the stowaways from the Arcane Church. This stargate station was equipped with all sorts of stealth devices to conceal its own energy reaction and prevent it from being detected by any kind of radar.

The Arcane Church's technology was on par with the dynasty's, only they had different focuses. The dynasty had been searching for the whereabouts of some Super Star Cluster civilizations lately but never found the secret stargate of the Arcane Church and the Federation of Light.

In order to remain stealthy, the Arcane Church would not frequently use the secret stargate, so this stargate station was silent most of the time.

That day, however, this stargate station was activated. The blue space energy inside the stargate suddenly accelerated its spinning, and battleships appeared from within.

These battleships were not the standard disc-shaped spaceships of the Arcane Church but quadrangular cone-shaped ships with red light swirling at the edges and black exterior armor.

This type of quadrangular cone battleship was one of the dozens of common high-level battleships in the galaxy. It circulated in the market on a large scale, so the owner's identity could not be identified from its model. The surface of the ships did not have any symbols that represented any identity.

Battleships came out of the stargate continuously. It was an enormous fleet of up to more than a million battleships.

The Arcane Church officer at the stronghold watched this silently. He did not know who this fleet was. All he knew was that his superiors had given him a direct order not to do anything and to let this fleet leave.

This mysterious fleet had no intention of communicating either. The stronghold officer watched as this fleet turned into streams of light and disappeared.

"What are the people above planning? A million battleships... Are we going to war with the dynasty?" the stronghold officer murmured.

As the stargate station disappeared from the sights of this mysterious fleet, inside the command room of its main ship, a hooded man looked up—it was an EsGod doppelganger.

"Humph, Arcane Church." The EsGod doppelganger snorted. EsGod's consciousness was on this doppelganger.

This fleet was a division of the Fallen Ark.

EsGod's forces were between the gaps of the Central Galaxy. In order to quickly come to the Flickering World through multiple Star Fields, they could only use stargates. The Arcane Church had secretly built stargates in the desolate universe belt of the Central Galaxy long ago to provide services to EsGod's troops so that EsGod could travel this long distance. Of course, this was only temporary.

Using the stargate of the Arcane Church, this division secretly arrived at the Flickering World. However, despite them temporarily working together, EsGod did not trust the Arcane Church.

To prevent the Arcane Church from ambushing him, he only sent a doppelganger and a division fleet. The mission of this division was to build his own secret stargate in the Flickering World so that his means of retreating would be in his own hands if things went wrong.

Stargates were a Star Cluster civilization technology, but the black market allowed people to buy things that they would never be able to buy through ordinary means. EsGod's stargate device had been bought from the black market at an extremely high price. In the entire universe, there were more than a few Star Cluster civilizations, so the stargate devices could not be kept completely exclusive.

EsGod's main body would only go to the Flickering World personally once he had a certain way of retreating.

"Open the star map."

His subordinate opened the 3D star map of the Flickering World that they had received from the Arcane Church.

Although this was the dynasty's star map, the Arcane Church had a way to obtain it since the universal civilizations all had a certain degree of infiltration of each other. However, this star map did not display the dynasty's lines of defense in the Flickering World. This was a top secret that even the Arcane Church could not easily obtain.

Nonetheless, the defensive force of Planet Lighthouse was highlighted. The planet's garrison consisted of about three million battleships, with more than one million battleships patrolling nearby.

The dynasty had dispatched hundreds of millions of battleships to the Flickering World, but most of them were exploring. With four million battleships defending it at all times, Planet Lighthouse was already the most heavily guarded planet in the entire Flickering World.

"Four million... looks like I need to bring some more people here." The EsGod doppelganger's tone was calm. The Fallen Ark was said to have sixty million battleships, and the actual number might exceed that. There was a reason he was feared by the three civilizations. He could easily dispatch this amount of manpower.

After a pause, the EsGod doppelganger took out the communicator and contacted the Arcane Church's special agent liaison officer. The upper echelons of the Arcane Church would not contact a criminal like him personally, so the Arcane Church's secret agent was the middleman between them. The Arcane Church could thus claim that there was no such person in their organization if things went south.

"Our troops are in position. When will you guys act?"

"In twenty days. I will notify you of the exact time in advance. We need you to work together with our troops."

The EsGod doppelganger replied with a mocking tone, "Work together how exactly?"

"According to the upper echelons, we will not appear at the same time. Therefore, we will have to split up. You shall be responsible for the direct attack to attract the garrison of Planet Lighthouse, and we will surprise attack."

The EsGod doppelganger nodded. He understood the Arcane Church's intentions. He knew that the Arcane Church would not send their Beyond Grade As to act together with him, so their strategy was within his expectations.

However, Planet Lighthouse's security forces filled up the entire sector. His troops would not be able to avoid the dynasty's eyes, nor could the Arcane Church's troops. There was no such thing as an actual surprise attack. EsGod felt that this was just so that he could attract more firepower so that the Arcane Church could enter the battlefield from another direction.

EsGod was not worried about the Arcane Church making him take on the brunt of the defense, as the dynasty would send reinforcements his way as soon as his troops triggered the alarm of Planet Lighthouse, and he felt that the Arcane Church would not miss this opportunity.

However, EsGod had no idea that the Arcane Church's plan was very different to what he expected.

In a dark room, a round table was surrounded by more than ten seats. At this moment, six were occupied by someone.

The term 'someone' would not be too accurate. All of them were remote projections, and one of them was Psyker.

Every seat there belonged to a Beyond Grade A combatant in the Arcane Church.

For this operation, the Arcane Church had sent out a total of six Beyond Grade As!

These six people were more than half of what the Arcane Church could gather in such a short period. The other Beyond Grade As all had their own tasks and would not be able to secretly move without being noticed.

The Arcane Church had six Beyond Grade As as well as external reinforcements. The opponents were only Black Star, Milizaus, and Beyoni. The difference in strength was extremely one-sided—the Arcane Church was planning to launch a thunderous strike!

Currently, the six of them were casually chatting.

"It's been a very long time since I've seen such a large operation like this."

"Hmm, Milizaus... that dragon is not easy to deal with. I've fought him before. We could not kill each other, and it ended in a draw. However, this time, even the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter will be used, so his chances of surviving are very slim."

"The Arcane Church is out of their minds. Are they planning to start a war? After killing three Beyond Grade As of the Crimson Dynasty at once, things might escalate into a full out war."

"Isn't that exactly what the Federation of Light wants? That's why they agreed to help and even allowed us to borrow their Universal Treasure."

The Beyond Grade As shook their heads—the Arcane Church was clearly going to make the headlines.

They had no worries for the result of this operation at all. With such a wide strength difference, there was basically zero possibility they would fail. What they were worried about was what impact this operation would have after they succeed.

They could see that after killing three Beyond Grade As of the dynasty, if the conflict between the Arcane Church and the Crimson Dynasty turned into an all-out war, as the participants of this event, they would be targeted by the dynasty.

Although they were not afraid of the Crimson Dynasty, some of their territories were in other Star Fields. If they were targeted by the dynasty, they would be caught in a whole lot of trouble. Therefore, some of them were not keen on taking part in this operation.

However, as allies who had received so many benefits over time, they could only answer to the Arcane Church's summons with resignation even if they were reluctant.

"If not because Psyker lost the Evolution Cube, there would be no need for this operation." Someone grunted and blamed Psyker.

Psyker glanced at him, confirmed that it was someone he could not beat, and chose not to say anything.

"Since the Arcane Church has made such a large-scale operation, even if we retrieve the Evolution Cube, there's no way it will be returned to you," someone else said with a deep voice.

"I know." Psyker's expression remained the same. "It's acceptable to me as long as it's not in someone else's hands."

"Tsk, if Black Star returned the Evolution Cube back to you back then, he would not have gotten himself into this mess. Apparently, Black Star took the shortest time to reach Beyond Grade A in all of history. Sadly, he's too greedy," someone else said with a pitiful tone.

"He took something he shouldn't have. He deserves it," Psyker said coldly.

He knew that the Evolution Cube would not go back to him after the Arcane Church succeeded. However, as the Evolution Cube was sealed by Han Xiao, his Soul Connection with the Evolution Cube was severed. Hence, he lost the enhancement of his psychic power. Therefore, his requirement lowered.

Even if the Arcane Church took the Evolution Cube, as long as his Soul Connection was maintained, Psyker could accept it. Han Xiao was the cause of all of this, and Psyker had immense hatred for him. He would not let this opportunity to eliminate Han Xiao slip through his fingers.

Personal hatred was one thing, but Black Star's organization was in the Shattered Star Ring just like his. Due to the fact that they were enemies, Black Star had become an obstacle of the Star Pupil Holy Race's growth, and the previous Civilization Conference was an example of that. For the growth and development of his civilization, Psyker also wanted to eliminate Black Star.

A Beyond Grade A beside Psyker seemed to know what Psyker was thinking. He patted Psyker's shoulder and said, "Don't worry, I'll eliminate Black Star for you."

"Thanks, Dylan." Although Psyker was not in a good mood, he still forced a smile for this person. "Let's fight him together then."

Dylan nodded. His long, dark-green hair swayed like seaweed.

His skin was blue, and his face was covered in tiny scales and had similarities to fish. He had a pair of large, bright eyes that occasionally blinked and another conspicuous third eye on his forehead. There was webbing on his hands and feet and one eyeball in both of his palms. It was quite strange. His back was crouched as if he had a hunchback, and there were fins on it. He looked like a marine creature. Who knew what his ancestors did to fish... or what the fish did to his ancestors?

With such a look, his ability was clearly related to water. Dylan was an Esper, nicknamed 'Sea Spirit' and 'Ruler of the Sea'. His Esper Ability was controlling water. It sounded ordinary and seemed weak in space, but no Beyond Grade A Super was weak.

Dylan could compress water to an extreme extent that could easily slash through battleships. Not only that, he could even turn water into a powerful energy beam that had the destructive power on par with battleship weapons. At the same time, his body could store a huge amount of water that was more than enough to flood the surface of an entire planet.

This type of Esper Ability was not suitable for duels, but it was quite good in group battles.

Having been part of the Arcane Church for many years, Psyker had friends, and Dylan was one of them. He was the closest friend Psyker had among the Beyond Grade A allies. It might be because both of them had many eyes, so they shared common interests.

On the Federation of Light's mother planet, the Federation of Light president, Bader, was also paying attention to the Arcane Church's movements. It was his decision to provide help to the Arcane Church.

"With our help, as long as the Arcane Church doesn't underestimate them, the chance of this operation succeeding is higher than ninety-five percent. At least one Beyond Grade A will die on the Crimson Dynasty's side." Bader's tone was confident.

The Chief Elder nodded with approval. "Hmm, the death of a Beyond Grade A is more than enough to trigger conflict between the Arcane Church and the Crimson Dynasty, which is very beneficial to us.

The Federation of Light aided the Arcane Church in order to watch them fight. If the Arcane Church and the Crimson Dynasty battled with each other, they would be the ones who benefitted from it.

The Arcane Church knew this but still decided to continue the plan as they had their own goals. Furthermore, working with EsGod was never something justifiable, so they did not tell the Federation of Light. Since the Federation of Light had provided help, they would be dragged down as well and would not be able to use this against the Arcane Church.

Although both sides had their own goals, they also shared a goal—to apply pressure to the Crimson Dynasty and test the dynasty's attitude to see if they could eat them up.

As for whether Milizaus or Black Star would be killed, it made no difference to Bader, and he did not care at all.

Chapter 843: Showing themselves!

In Base No. 4 of Planet Lighthouse, within the real-life war training room, a spar was being carried out.

Bang!

A mechanical fist slammed against a hardened fist, and a shock wave burst out from the point of contact.

Hadavy braced himself, catching Psionic Prime's fist, before viciously swinging forward with a right hook, knocking him backward onto the defense line formed by the mechanical soldiers.

Behind his line of defense, Han Xiao slightly shifted, waving his hand and shooting a beam of Mechanical Force to stabilize the body of Psionic Prime.

His eyes immediately flashed with an electrical glow, and the next instant, along the route Hadavy was taking toward him, a psionic barrier appeared.

Because the barrier appeared too suddenly and was too close, Hadavy rammed straight into it.

Boom!

"Good sound. You have a good head."

The corners of Han Xiao's mouth curled up, and he suddenly clenched his fist. The wall-like barrier shrank instantly into a minute dot before imploding directly on Hadavy's face. With a thunderous noise, it shot out a blue beam, knocking Hadavy into the wall of the training room.

Boom!

The metal plates of the room were bent and broken, and a human-shaped hole appeared in the wall.

The mechanical soldiers forming the line of defense began to concentrate their fire, their ammunition blanketing the entire area, shooting straight into the human shaped pit.

Boom!

A dazzling explosion of light turned the entire room a pure white for a moment.

During this time, a red-colored light suddenly rushed toward Han Xiao's back, piercing through ten or so mechanical soldiers, before aiming toward the back of his head.

Psionic Prime immediately disassembled and reassembled as a floating cannon model, activating a psionic shield to cover Han Xiao's back. The red light hit the blue shield, shattering into fine shards.

As Han Xiao leisurely turned his head back, Hila shot backward, creating distance between them while firing her death rays. Against him, she did not dare go close range and could only resort to this long distance style of attacking.

This spar was a challenge for all the Black Star Guards to fight against Han Xiao. In order to achieve the effect of training them, Han Xiao naturally would not activate all his troops and only utilized a thousand mechanical soldiers. Without his Human Wave Tactic, he made up for it with a variety of mechanical equipment.

The training room was reduced to a mess. Most of the Black Star Guards had collapsed at this time, and only Hadavy and Hila were still going, looking extremely bedraggled.

"Come over here, darling." Han Xiao stretched out his hands toward Hila, and the mechanical components assembled around his arm. Mechanical Force flashed, and a strong gravitational force was released from the arm of his mechanical suit, producing the sound of wind being sucked into it.

The mechanical soldiers instantly dodged, and the gaps appeared in the line of defense wherever Hila moved.

She immediately felt a strong pulling force dragging her toward Han Xiao's side. Her pupils flared red, and the energy in her body burst out, resisting the pull of the gravitation, but her speed was inevitably slower.

Seeing that the gravitational machine had limited success, Han Xiao frowned before his body moved. He started up five strong suction traction beams behind him before activating them all at once.

Hum!

A huge attraction force suddenly superimposed on the original gravitational force, and Hila could no longer resist, being yanked over. She simply gave up resistance, and her flight speed soared. Approaching Han Xiao, she concentrated her energy within her legs, and a strong force was whipped about, powerful enough to destroy a mountain.

Han Xiao remained unmoved, and his latest generation of the Battle Tiger mechanical suit simply unfolded.

Clank clank!

The black mechanical suit covered his entire body, only revealing his head. Han Xiao bent his arms and used his forearm to meet Hila's leg whip.

Boom!

Her legs, wrapped in energy, collided with his forearms covered in mechanical parts. The nanoparticles within the suit surface undulated and transferred the force to the legs and body.

Peng!

The next moment, a shock wave was emitted from Han Xiao's sole, and the metal flooring all warped and broke apart. The excess strength was converted into a shockwave that blew away the surrounding smoke.

Han Xiao was still in his previous position. While Hila's melee skills were not bad, she was not a Pugilist, and thus, her attributes were far lower than Han Xiao's, unable to cause any threat.

Han Xiao did not pause in his motions. He immediately stretched out his hand used to block and latched on to Hila's neck before applying strength to slam her against the ground with a sickening crunch.

"Ugh!" Being heavily slammed, Hila groaned and gritted her teeth in resistance. Her explosive figure twisted under Han Xiao like a slippery snake, yet she was unable to escape his grasp.

Suddenly, Hila's vision darkened, and she looked to see Han Xiao leaning over, his face almost sticking toward hers with a smug expression.

"Stop twisting, the battle has already ended since you were caught by me. Based on your physique, you cannot possibly escape."

Only upon hearing this did Hila finally stop her resistance. She bit her lips, locking eyes with Han Xiao.

The distance between their eyes was not even ten centimeters, and they could feel the warmth of each other's breath on their faces.

Han Xiao's nose twitched as a fragrance entered his nose. His face suddenly turned strange.

"Strange, why is there a fragrance? Did you put on perfume, or is that your natural fragrance?"

"... Let go."

"Sure, of course."

Han Xiao released his hands and straightened his waist, ready to help Hila up, but she ignored his offered hand, climbing back up by herself and dusting her clothes.

Seeing her impassive expression, Han Xiao helplessly shook his head. Having sparred so many times, he understood Hila's attitude too well. Even with the gap in strength, Hila would not feel good every time she lost in a spar.

The mechanical troops also ceased firing, revealing many pits in the walls. There was a sound of stirring metal debris coming from within. The debris clanked, and Hadavy, covered in soot, crawled out from the hole. As he walked toward Han Xiao, he started to peel off the burnt skin over his body.

The mechanical devices imprisoning the various Black Star Guards were also put away, and they got up, rubbing their bruises. Among them, the one with the most decent appearance was probably Feidin. This was because Han Xiao was mainly reluctant to hit him, afraid to ruin his handsome face.

Since they were both handsome people, giving some privileges was only natural.

"This is great!" Hadavy grinned, his blackened face showing an expression of comfort.

Han Xiao ignored him, instead looking at the time. "You guys lasted thirty-seven seconds longer than the previous spar. Good improvement."

Since the worst of these guards were also elite Calamity Grades, it was difficult for them to even take another step forward. Only Hila and Feidin showed the most improvements. After all, they had heaven defying gifts in the first place. In another twenty years, they would probably achieve the level of a Beyond Grade A seed.

As for breaking through to the Beyond Grade A realm, only Hila who had proven her strength in his previous life had a chance, but since she did not slaughter an entire planet like in the past, her rate of improvement would not be so perverted.

"The training room is too small and limits my range of movement. It will place me in the range of the traction beam sooner or later. If we had unlimited space for movement, I could have lasted longer. Next time, we need to take this into consideration..." Hila frowned as she summarized her experience.

Just as Han Xiao was about to say something, his communicator beeped as it received a message.

Glancing at it, Han Xiao laughed before saying, "You guys continue training. Tarrokov and the others are looking for me for a chat."

After staying on Planet Lighthouse for more than half a month, Han Xiao was already familiar with Milizaus. Since he also had nothing to do, the chief commander holding the fort, Tarrokov, would typically invite the Beyond Grade As to his room for tea and some conversion to pass the time.

Hearing this, Hila stopped talking. She seemed to want Han Xiao to continue teaching, but she nodded in the end, calling the rest of the Black Star Guards to gather and continue practicing whilst she looked at the exiting Han Xiao from the corner of her eyes.

While he was walking over, Han Xiao entered his quantum network.

"Phillip, any news from the long-range patrol today?"

"Reporting to master, there is nothing, hum..."

Seems like the Arcane Church still hasn't taken action yet... Han Xiao nodded.

Even under the protection of the dynasty, Han Xiao did not lower his vigilance. This period when he stayed at Planet Lighthouse was not spent idly. Other than building more machinery and training his Black Star Guards, he had also sent out remotely controlled troops to form a security perimeter around Planet Lighthouse. Under their surveillance, he would receive intelligence reports every day. The moment they discovered traces of the Arcane Church, he would get the news immediately.

Staying on Planet Lighthouse was not just for Han Xiao to receive protection from the strong security but also because it was the dynasty outpost and had many stargates. If the enemy was too strong, he had enough time to use the stargates to escape. Han Xiao would not send himself off to die for no reason, and staying on Planet Lighthouse left him enough time to escape.

While the past half a month had been peaceful, Han Xiao had a feeling that it was the calm before the storm. He did not think that the Arcane Church would give up on the Evolution Cube just like that.

Occasionally, he would also use the Evolution Cube on Milizaus' Armed Dragon Guards. During the usage, he would naturally unseal the Spacetime Amber, and thus, Psyker would be able to detect where the Evolution Cube was, like an intermittent signal.

"The enemy is in the shadows while I'm in the open. If the Arcane Church wants to make a move, they can only do so through sending troops."

Han Xiao shook his head before opening the forums to take a look.

During this period, the exploration had been very smooth. Although Ravenlaude had obtained some profits by using the stargate that he built, the majority of resource rich planets along the way had been seized by the members of the Black Star Army. Ravenlaude could not forcibly snatch the territory of others under the dynasty's eye. Thus, he could only search for other territories.

The players had been working hard at the exploration and had accumulated a great number of mission points. Those from China, Russia, and even Australia had all put their hands together to perform missions, building more harmonious relationships. However, the friction between the three parties was also becoming more intense.

One reason was because of the competition for resources. During this time, the Black Star Army had sent out another batch of troops to supplement the exploration. It was the second batch of players that had migrated from the Constellation Corridor. The guilds of Russia and Australia had decided to ally together temporarily and sent a group of new guild players to support their branches, attempting to break away from China's suppression.

With an increase in numbers, they also gained more strength and were no longer willing to reside on third-rate resource planets. Thus, they began to try and fight for better quality resource areas, increasing friction with the Chinese.

"If this carries on, I'm afraid it will devolve into a full-scale guild war. If these clubs even instigate players from their country, it will be on a national scale," Han Xiao speculated.

However, this was an internal affair of the player group. He could not nor did he wish to obstruct them. Previously, they made friends with each other to prevent any hostile behavior directed toward them.

There was still a certain measure of success in this plan. The relationships between the ordinary players were harmonious, and even if they were dragged to fight in a national war, they would still be good friends after the fight, with no obvious separation into factions. After all, this was something unique to the players—they could be on opposing sides and still be friends.

Upon reaching the chief commander's office, Han Xiao saw Beyoni, Tarrokov, and Milizaus all seated on the sofa. The reception table in front of them was filled with special drinks from the dynasty, as well as... the evil Wayne Cards.

Because of the popularity of the Wayne Cards, even Beyond Grade As would also turn to it for entertainment.

Hearing the door open, the trio immediately looked over. Beyoni even waved.

"Black Star, you're here at last. Come, sit."

Nodding, Han Xiao sat down next to Milizaus, picking up his glass and taking a sip.

"Why did you drink mine?" Milizaus had an unsatisfied tone.

"As a mana incarnation, you don't have taste buds. Don't waste such a good thing." Han Xiao remained unfazed.

After more than half a month of getting along, their relationship had improved, and he was more aware of Milizaus' personality. Although he was very strong, he did not put on any airs, much better than the cold faced 'Dark Lord' Clotti. Compared to the first time they met, Han Xiao was more casual toward him now... almost bordering on disrespect.

"Sigh, you guys have been at Planet Lighthouse for almost a month. If not for you guys, I wouldn't be so lazy."

Tarrokov sighed. He originally did not have people of similar status to converse with, and now that Han Xiao and company had camped there for so long, this chief commander began to show his lazy side.

"Actually, there's something that I'm curious about. What sort of relationship do Clotti and Urranrell share? I don't think it's so simple as just a guard." Milizaus was curious. "As an Imperial Ruler, one must have a family, but Urranrell is a widow, and Clotti is that sort of cold-blooded head of state. Could it be..."

While the dynasty's marriage laws emphasized monogamy, Beyoni seemed to think that it had nothing to do with him.

"Tsk tsk, while I'm a very mild person, I'm still one of the top officers of the Dynasty. To say such things in front of me, is that really good?" Tarrokov was helpless. "I don't know anything about this, and even if I knew, I wouldn't say."

Milizaus snorted and threw out a Wayne Card, saying, "Then you lose."

Tarrokov froze, looking at his cards, before narrowing his eyes in suspicion. "Did you use magic to change my cards again?"

"Don't try to wiggle your way out. Would I do such a meaningless thing‽" Milizaus got angry.

In actual fact, you would... because I didn't see that darned card in your hand just now...

Han Xiao could not help but think of Lagi. Whenever he played cards, he had a signature catchphrase, 'Only trash utilizes magic when playing cards!'

From then on, he knew that if one wished to stop a mage from cheating, one had to counter with an even stronger magic...

And among the three of them, one was lazy, one played with fire, and one touched machines all day. There was simply no one who could stop the mage.

Looking at these big shots grumbling and boasting without dignity, Han Xiao could not help but relax.

This is the life...

But before he could even finish his internal monologue, an abrupt change happened.

Woo!

Piercing alarms sounded, and the four of them jumped up as one.

Tarrokov's expression turned solemn, and he opened the real-time monitoring star map, checking the situation.

At the same time, Han Xiao also received an intelligence report from Phillip.

"Master, master, squad 025 has spotted the trail of a large fleet that is moving toward Planet Lighthouse, hum..."

The image was sent over and showed a mysterious fleet entering the warning sector of Planet Lighthouse, triggering the alarm.

This fleet consisted of quadrangular pyramid spaceships, and at a glance, there were over a million of them!

The mysterious fleet engaged the dynasty patrol fleet in that direction, breaking through the defense line, showcasing their intention to attack Planet Lighthouse.

Han Xiao knew that something was wrong.

"The Arcane Church? They really came!"

Chapter 844: Shocking Change!

The instant that the alarms went off in Planet Lighthouse, more than three million Fallen Ark battleships appeared near the security perimeter in a long, stretched-out formation.

In the flagship, EsGod's subordinate Fakisen was looking at the star map, and the distance between them and Planet Lighthouse was rapidly shrinking.

"Boss, we have already entered the security perimeter of Planet Lighthouse. The radar shows that the nearby dynasty fleet is heading our way and will exchange fire with us soon."

Fakisen used his long tongue to scratch the back of his neck as he spoke.

"Try to speed up. Do not get tied down by them," EsGod said calmly. This time, his main body had made an appearance.

Fakisen swung his tongue around and said, "Even though we are working together, the Arcane Church still has their guard up against us. Not only did they not reveal their exact plans, they even changed the location of their secret stargate. They are obviously guarding against us, and who knows when they will take action and from which direction?"

EsGod was not too bothered; it was perfectly normal for them to guard against each other. It was just like how he would not inform the Arcane Church of where his secret stargate was located.

With Planet Lighthouse at the center, the security perimeter around the planet was extremely large, and the dynasty had sufficient time to mobilize their troops the moment an enemy was spotted. Thus, EsGod could guess what the Arcane Church's intention was even if they kept it confidential.

They obviously wanted him to be the vanguard, and the size of his troops was not sufficient to get the dynasty to abandon their Planet Lighthouse outpost. By the time he fought his way to Planet Lighthouse and tied down Black Star and the two other Beyond Grade A Supers, the Arcane Church would take action.

EsGod felt that his guess was definitely not too far from the truth, and the only thing that he was not sure about was how many high level combatants the Arcane Church had sent out this time.

The dynasty had three Beyond Grade A, and Milizaus' strength could almost equal his own. If that was the case, the Arcane Church only needed to send out manpower to deal with Black Star and Beyoni.

Black Star and Beyoni were still a distance away from a top notch Beyond Grade A Super, and it should be sufficient for the Arcane Church to send out four Beyond Grade A Supers.

I wonder who the Arcane Church will send out this time...

EsGod narrowed his eyes. If the Arcane Church sent out too powerful a line up, he would have to be careful as well.

Right at this moment, the dynasty's fleet arrived and appeared on their radar.

Fakisen looked at EsGod, and upon seeing that his boss did not have any intentions of saying anything, he ordered on behalf of EsGod, "All weapons free! Destroy all the battleships in our way!"

...

Planet Lighthouse had already entered high alert, and the three Beyond Grade A Supers entered the command room together with Tarrokov.

A large number of military personnel were gathered in the room with plenty of messages being sent back from the battlefield. Tarrokov stood in front of the 3D battlefield model with a solemn expression.

The scene being shown on the battlefield was the battle between the Fallen Ark fleet and the dynasty's fleet. The battleships of both parties had been shrunk down many times to completely simulate the battlefield environment. It was as though two mini fleets were battling it out in front of everyone's eyes.

"The enemy fleet has about 3,200,000 battleships. An organization capable of sending a fleet of such a size to the Flickering World is definitely a powerful one. We cannot see the origins of the fleet from the models of the spaceships," a staff sergeant said. "The highest possibility is the Arcane Church."

As he said that, Tarrokov turned around to look at Han Xiao and said, "However, they may also belong to other organizations."

Han Xiao noticed his gaze and said without any hesitation, "They are from the Arcane Church."

Tarrokov nodded slowly and said, "I understand."

Although Han Xiao's expression seemed calm, his mood was low.

His words were not completely baseless as a notification popped up after the appearance of the fleet.

You have triggered an Urgent Mission [Cause and Effect]

Mission Introduction: You have snatched the Evolution Cube and attracted the enmity of the Arcane Church. They have finally taken today and decided to deal a lightning fast blow to you to snatch the Evolution Cube back!

Mission Requirements: Defeat the enemy or escape successfully.

Failure Condition(s): Death or lose the Evolution Cube

Reward: 24,000,000,000 – 45,000,000,000 Experience, 1 Legendary Point, 3 Random Rewards, 3 Unknown Character Summon Cards

Han Xiao was shocked upon seeing the reward.

Twenty-four billion experience at the very least‽ The highest reward when he was fighting Heber was only 8.5 billion experience!

Even he felt that this was a huge sum of experience!

However, Han Xiao just could not find it in himself to be happy. The reward would correspond to the difficulty of the mission. With such a large reward, this meant that the strength of the Arcane Church would be extremely frightening! The reward of over forty-five billion meant that he had to face at least five Beyond Grade A Supers!

Just who would be able to survive‽

Although Han Xiao had already secretly hired help just to be safe, he could not help but have thoughts of retreating. At the same time, however, he was also extremely wary.

If he escaped through the stargate right now, he should be extremely safe. However, would it be so simple to complete a mission with a reward of twenty-four billion experience?

Perhaps the Arcane Church had some other means that would make it easier for them to catch him if he escaped alone.

He was currently being surrounded by many layers of defense and was still considered safe. Furthermore, the dynasty would not think too highly of him if he escaped the moment he met an enemy. After pondering for a moment, Han Xiao did not make any rash moves but arrived at the command room together with Tarrokov.

Since they had a sufficiently large buffer zone, it would not be too late for him to decide to run after observing the battle.

The name of the mission is [Cause and Effect]. Heh, a Universal Treasure truly isn't that easy to take.

However, all those present did not know what he was thinking about.

Tarrokov observed the changes in the battlefield and issued a command.

"Inform all our Beyond Grade A allies to return immediately."

Upon hearing that, Han Xiao's eyes sparkled, and he nodded.

Tarrokov had obviously noticed something, and this chief commander truly had foresight.

There were still another three Beyond Grade A Supers in the Flickering World: Heber, Ravenlaude and another Mechanic who was called Maximiler. If they all returned, there would be six Beyond Grade A present, and they would not have to be afraid of the enemy.

Without knowing how many high-level combatants the Arcane Church had, Tarrokov did not mind being on the safe side. Even if his actions were deemed unnecessary after this battle, it would be better than regretting his inaction.

"Our fleet has sent a message for reinforcements. They won't be able to hold the enemy back. Chief commander, are we going to send the security fleet from the other regions to support them?"

Tarrokov observed the battle for a moment before saying, "Only mobilize the security fleet in that direction. Do not move the other fleets in the other directions. The remaining reinforcement troops shall be sent from Planet Lighthouse."

Beyoni could not help but be surprised by the order. "It will take quite some time to send out troops from our base. The enemy fleet will then be able to close the gap quickly. Why don't you mobilize the troops on the outside instead?"

"The enemy doesn't have any insignia and chose to attack our security perimeter alone," Tarrokov replied with a deep voice. "I think that this isn't the Arcane Church's main force but a vanguard force. Their objective is to tie down our defense force on the security perimeter and create a gap in our formation. Their main force will then break through our defenses, and we will have to face a pincer attack. This should be the Arcane Church's tactic."

Upon hearing the explanation of the chief commander and looking at the battlefield, everyone had to admit that it was likely for the enemy to employ such a strategy. Since Tarrokov had seen through their plans, his method of dealing with it was not too bad.

"However, this is only a temporary measure. We need intelligence on how many Beyond Grade A combatants this fleet has."

Tarrokov then looked at the three people with his intentions obvious. Only someone at the same level would be able to force the enemy out.

"Hand it over to my long-distance troops."

Han Xiao nodded. Since he was the enemy's target and a key character of this battle, it would not be good for the three of them to split up at such a time.

The long-distance troops that he had sent out would also show their use.

...

"What? Planet Lighthouse was attacked‽"

The Bloodshed Land troops that were currently in Renault received news from Jorde and could not help but be surprised.

"The enemy is the Arcane Church, and their target is Black Star. Chief commander Tarrokov asked us to return to reinforce them... Your Excellency Tyrant, what should we do?" Jorde asked carefully.

Heber began to frown. He did not wish to help Black Star. However, he suddenly thought about something, and his brows relaxed.

"Since it is the dynasty's orders, we shall return to reinforce them. Inform my troops to head to the nearest stargate at full speed!"

Heber's fleet then turned around and headed to Planet Lighthouse at full speed.

Although Han Xiao and he had some conflicts, this matter concerned the pride of the dynasty. As a member of the dynasty, defending the dynasty was compatible with his own benefits.

In the Garu Star Cluster, Ravenlaude also received Tarrokov's request for reinforcements.

Black Star's death had nothing to do with him, and he would rather have one less competitor.

However, it was a pity that his organization was located in the Central Galaxy, and he needed to rely on the dynasty.

Such a small matter was not worth disobeying the dynasty's orders, so he could only lead his troops over.

Very quickly, he realized a very frustrating matter. Black Star had constructed a stargate in the Garu Star Cluster, which meant that he could arrive at Planet Lighthouse rapidly and did not have any excuse to delay.

Right at this moment, Ravenlaude suddenly realized something.

Could it be that Black Star had constructed the long distance stargate because he knew that something like this would happen‽

That's right. This must definitely be the case. If not, I can't think of another reason why Black Star would sacrifice his own benefits to construct a long distance stargate.

Ravenlaude finally understood Black Star's 'true goal'. To think that he was still laughing at the other party's thoughts before this. Even if his skin was not too thick, he could not help but feel a little embarrassed at this moment.

...

EsGod's fleet gradually entered the core of the security perimeter and battled the dynasty's fleet along the way with the battle line being dragged out.

The dynasty's fleet stabilized the space along the way, and neither party could enter hyperdrive. EsGod's fleet was slowed down inevitably and continued to be harassed along the way.

Millions of battleships exchanged fire, and a large intergalactic war exploded.

Laser beams of different colors flew in all directions and lit up the pitch-black space. The explosions of the battleships became fireworks in the universe.

There was a special fleet in the battlefield that was the long-distance force that Han Xiao had sent out. The fleet weaved around the formation of the Fallen Ark fleet like a flock of crows.

This mechanical fleet had more than a hundred thousand mechanical soldiers, and they were all boosted by his Mechanical Force. Their attributes were boosted and could achieve the strength of a Beyond Grade A Super.

Energy explosion!

Another three enemy spaceships were destroyed, and the mechanical army was about to find their next target. Right at this moment, a dark red energy pillar swept past the explosion and smashed right into the mechanical army, swallowing almost half of the troops.

After the pillar of light disappeared, the mechanical soldiers that were hit by it had been reduced to scrap.

Han Xiao's eyes narrowed upon witnessing such a scene.

"An enemy Beyond Grade A Super has taken action! This isn't an ordinary individual..."

Han Xiao looked in the direction of the attack through the viewpoint of his army. He wanted to see who the enemy was, and EsGod's figure appeared in his sights.

The next moment, Tarrokov, Milizaus, and Beyoni saw Han Xiao's expression change greatly.

"Did you see who the enemy is?" Tarrokov asked.

Han Xiao let out a deep breath and said with a solemn expression, "It's actually... EsGod! It's his main body!"

Everyone was stunned for a moment.

"Isn't the enemy the Arcane Church? Why would EsGod be here‽"

Beyoni was truly shaken. Because he had personally fought EsGod before, he was extremely clear about his strength.

Tarrokov's expression grew solemn. "The Arcane Church must have provided aid to EsGod and gotten him to leave the Central Galaxy. Dammit! To think that they would work together with such a character for the Evolution Cube!"

EsGod's combat strength was famous throughout the universe, but this time, they also had a top-notch Beyond Grade A Super on their side.

Milizaus shook his head and said, "I've fought EsGod many times before, and holding him back won't be a problem. However, I won't be able to be distracted when fighting him, and I won't be able to do anything else.

"Apart from EsGod, the Arcane Church will definitely send out other high-level combatants, and the situation is not to our advantage. Chief commander, what are your thoughts?"

Upon hearing that, Tarrokov fell into deep thought.

The enemy had a single EsGod and a few million battleships on the surface, and they would definitely have three Beyond Grade A Supers and even more battleships being hidden for sure.

On his side, they had three Beyond Grade A Supers and around four million battleships guarding Planet Lighthouse. Their strength was definitely on the losing side, but they would be able to stall for time with the huge buffer zone for their security perimeter. Furthermore, the dynasty had more troops in this Star Field, and they were currently rushing over from various regions.

Tarrokov was currently considering whether he should retreat immediately or wait for reinforcements to arrive.

The enemy's target was Black Star, and if they chose to retreat, they should be able to protect Black Star. However, the dynasty's outpost would definitely be destroyed by the enemy if it was not guarded. Losing the resources was secondary, but they would definitely have to close up their stargate if they did not want to let it fall into enemy hands. If that was the case, the dynasty would temporarily lose the core of their transportation network, and their mobility would be greatly affected.

Upon thinking about that, he then took a look at the battlefield again. Apart from the dynasty's troops that were facing EsGod, the other troops were currently awaiting their orders and keeping their guard up in their respective regions.

He had even sent out a portion of the fleet stationed on Planet Lighthouse as a quick response force to prevent another enemy force from launching an ambush.

After thinking for a moment, Tarrokov let out a long sigh and said with a deep voice, "Although the situation isn't good, we have the ability to hold on. Let's try to stall for time. When the reinforcements arrive, we will be..."

Woo!

Before he could even finish, an ear-piercing alarm went off in the command room.

"Alert! Alert! Detecting an odd spacetime disturbance outside the planet! Spacetime is being shifted to form a wormhole!"

"Wormhole? Transportation gate?"

Tarrokov had a face full of shock; the appearance of a wormhole was truly out of his expectations. It was not because he did not have any preparations. With the Crimson Dynasty's technological skills, they would definitely install appropriate equipment to cut off any long-distance transportation, and it was impossible for the Arcane Church not to know about this.

He did not understand why the Arcane Church would make such a pointless attempt!

Right outside the atmosphere of Planet Lighthouse, space seemed to have been folded. This was the sign of a wormhole appearing. The forces stationed on Planet Lighthouse also made an appropriate response. They immediately triggered the space stabilizing equipment to disrupt the formation of the wormhole. This would work regardless of whether the other party was using magic or technology.

However, the scene that followed truly shocked everyone. Their infallible anti-wormhole equipment was useless. Space continued to fold, but the wormhole did not appear immediately, and a strange scene occurred.

A hazy appearance of battleships appeared outside the atmosphere like an illusion.

Just when everyone was still in a daze, the next moment, the folds in space suddenly flattened out, and these hazy figures became solid. In the blink of an eye, the illusion became reality!

This fleet contained a few million Arcane Church spaceships with the famous Butterfly Flagship!

In that instant, a few million spaceships descended upon Planet Lighthouse!

They had ignored the security perimeter of Planet Lighthouse, and the defenses of Planet Lighthouse had weakened because they had sent out a portion of their fleet. This was the Arcane Church's true strategy.

Tarrokov suddenly seemed to have thought about something, and his expression changed abruptly.

"This isn't wormhole transportation. Only the strategic Universal Treasure of the Federation of Light, [Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device], has such an effect!"

"The Arcane Church actually joined hands with the Federation of Light‽"

Chapter 845: The Battle Begins!

[Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device].

Han Xiao felt his heart shake. He was no stranger to this Universal Treasure. This was the Universal Treasure that the Federation of Light had spent a vast amount of resources to forge. It was technology that belonged solely to them. Just like how the Evolutionary Civilization created the Evolution Cube, all civilizations that had reached the level of a Universal Civilization had more or less crafted their own Universal Treasure.

The principles of this item were related to the principles of multi-dimensional projections and appearance. It upgraded an entire fleet to a higher dimension and transported them to their destination before restoring the original dimension of the troops.

In essence, it was like transforming the universe into a flat 2D plane and transforming the troops to be transported into a 3D object. Because the obstructions within a 2D plane were not able to affect a 3D object, the transported object could move about freely on the surface of the 2D plane.

It was extremely difficult for a normal wormhole to emulate the effect of the [Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device], and this technological skill had always been a strategic trump card of the Federation of Light during the exploration era. All their troops had extremely high mobility, and it was frightening in times of war.

By relying on this technology, the Federation of Light fleet had been able to defeat numerous enemies during the exploration era and survive until the new generation.

It naturally had a flaw as well. First, the amount of resources consumed every time it was activated was extremely frightening and increased with the distance of the transportation. Second, it required a long time to charge up. Third, it required extremely precise coordinates for a long-distance transfer. Fourth, [Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device] was large equipment similar to a stargate and would not be transported together with the fleet. Thus, the fleet being sent out would not be able to return via the same method unless they brought another [Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device].

The Federation of Light naturally would not lend their specialty Universal Treasure to the Arcane Church, and they did not have any obligation to help the Arcane Church retreat.

"My goodness, even the Federation of Light had intervened..."

Looking at the descending Arcane Church fleet, everyone in the command room was shocked, and their mood sunk.

Han Xiao had never expected the enemy to work together with the Federation of Light and appear on Planet Lighthouse with special equipment.

The cooperation between the Federation of Light and the Arcane Church was something that was impossible for him to predict, and both parties kept their plans confidential. As such, the dynasty's intelligence net had not been able to gather any news about it.

Tarrokov forecast that the enemy would attack from the outside and thus sent out a large number of battleships, which resulted in the defenses of Planet Lighthouse being empty. Currently, they only had little more than a million battleships. However, the enemy had a few million battleships, and they were right outside the atmosphere.

The situation had immediately swung against their favor, and Planet Lighthouse was now in danger.

The entire control room became silent, and everyone was shocked by the sudden change in the situation.

Tarrokov broke the silence and maintained his cool. "Apart from the fleet blocking EsGod's troops, all other troops are to return immediately. There's no need to keep guard anymore. Inform the forces stationed at the stargates to destroy all stargates. We mustn't let them fall into enemy hands."

"Destroy all the stargates? Are you crazy‽ That is our only route to retreat!" Beyoni burst out with rage.

"The stargates are too close to Planet Lighthouse, and the Arcane Church will definitely send their troops to capture them," Tarrokov replied expressionlessly. "Our troops are on the losing side, and our defenses will be weakened if we try to defend them. The combined forces of EsGod and the Arcane Church are more than twice ours, and it will be impossible for us to fight on two separate lines. We cannot separate our troops any further at such a moment."

"But without the stargates, our route of retreat..."

"We are already in a desperate situation without any routes of retreat," Tarrokov said with a solemn voice. "Our only hope is to gather all our forces and defend Planet Lighthouse while waiting for our reinforcements to arrive. Even though we don't have the stargates, our warehouse still has plenty of stargate equipment, and we can create another stargate channel on the spot when our reinforcements arrive at the entrance on the other side. However, our reinforcements haven't arrived yet, and we will only hasten our demise if we spread out our army."

Tarrokov tried to sound extremely confident, but everyone there knew that actually carrying out such a plan would definitely be difficult. Setting up a new stargate required some time, and the enemy would not watch by the side quietly!

When their reinforcements reach the entrance, they would have to set up a stargate in front of their enemy, and a bitter battle will break out. The problem was, they might not even be able to survive until the reinforcements arrived.

Six figures suddenly appeared in front of the Arcane Church fleet.

After seeing their appearance, Tarrokov could not help reeling in shock.

'Child of Light' Sagman, 'Desolate Beast' Mercer, 'Divine Spell' Ninjia, 'World Gate' Taylor, 'Star Pupil' Psyker, and 'Sea Spirit' Dylan.

Six Beyond Grade As‽

That was twice the number that they had!

Together with EsGod, who was on the outside reinforcing them...

Tarrokov, Milizaus, and Beyoni felt their hearts sink. The Arcane Church was truly resolute and was not afraid of starting a war with the dynasty.

Milizaus and Beyoni already felt some regret. They had volunteered to be Black Star's bodyguards because of the Evolution Cube, and their lives might be sacrificed this time.

We really shouldn't have interfered this time...

They could not help but look toward Han Xiao, but they realized that Han Xiao already had his eyes shut.

"What are you..."

Before they could finish their question, a powerful surge of Mechanical Force burst forth from Han Xiao's body, and the energy level in Han Xiao's body increased rapidly.

Upon witnessing the descending Arcane Church troops, Han Xiao could not be bothered with the others in the room and immediately put all his experience into leveling up.

During such an urgent situation, he could no longer be bothered about the waste because of the penalty! Every little bit of strength would count!

It has been seven to eight months since he entered the Beyond Grade A level, and Han Xiao had accumulated a huge reserve of experience during this period.

Even with the forty percent penalty, the experience that he had was enough to increase his level from 240 to 260!

His cells oozed out with energy, and his entire body erupted with power!

A series of notifications popped up on the interface.

...

_____________________

[Emperor Mechanic] leveled up to Lv.35 (Max).

+1000 Energy, +5 STR, +5 DEX, +8 END, +12 INT.

You have received 10 Free Attribute Points.

You have received 1 Potential Point.

Main Class level limit achieved.

You have triggered Class Advancement Mission: [All Rivers Run into the Sea]

[All Rivers Run into the Sea]: Pay a visit to 100 Grade A and above Mechanics and have a Mechanic skill exchange with them. A powerful Mechanic will never close the doors of his workshop but knows how to increase his strength through learning.

You have reached Lv.260.

You have triggered the Promotion Mission [Never-ending Challenger].

[Never-ending Challenger]: Personally challenge a Beyond Grade A Super and survive (Summoning Creatures and Long Distance troops are disallowed). The battle cannot be less than thirty seconds, and you cannot leave the battle during the period. After completing the requirement, leaving the battle will complete the mission.

_____________________

Upon reaching the level 260 bottleneck, his Class Advancement and Promotion mission arrived at the same time.

All the Random Rewards that he had accumulated during this period did not give him a Mission Completion Card. Instead, he drew two blank Character Summon Cards and a skill level up card. He only had a single Mission Completion Card left, which was the one left from his previous missions. Thus, he can only choose to skip a single mission.

Upon seeing these two missions, Han Xiao was overjoyed. The heavens had left him a way out!

[All Rivers Run into the Sea] was a Class Advancement Mission that required a lot of time. In the entire universe, finding a hundred Calamity Grade Mechanics was definitely possible, but they would be spread out in all the different regions. This mission would definitely require him to spend a long time travelling and farming favorability points for the other party to be interested in having an exchange with him.

Despite it being extremely troublesome, the advantage was that it was not difficult at all.

In comparison, his Promotion Mission was much harder for ordinary players. Facing a Beyond Grade A Super head on for thirty seconds was a Promotion Mission that would only appear in the later stages. Not losing thirty seconds was not a problem, but the 'surviving' requirement was the difficult one.

There were two common ways for players to complete such a mission. First, go all out and try their luck to see if they died.

The second method was much safer. Join a Beyond Grade A Super faction and farm for favorability points to exchange for a chance to spar. Since it was a spar, the Beyond Grade A Super would not kill them even if they lost. Although it required a lot of time, the second method had a higher chance of success, and the interface would not allow all the players to get stuck on such a Promotion Mission.

However, this mission had no difficulty for Han Xiao. Not to mention a single Beyond Grade A, there were six in front of him, and together with EsGod, the number of Beyond Grade A Supers were as many as Psyker's eyes!

Without any hesitation, Han Xiao used the Mission Completion Card on [All Rivers Run into the Sea].

In comparison, he would be able to complete the Promotion Mission without a short amount of time.

The only problem was that the mission would only be complete after he exited the battle. However, it would not be so easy for him to exit the battle if the enemy wanted to tangle with him. Perhaps he could try to fight his teammates.

Han Xiao turned around abruptly and said, "Beyoni, fight me right now!"

"Huh?"

Everyone was confused.

With the enemy in front of you, has your brain short circuited?

Are you going to betray us for the Arcane Church in order to survive‽

Boom!

Right at that moment, the room suddenly shook, and a series of explosions came from the sky above.

The Arcane Church fleet outside the atmosphere began their attack and shot out psionic cannons while fighting the defensive troops. The huge protective shield around the planet began to flicker under the continuous explosions, and the ground shook.

Just as Tarrokov had predicted, the enemy had indeed sent out another fleet toward the stargate located not too far away and tried to snatch it.

The enemy's fleet began their assault, and the various fleets located on Planet Lighthouse fought back.

With cannon fire being exchanged between both parties, the sky above Planet Lighthouse was colored with a myriad of different colors, and the radioactive explosions were both deadly and beautiful.

On the other side, the most powerful Beyond Grade As 'Child of Light' Sagman and 'Divine Spell' Ninjia began tangling with Milizaus' main body, which was outside the atmosphere.

Milizaus tried to use a transportation spell, but it was disrupted by Ninjia, who was also a Beyond Grade A mage.

Meanwhile, Psyker and the other Beyond Grade A Supers began to charge at the defensive line of the dynasty and rapidly approached the ground. Their target was obviously to destroy Planet Lighthouse's base and force Han Xiao and Beyoni out!

"All ground troops are to block the enemy's attack!" Tarrokov ordered. "Black Star and Beyoni, the four Beyond Grade A shall be left to the both of you. We don't have any other choice."

Although he knew that Black Star was the other party's target, he could not allow a Beyond Grade A Super to avoid battle at such a moment. They would only have a chance to survive if they fought back.

"I understand," Han Xiao said with a solemn expression.

Han Xiao knew that he did not have the time to waste on a spar with Beyoni. He could only complete the Promotion Mission on the enemy.

Swoo!

The next moment, two figures flew out from the base and entered the sky like a black and red ray of light.

Han Xiao opened his secondary dimensional army box and let out his mechanical army. A black current followed behind him as he charged into the sky.

Very quickly, both parties clashed in midair, and the battle began.

Hu!

The six experts froze in midair and glared at each other, their gazes filled with killing intent.

The energy wave of the four enemies was like a large ocean, and Beyoni felt immense pressure.

He knew that he did not have a physique like Han Xiao, and the chances of him dying were even higher than Black Star.

After both parties glared at each other for a few seconds, Psyker said, "I warned you before. Did you not think that this day would arrive when you stole the Evolution Cube?"

Han Xiao completely ignored those words. This was not the time to trash talk Psyker, and he observed the enemies carefully. There was a Pugilist, a Psychic, a Mage, and an Esper.

Four Beyond Grade A Supers... I won't be able to tank their attacks even with my recovery speed. It seems like I will have to use Aurora's Character Summon Card and medicine. I hope that those fellows will be able to arrive quickly to share the burden.

Han Xiao gritted his teeth and threw all his Free Attribute Points into Endurance. His Health then increased by about 200,000.

Since the disparity in their strength was too large, he could only choose to be as tanky as possible.

The six of them then moved at the same instant.

The battle had erupted!

...

On the other side, EsGod was still leading his troops to fight the troops on the security perimeter.

EsGod got Fakisen to ask the Arcane Church when they were going to take action, and the response shocked him.

"The Arcane Church received help from the Federation of Light and killed their way to Planet Lighthouse directly? They even sent out six Beyond Grade A Supers‽"

EsGod's expression changed, and he immediately issued an order.

"All forces, speed up immediately!"

Since the Arcane Church had sent out six Beyond Grade A Supers, EsGod did not know how long Planet Lighthouse could last under such a frightening attack.

If the Arcane Church snatched the Evolution Cube back before he arrived at the battlefield, EsGod did not think that they would fulfil their promise and lend him the Evolution Cube. Furthermore, he would not be able to snatch it from the six Beyond Grade A Supers.

Thus, EsGod was a little anxious and planned to enter the battlefield to take a share of the loot.

Chapter 846: External Reinforcements!

Outside the atmosphere of Planet Lighthouse, a gigantic dragon that looked like a flagship flew around the battlefield with the colorful formation covering its body deflecting all the cannon fire and leaving a series of explosions in its trail.

Milizaus flapped his wings, and his gigantic body shot forward. The magical force in his body surged, and he threw out an endless wave of magical spells to create a huge magical storm on the battlefield.

Two small figures were following beside Milizaus; they were Sagman and Ninjia. 'Child of Light' Sagman's body shone with a golden light, and he tried his best to shatter Milizaus' protective formations. Meanwhile, 'Divine Spell' Ninjia shot out his own spells, and the both of them tied Milizaus down.

Because of his huge size, Milizaus' dodging capability was extremely poor, and he was almost like a living target. However, the strength of his flesh could almost ignore all Mages. His energy was also extremely robust as a result and could strengthen his own spells. Although Sagman and Ninjia could tie him down, the battle between both parties would be a stalemate in the short run.

As the three Beyond Grade A Supers roamed the battlefield, all the battleships in the surroundings were caught up in their battle with plenty of battleships being destroyed.

"Two troublesome fellows..." Milizaus had a grave look in his eyes. Sagman was the strongest among the six, and together with another Beyond Grade A Mage, it was extremely difficult to deal with them.

Although he could face them alone, he would not be able to aid Black Star.

"The objective of these two fellows is to tie me down, but it can also be said that I have tied two of their combatants down. However, Black Star must deal with four people, and even if I attempt to help him, these two will also follow along, so it would be equally dangerous for Black Star... Sigh, it can't be helped. I can only hope that Beyoni and Black Star will be able to hang in there. I won't be able to help them..."

Milizaus was helpless. Even though he was extremely powerful and one of the three pillars of the dynasty, the two Beyond Grade A Supers that he was facing should not be underestimated. He had no choice but to focus all his attention on them.

If he did not choose to step into this mess from the beginning, he would not be facing such danger.

His frustration at his own choice, anger toward the enemy, and worry for his current situation filled his head. Milizaus got more enraged the more he thought about it and let out destructive golden dragon breath toward the sky. It collided with the light pulse that Sagman sent out, and a huge fiery explosion occurred.

Ninjia used a spell to transmit his voice to Milizaus. "Ah, our four comrades are dealing with two of your comrades, and Black Star won't be able to last long. The battle over there will end very quickly, so there's no point in you fighting back. Why not give up now and join our Arcane Church? This is the only way for you to leave alive. You aren't a direct subordinate of the dynasty, so there's no need for you to die for them."

The only reply he received was a shot of dragon's breath.

"Humph, I knew that you wouldn't give in." Ninjia snorted and conjured a magical shield to block the attack.

"Then, let's continue according to our plan," Sagman calmly said. "He thinks that we are only trying to tie him down, and we can create an opportunity to use the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter."

"Sure!"

At this moment, Milizaus was unaware that he was also one of the Arcane Church's targets!

...

Han Xiao and Beyoni had also begun fighting the four opposing enemies.

The instant the battle erupted, Han Xiao activated the Reynold Character Summon Card without any hesitation, and his Mechanical Force expanded rapidly.

Perfect Mechanical Sense!

This Character Summon Card could only be used three times, and this was the last time!

The 1.4 times Machinery Affinity immediately increased the strength of his mechanical army to the next level. The densely packed mechanical army around him opened, fire and their firepower engulfed the entire sky.

The four instantly moved. A blue light flashed in Dylan's eyes, and sea water shot out from his body to form a gigantic water dragon. The water dragon curled around his comrades and formed a barrier. Under his control, the water barrier was greatly pressurized and transformed into a solid shield.

Psyker did not remain idle either and released his psychic force to cover the water barrier and increase its defenses.

Boom!

One wave of fire after another crashed down on the water barrier and psychic shield. The shield was broken many times, but it was quickly repaired by Dylan and Psyker each time. Under their combined strength, Han Xiao's mechanical army needed to break through the defenses of two Beyond Grade As.

The four enemies would not stand still and receive the attacks, so they began to move at high speed as well.

'Desolate Beast' Mercer was a gray beastman over seven meters tall, and his appearance looked like a beast that was standing up straight. He was covered in a thick layer of fur from head to toe and was extremely muscular. He had simple custom-made armor on and was currently covered in green Pugilist flames.

Han Xiao was already covered with his mechanical suit, and he was extremely experienced in dealing with Pugilists after fighting Heber. He kept changing his location and operated his mechanical troops to block the other party while maintaining a gap with Mercer.

Facing four powerful enemies, Beyoni, who was by the side, did not dare remain idle and activated his Esper Ability. His main target was Dylan, and he lit up Dylan's sea water to form a blazing ocean. The water barrier instantly transformed into a large ball of mist after coming into contact with the sea of flames.

Right at this moment, Han Xiao and Beyoni felt a strange fluctuation in space and turned around to look up. They then saw 'World Gate' Taylor holding on to a staff and chanting an incantation. A gigantic magical formation then appeared behind him.

Boom!

Palace doors being pushed open sounded in Han Xiao's ears, and the formation behind Taylor revealed a crack in the middle and transformed into a gigantic door of light.

Inside the door of light was a pitch-black world with red light dots like fireflies as though they were the eyes of a living creature.

"This is... a summoning formation!" Han Xiao's eyes narrowed.

Ra!

The next moment, countless blood red creatures let out a roar and charged out from the door of light like a flood of blood!

These creatures looked like mutated bats. They had sharp claws, bone spikes, a long horn on their head, and blood red eyes that glowed in the dark. Their appearance looked no different from the relatives of demons.

The moment these summoned creatures appeared, they immediately charged at the mechanical army, and both parties began fighting in midair.

Flesh collided with metal, with blood and oil being spilled. Chunks of flesh and destroyed spare parts rained down from the sky.

Taylor was also a Mage but specialized in summoning spells. This was how he got the nickname 'World Gate'.

"A Summoner is extremely disadvantageous to me..." Han Xiao gritted his teeth.

Army Style Mechanics and Summoner Mages were the two gangster classes who made use of a Human Wave Tactic. The difference between the two was that a Mechanic burned money and could construct an army before the battle to appear instantly, but a Summoner could only slowly summon their babies during battle by burning mana.

Currently, Han Xiao's mechanical army had over ten million soldiers, and it would take a very long time for Taylor to summon the same number of creatures. As such, the first batch of summoned creatures would not be able to deal too much damage to the mechanical army. But if he allowed Taylor to continue casting his spell and summon more creatures, Han Xiao's Human Wave Tactic would be greatly weakened.

If they were fighting a one-on-one battle, Han Xiao had a dozen different ways to disrupt the other party's summoning. However, they were currently in a group battle, and he had a numerical disadvantage. Thus, it was many times more difficult to stop Taylor from summoning creatures.

"The Pugilist is taking up a forward position to apply pressure to me while the Psychic and Esper control the battlefield from the side. Thus, the Summoner won't have to face any pressure at all. This is truly a good combination."

Han Xiao felt his head ache. The enemy had obviously come prepared.

Beyoni understood this point, and he immediately included the summoned creatures as part of his target.

Whoosh!

His area of effect ability was equally powerful, and waves of summoned creatures were burnt up without any ability to fight back.

"I will deal with him," Dylan said and controlled the sea water to rush toward Beyoni.

He then stepped on top of the wave and shot toward Beyoni like a cannonball.

Beyoni's body was covered in flames, and his Pyre Demon Tribe blood began surging. He spat out a mouthful of flames and evaporated a large wave of sea water in an instant, clashing head on with Dylan in midair.

Fire and water. Red and blue. Both parties refused to back down, and a large amount of steam was created by the clash.

A thick fog gushed out, and both their fields of vision were blocked. However, this was not a big deal to a Beyond Grade A Super.

Han Xiao could not afford to be distracted. The other party only needed to use a single person to tie Beyoni down, and Psyker, Mercer, and Taylor surrounded him together.

The casualties of his mechanical army increased rapidly, and if not for the boost from Perfect Mechanical Sense, the damage would only have been greater.

Han Xiao was in an extremely bad state as well and was continuously avoiding magic, psychic, and pugilist attacks, without even a second to catch his breath.

With his current strength, it was a stretch for him to deal with three Beyond Grade A Supers at the same time. Beyond Grade A Supers all had vast combat experience and worked together extremely well. Their combined strength was not simply an additive one. Thus, Han Xiao could only spend ninety percent of his time dodging and was in an extremely passive position.

As the three of them chased after Han Xiao, they also destroyed all his mechanical soldiers. They had read through Han Xiao's file before and knew of his 'Undying' title.

Although they believed that Black Star would definitely lose the title of 'Undying' under their joint assault, they would only be able to output damage safely after getting rid of Black Star's mechanical army. After all, the mechanical army did pose a threat to them. The boost from the Perfect Mechanical Sense and [Legendary Battle Technique] True Damage could severely injure them if they were not careful.

As such, Psyker and the other two gave Han Xiao's mechanical army special attention.

As his mechanical soldiers were destroyed by the enemy, Han Xiao brought them back with [Waste Modification], and it seemed to be like a back and forth tussle.

"Things will be bad if it continues this way..." Han Xiao muttered to himself bitterly as he avoided the attacks.

Although he was able to repair the mechanical army, there was a limit. In the face of four Beyond Grade A Supers, his mechanical army definitely would not be the one surviving to the end.

If all of his mechanical troops were destroyed, he would be like a toothless tiger and would not be able to fight back regardless of how tanky he was.

...

The defensive troops of Planet Lighthouse had also begun their battle with the Arcane Church's forces.

Milizaus' Armed Dragon Guards had long joined the battle, and the gigantic dragons clad in heavy armor clashed together with the battleships of the Arcane Church.

Hila, Hadavy, Feidin, and all the Black Star Guards had joined the battle outside the atmosphere to help the dynasty fight against the Arcane Church fleet.

All the Calamity Grade officers weaved through the battleships and used their various abilities to destroy one battleship after another.

Although they wished to help Han Xiao, they knew that the battle between the six Beyond Grade A was not one that they could intervene in. They would only drag Han Xiao down if they attempted to do so, and the only thing they could do was battle together with the dynasty's forces.

The Black Star Guards were made up of Calamity Grade elites, and they could display their strength in the battlefield.

Apart from sending out Beyond Grade A experts, the Arcane Church had also sent out a group of Calamity Grade combatants, but the numbers could not be compared to the dynasty.

The Calamity Grades from both parties very quickly found each other, and the killing began.

Hadavy endured the pressure of attacks coming in all directions as he chased after the enemy.

Feidin controlled his psychic force, and his psychic attacks accurately found its mark every time.

In such a large-scale battlefield, an endless supply of souls were present to allow her strength to grow rapidly.

Without holding anything back, the dark red energy of death flooded out like a tsunami.

She then looked up at the battle up in the sky. The six Beyond Grade As were fighting, and the energy waves being sent out were too frightening.

"You'd better not die..."

Hila gritted her teeth and went to search for her next enemy.

...

The battlefield between the six shifted continuously, and the summoned creatures grew larger and larger. On the contrary, the mechanical army dwindled.

Han Xiao and Beyoni became more and more passive.

Han Xiao had also suffered from many attacks, but his recovery rate was powerful, and it would not affect him much.

However, Beyoni was different. He did not have a powerful physique and also did not have any defensive means to deal with Psyker's psychic attacks. As such, his situation got worse and worse.

"This fellow is not going to make it..." Looking at the injured Beyoni, Han Xiao felt his heart sink.

This teammate was his only aid at this moment, and if his only teammate ended up dying, Han Xiao would have to face four Beyond Grade As alone. If that happened, he would be as good as dead.

Right at that moment, Psyker's group of four exchanged glances and suddenly intensified their attacks.

Xiu!

A white jade beast statue that was over a hundred meters tall suddenly spat out gray light toward Han Xiao. This was Taylor's elite summoned creature.

Han Xiao immediately tried to avoid the attack. Information about his void bloodline had already been recorded, and his Void Hyperdrive was being restricted by the enemy.

As a Beyond Grade A Mage, Taylor naturally had many means to control dimensional energy. This was the basic skill of a Summoner. As long as Han Xiao entered the Void Dimension, he would be forced out by the other party not too long later. It would be impossible for him to maintain a Void Dimension Jump for long and thus impossible for him to escape.

In truth, from the moment the Arcane Church's fleet appeared, it was impossible for Han Xiao to escape with the Void Dimension Jump. Even if he abandoned everyone else to escape alone, the Arcane Church's hyperdrive speed would not be slower than him. They would catch up to him very quickly, and he would have to face them alone.

Avoiding the gray light, psychic energy and a water dragon immediately assaulted him. Han Xiao had no choice but to activate his psionic energy and block the attack while trying to evade them.

Right at this moment, a figure appeared in front of him almost instantaneously. This figure was Mercer, and a flaming fist crashed down on him.

"Isn't this the instantaneous movement skill that Heber used before?" Han Xiao was shocked and immediately tried to block the attack.

However, the fist seemed to have passed through Han Xiao's body like an illusion, which proved that the figure in front of him was an illusion.

"Sh*t!" Han Xiao immediately realized what was going on and turned around to look at Beyoni.

Taylor waved his staff, and Mercer appeared beside Beyoni and unleashed a flurry of punches.

Dong! Dong!

Seeing Beyoni being hit, the three others immediately changed their target and unleashed all their firepower on Beyoni!

If he was hit by this wave of attacks in his current state, Beyoni would probably be dead.

Whoosh!

Han Xiao did not consider anything else and made use of his Void Hyperdrive, which was restricted, appearing in front of Beyoni. This short distance was something that he could still manage.

Han Xiao then pushed Beyoni behind him, and he personally endured the combined attacks of the four Beyond Grade As.

Boom!

His mechanical suit was shattered, and his health fell greatly.

Han Xiao felt his entire body ache, and he was sent flying like a ball.

His mechanical army blocked Psyker's group of four without any consideration for their losses, which gave him some time to stabilize his body.

Bearing with the intense pain, Han Xiao took a look at his health.

"This wave of damage is too frightening. If not for me enduring the attack, Beyoni would probably be dead..."

Han Xiao laughed bitterly in his heart. He was truly a meat shield this time.

Beyoni then supported Han Xiao from the side and asked, "Are you alright?"

"I am still fine. I won't die so easily. Don't forget what my nickname is."

Han Xiao then took a deep breath and activated the recovery ability of his cells to let his frightening injuries recover.

"Thank you. If not for you, I would have died..." Beyoni said with gratitude, but his voice suddenly turned depressed. "No, we are still dead for sure, and it is only a matter of time."

"Aren't you stating the obvious? Everyone will die eventually." Han Xiao could not help but roll his eyes.

"..." Beyoni was truly speechless. You still have the time to joke at this moment...

After which, Han Xiao shook his head and said resolutely, "However, today is not the day!"

Just when Psyker's group of four were about to give chase, Taylor said with shock, "Wait a moment. I detect a powerful surge of magical energy approaching us through the secondary dimension. It is extremely powerful!"

Space suddenly began to contort, and a gigantic transportation door appeared.

The dynasty's anti-wormhole apparatus had already been shut down, and Taylor attempted to use his own spacetime magic to restrict the transportation door but realized that the magical fluctuations had exceeded all the Mages that he had ever seen before!

Taylor was shocked. He actually was not able to stop a transportation door with his strength!

The next moment, a gigantic castle appeared from within the transportation door.

"What is he doing here‽" Psyker's eyes widened with shock. As a Beyond Grade A of the Shattered Star Ring, he was too familiar with this castle.

It was the Palace of Hidden Spells!

Austin floated at the top of the Palace of Hidden Spells with his Forbidden Sorcerers behind him.

"Ah, I'm not late, right?"

Chapter 847: Ten Thousand Deity Scepter

The four Beyond Grade As looked at the magical aura being emanated from the Palace of Hidden Spells. Austin's sudden arrival had truly shocked them.

Psyker had a belly full of doubts.

Isn't this darn old man always neutral?

Why would he appear here! Furthermore, it seems like he was here to help Black Star!

Psyker was enraged. "Austin, did you join the Crimson Dynasty‽"

"Nope." Austin smiled.

"Then what are you doing here? This matter has nothing to do with you. Go and continue maintaining your neutrality and not causing trouble here," Psyker said with a deep voice.

"My apologies, I had a deal with Black Star. This matter has nothing to do with the Crimson Dynasty and is a personal matter." Austin chuckled.

In order to borrow the Evolution Cube, he had promised Han Xiao a few conditions during the Tyrant Party. One of them was to help Han Xiao with a single matter that did not go against his principles. This was why he was there.

As soon as Han Xiao noticed the strange actions of the Arcane Church, he had requested Austin's aid in order to be safe. To fulfil his promise, Austin had piloted his Palace of Hidden Spells and secretly arrived at the Flickering World through long distance teleportations.

He did not make use of the Crimson Dynasty's stargate and declared that he was finding other secondary dimensional magical materials to the public.

Because it was extremely common for a Beyond Grade A Mage to find secondary dimensional materials together with the fact that Austin had always maintained neutrality, the outside world did not pay close attention to the movements of the Palace of Hidden Spells. None of them had expected a neutral party like Austin to secretly arrive in the Flickering World without seeking approval from the dynasty.

As gold grade equipment and a Universal Treasure, the value of the Palace of Hidden Spells was definitely astronomical. It was capable of long-distance teleportation and only required little over ten days to arrive at the Flickering World from the Shattered Star Ring. It was far faster than the spaceships of the stowaways. He then found a place to wait and activated the concealment formation of the Palace of Hidden Spells. It would not be easy for ordinary detection equipment to see through the concealment ability of a Universal Treasure.

However, Austin did not know that there were so many enemies at the start. He originally thought that the Arcane Church would not take action, and he would only have to stay there for a period of time to easily complete his promise. Even if he was discovered by the dynasty, the dynasty would not do anything to him with Black Star's testimony.

However, he never imagined the Arcane Church to create such a huge scene!

After being caught in a dilemma for a while, he decided not to watch by the side and led his Palace of Hidden Spells to reinforce Black Star!

As someone who maintained neutrality, he naturally understood that doing so was not to his advantage. But since he had made a promise with Black Star already, Austin would not go back on his word.

Although Austin looked as though he was chuckling and relaxed on the surface, he was cursing in his heart.

He had truly been scammed!

Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief, and his lips curled up slightly. "Darn old man, you've finally arrived. With you around, you can help us share the pressure."

Austin rolled his eyes at Han Xiao and snorted, "I must really be crazy to enter such a battle. I suffered a huge loss from using your Evolution Cube!"

Upon hearing that, Beyoni agreed with those sentiments whole heartedly.

Looking at Han Xiao, who was currently recovering, Beyoni could not help but grumble in his heart.

I shall just keep all my grievances in my heart.

Upon noticing Beyoni's expression, Han Xiao took out a syringe and indicated to Beyoni to lower his defenses.

"What do you want to do?"

"Treat you."

"Sigh, the life force of a Beyond Grade A is incredibly large. What can that little syringe of yours do. I... oh? What did you inject me with‽"

Before he could even finish, Han Xiao injected Beyoni with Aurora's life potion.

Beyoni's face then changed abruptly, and a look of shock could be seen on his face.

He could feel a powerful surge of life filling his entire body. The cells of his body all cheered with joy and became extremely active. The recovery of his wounds had also sped up many times over.

Although he was not fully recovered, he was no longer severely injured.

"Just what is this medicine? To think that the effect would be so great on a Beyond Grade A!" Beyoni was shocked.

"You still have time to be curious? First deal with the situation before us."

Although Psyker's group of four had stopped their attacks, the mechanical army was still fighting the summoned creatures. Since the mechanical soldiers that had received Han Xiao's Mechanical Force boost were still in combat, it was akin to Han Xiao being in combat. Furthermore, he would need to leave the battle for five minutes, and it was far from enough.

Despite the enemy being shocked, they would not remain idle for such a long time. Upon seeing Austin determined to interfere, they all accepted the reality and also treated Austin as their target.

Austin activated the Palace of Hidden Spells and triggered all the formations to absorb dark energy. With a humming sound, the Palace of Hidden Spells began glowing with magical radiance, and rays of magical energy were shot out.

On the other side, Mercer who was extremely close to Han Xiao appeared right in front of Han Xiao, and his fists smashed down on Han Xiao's head.

With such a short distance together with the fact that he had just used the Void Hyperdrive and had the paper Beyoni behind him, Han Xiao activated the Heber Character Summon Card, and his Strength increased by four thousand points!

A powerful force exploded from his muscles, and Han Xiao also threw a punch in response.

Bang!

The fists collided with each other, and a shockwave was sent in all directions, clearing out the fog in the area.

Mercer could feel a strength no weaker than his own colliding with his fist, and his body was sent flying uncontrollably. Upon stabilizing his body, he realized that Han Xiao had also been sent flying.

Both parties were sent flying, and their strengths were equal!

"Why do you have such strength?" Mercer had a face full of shock.

His most powerful attribute was his strength, but a Mechanic was actually able to compete with his strength‽

Are you kidding me? Do you deserve to be called a Mechanic‽

Waving his arm, Han Xiao gritted his teeth. Heber's Character Summon Card could allow his attributes to match up to the enemy, but the Pugilist's flames had an extremely destructive capability that destroyed plenty of his cells.

By borrowing the force of the collision, Han Xiao retreated together with Beyoni and hid within the defensive line of his mechanical army. At the same time, he began to analyze the situation.

"Milizaus is able to tie two people down, and the battle on my side is now three against four. Although the opponents have one more person, Austin has the Palace of Hidden Spells and can endure more pressure. We will no longer be on the losing end and can barely hang in there...

"However, the enemy still has powerful reinforcements. If EsGod arrives on the battlefield, the balance would be broken.

"Austin's Palace of Hidden Spells can bring me along to escape, and a single Mage shouldn't be able to stop him. However, the enemy has two Mages, and they will definitely be able to restrict the transportation of the Palace of Hidden Spells if they work together. If I want to run, I can only bring Beyoni along. If I want to bring Milizaus along as well, the enemy Mages will end up working together, and we won't be able to escape...

"There is still another problem. The Palace of Hidden Spells needs some time to charge up, and the other Mage definitely won't let their target escape so easily. He would abandon Milizaus and attempt to stop us. If Milizaus sees us abandoning him to escape, he won't remain behind to risk his life and tie Ninjia down. When Ninjia turns around to deal with us, Milizaus will probably use his teleportation spell to run away. At that time, the Palace of Hidden Spells will still be left behind, but we will lose a powerful ally like Milizaus."

Han Xiao's expression was solemn. If they wanted to rely on the Palace of Hidden Spells to escape, they would only be able to abandon Milizaus. However, the chances of success were too low, and it was likely that Milizaus would choose to seize the opportunity to escape. If that happened, they would lose a combatant, and their situation would be even more dire.

If he really chose to escape, the dynasty's troops would definitely be wiped out. Regardless of whether it was the Armed Dragon Guards or his Black Star Guards, none of them would be able to survive.

It would also be difficult to get the Palace of Hidden Spells to send reinforcements. Even the [Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device] had an upper limit to the transportation distance, and the Palace of Hidden Spells was the same. Furthermore, Heber and the two other reinforcements were in different Star Clusters, trying to rush toward Planet Lighthouse through stargates. Thus, the Palace of Hidden Spells would not be able to bring their reinforcements to them either.

"Tarrokov was right. We don't have much of a choice. We can only choose to hold on until our reinforcements arrive at the entrance of the stargate." Han Xiao gritted his teeth.

The more powerful he was, the greater his hope. He only needed to leave the battle for his mission to be completed, and he had to find an opportunity...

It would not be too realistic to wait for the enemy to stop, so he had to try another method.

...

After Austin joined the battle, the intensity of the battle went up a notch, and it was impossible for anyone under Beyond Grade A to intervene.

The Palace of Hidden Spells was Austin's combat equipment, and it boosted his magical force to a large extent. It was like a magical artillery tower firing without stopping.

Despite the battle being a three-on-four situation, the battle was no longer one-sided, and neither party could do anything to the other in the short run.

Han Xiao had someone to share the pressure with him, and his mechanical army now posed a greater threat to Psyker's group of four. The enemy had no choice but to be more wary and decrease the intensity of their attacks.

Taylor also could not summon creatures without any pressure anymore, and his summoning was interrupted time and time again.

The four Beyond Grade As had intentionally separated the Palace of Hidden Spells from Han Xiao, and they discussed their battle strategy while fighting.

Psyker used his Psychic force to connect his comrades and said with a grave voice, "Austin has the aid of the Palace of Hidden Spells, and his combat capability has been increased to the next level. It is extremely difficult to deal with him."

"Tsk, I wouldn't be afraid of him if I could bring my own Mage Pagoda along." Taylor was a little frustrated with his summoning spells being disrupted.

All Beyond Grade A Mages had their own Mage Pagoda, but not all of them were able to craft a Universal Treasure like the Palace of Hidden Spells.

Taylor and Ninjia did not bring their own Mage Pagodas because they were extremely bulky. After being sent over by the Federation of Light, they would have to leave on their own, and they would definitely be chased by the Crimson Dynasty fleet. As such, bringing such a bulky Mage Pagoda would only hinder their mobility. Furthermore, they had felt that they would have the absolute advantage, and there should have been no mishaps during the battle. Finally, it was to maintain the secrecy of their operation.

"Take note, Black Star may make use of the Palace of Hidden Spells to escape," Dylan reminded.

"If he has such intentions, I will immediately inform Ninjia to work together with me. I won't be able to stop the Palace of Hidden Spells alone, but both of us should be able to do so if we work together," Taylor said.

"Then Milizaus may make use of the opportunity to escape..."

"Then tell Sagman and Ninjia to hurry up and use the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. If not, force Milizaus over as well. If we really must choose between both of them, we can ignore Milizaus. Black Star is our main target," Psyker said.

Mercer could not be bothered to join the conversation, and he continued to give chase to Han Xiao. He wanted to test Han Xiao's strength again.

...

When the Palace of Hidden Spells appeared, the three battling outside the atmosphere also noticed the situation.

Milizaus was overjoyed at the powerful support that Han Xiao had, but both Sagman and Ninjia's expression became grave.

"Psyker said that the other party is Austin from the Shattered Star Ring. He is here to help Black Star. With one more Beyond Grade A joining in, our advantage has decreased," Sagman said with a frown.

"Four versus six. It will be difficult for us to settle the battle before EsGod arrives." Ninjia shook his head.

The Arcane Church instructed them to finish the mission as quickly as possible and try not to let EsGod join in the battle. It seemed like this objective would not be so easily fulfilled. Han Xiao's trump card was something that they had not expected.

"Don't be in a rush to come to a conclusion."

Sagman suddenly unleashed a light screen that was like the surging waves.

The wave like light energy shattered Milizaus' dragon breath, and the blinding light lit up the dark space.

Milizaus' vision and senses were also affected by the blinding light, and he suddenly felt a sense of fear in his heart that came from his intuition as a Beyond Grade A.

He unleashed his defensive spells without any hesitation and covered himself in layers of colorful magical shields like a tortoise.

Following which, Milizaus flapped his dragon wings and attempted to charge out from the light. Turning around to take a look, he saw Ninjia holding onto a strange looking black staff. With Milizaus' sense of sight, he could clearly see the thousands of small figures engraved on the black staff.

"This is... the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter‽"

The alarm bells went off in Milizaus' head. He was extremely knowledgeable, and it was impossible for him not to recognize this Arcane Church Universal Treasure.

The Arcane Church specialized in the soul, the mind, illusions, and beliefs. They had an unbelievable skill that turned fake 'deities' into a real existence and created artificial 'deities'.

The Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was a Universal Treasure that the Arcane Church created by 'coincidence' using such a skill, and it was impossible to replicate. It was a medium that borrowed the strength of these artificial deities.

Describing it simply, the Arcane Church's 'deities' were like gunpowder and bullets while the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was like a rifle.

If the Federation of Light's Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device was a strategic weapon, then the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was a singular killing weapon!

The might of the attack was not stunning, but it had an unbelievably lethal force toward living beings that had a soul. Furthermore, the more powerful the user, the more frightening the damage. During the exploration era, there were at least three powerful Primordial Ones who had died to this weapon!

The Ten Thousand Deity Scepter needed to use 'deities' as weapons, and the user would experience a backlash. The same person would not be able to use it continuously in a short time, and the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter would receive some damage every time it was used. This was the reason that the Arcane Church rarely used this Universal Treasure and kept it as a deterrent.

Milizaus had not imagined that he would be able to personally witness this infamous weapon in his life!

Just what kind of darn luck do I have? Did Black Star spread his bad luck to me‽

Did I steal your Arcane Church's rice? Is there a need to go so far‽

Just when he was still in a state of shock, Ninjia snapped his fingers, and the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter floated in front of him, aimed straight at Milizaus.

Ninjia's energy was then sucked into the black scepter, and the engravings on it lit up.

The engravings of the deities lit up and seemed to have become alive. Ten thousand partially transparent projections suddenly appeared and combined into an illusory energy pillar that shot toward Milizaus.

If it was anyone else, they might have been able to avoid this attack. However, Milizaus was not able to do so with his gigantic body. He could only madly release various forbidden defensive spells.

However, the energy pillar went through the shields, which were sufficient to defend against a psionic cannon, as though they did not exist.

Milizaus could only watch as the energy pillar shot through his numerous shields without the slightest restriction and smashed right into his chest.

"Black Star, you @$*%&!#*..."

Before he could even complete his string of curses, his gigantic dragon body trembled, and he lost control of his body as though he was a bird being shot down by an arrow.

His gigantic body was caught up by the gravitational pull of Planet Lighthouse and rapidly crashed down to the planet like a meteor.

Kacha!

The instant the attack landed, a few cracks could be seen on the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter.

"Urgh!" Ninjia let out a mellow grunt.

Sagman, who was by the side, shot out a light hand and grabbed the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. He knew that this attack was not enough to kill the thick skinned Milizaus. Ninjia would not be able to use the weapon again, so it was now his turn.

Chapter 848: Appearance of the Spacetime Amber!

A few minutes earlier...

In the skies of Planet Lighthouse, the seven Beyond Grade As were tangled up in an intense battle. Fire and water collided, magic and psychic energy tangled with each other, and machines collided with flesh.

With a three-on-four situation, the enemy had no choice but to slow their attacks. With the pressure on Han Xiao easing significantly, Han Xiao gradually gained his footing with his powerful recovery ability.

Han Xiao's mechanical army, Austin's Palace of Hidden Spells, Taylor's summoned creatures, Psyker's psychic energy, Dylan's control of water, Beyoni's flames... Various attacks filled the entire battlefield.

The most powerful area of effect abilities still came from the mechanical army. With over ten million soldiers, the psionic cannon fire covered almost every inch of sky. The boost from [Perfect Mechanical Sense] and True Damage from [Legendary Battle Technique] made it such that Psyker's group of four did not dare lower their guard.

Even a Beyond Grade A would not be able to emerge unscathed from such a battle. The summoned creatures and mechanical army that adopted Human Wave Tactics suffered huge casualties.

The mechanical army could be repaired, and the summoned creatures could be summoned without end. Both parties had their own advantages.

If they were fighting a one-on-one battle, Han Xiao would probably have been able to defeat Taylor without using [Perfect Mechanical Sense]. With the boost from the Perfect Mechanical Sense, he would be able to stably defeat the enemy.

However, Taylor had his teammates to tie down Han Xiao's mechanical army and to allow him to summon his summoned creatures more easily to call upon a never-ending supply of helpers.

There were many different summoned creatures of various shapes and forms. There were demonic bats, turquoise statues, plasma snakes, spirit hunters, ghost scepters, and so on. Their combat abilities varied, and they were the beasts that had been groomed by Taylor after signing a contract with him. A powerful Summoner would definitely have a large variety of summoned creatures.

Han Xiao split up three million mechanical soldiers for his AI to control just to deal with these summoned creatures.

The battle between the mechanical army and summoned creatures was like a war between two armies. The mechanical army had extremely good teamwork and could accurately snipe wave after wave of summoned creatures. Thus, their casualties were lower than the summoned creatures.

In the chaotic battlefield, a Mechanical Life squad under Psionic Prime's lead weaved throughout the heavy fire.

The combat artificial intelligence, Sparta, did not take over the body of the Mechanical Lives but was only in charge of issuing strategic commands.

A powerful data processing speed together with the battlefield module displayed the gaps in the rain of bullets and showed the best way to avoid all the bullets. Psionic Prime then followed the predetermined path with his entire team behind him and avoided all the incoming energy beams, blocking all those that could not be dodged with a psionic shield.

The destination of the squad was a group of elite summoned creatures.

Their target was a team of powerful leader-grade demonic bats that were guarding a group of turquoise statues that were firing laser beams. They were all being boosted by the Summoner and had their attributes increased greatly. Plenty of ordinary mechanical soldiers had already been destroyed by them.

"All forces, take note. Our mission is to wipe out the enemy's elites."

Psionic Prime's emotionless voice sounded in the communication channel.

These demonic bats discovered the rapidly approaching Mechanical Life squad and immediately went forward to intercept them.

"The distance between the target is shrinking. Get ready for battle!"

"Target locked on. Open fire!"

The Mechanical Life that belonged to the long-distance attacking squad reverted to their original forms. There were dark energy artillery towers, psionic jet cannons, firepower forts, high energy short range guided missiles, and many other models. They let out a series of long-range attacks.

Boom boom boom!

The leader grade demonic bats opened their demonic shields and charged forward while enduring fire. From time to time, some of their shields would be broken, and they would succumb to the firepower of the mechanical soldiers.

Facing a wave of attacks, the gigantic turquoise statues also turned around with their eyes charging up with white energy. The next moment, a thick magical beam shot out of their eyes and destroyed all the mechanical soldiers and summoned creatures in the way of their target.

"Giant King Kong, attack!"

Behind Psionic Prime, a gigantic shadow descended, and a Giant Soldier that was a few hundred meters tall appeared. It was called Giant King Kong.

Giant King Kong held up a huge psionic shield to protect the members of the team and block all the magical beams.

Bang!

A huge explosion erupted by Giant King Kong only suffered from some external damage.

The thrusters behind Giant King Kong then blasted out at full power, and the gigantic figure crashed into the incoming summoned creatures before landing beside the turquoise statues. Both gigantic figures clashed with each other!

Boom!

It was as though the mountains were shaking!

The turquoise statues suffered from a flurry of punches and turquoise fragments flew in all directions. With both the gigantic creatures engaging in battle, the smaller troops had also begun an intense battle.

These Mechanical Lives were all elites and had grown for a long period of time. There were some of them who were like mini bosses, and their combat capabilities were exceptional. This was Han Xiao's most powerful elite troop.

The armed cavalry, Oathkeeper, beastman warriors, and various other different models of Mechanical Life charged forward in unison. It was a complete one-sided massacre of the summoned creatures.

The spirit hunters that joined the battle were also easily taken care of by the Mechanical Life squad.

Psionic Prime's body was reconstructed many times, and he had easily reduced the demonic bats into piles of meat. He then looked around and realized that his teammates had all finished their battles.

"Humph, easy." Silver Flash released the corpse of a demonic bat. "It's a pity that we are fighting a defensive war. If I could attack, I would be able to unleash all my firepower, and the battle would have been over already."

"Stop bragging!" Scarlet Flame said.

Silver Flash ignored him and looked toward the battlefield of the seven Beyond Grade As. "It's a pity we aren't strong enough. I really wish to help father."

"Father is protecting us," Giant King Kong replied.

"We are the weapons that father created, but he is protecting us. Is this the fatherly love that those living creatures possess?" Silver Flash asked curiously.

Psionic Prime was about to reply, but a large whooshing sound could suddenly be heard from the sky.

Swoosh!

All the Mechanical Lives looked up.

A gigantic dragon was descending rapidly from outside the atmosphere with dragon blood raining down like a thunderstorm. The dragon's body was burning like a meteor, and it crashed through a wave of mechanical soldiers and summoned creatures.

Boom!

The gigantic dragon crash landed on the planet like an atomic bomb with a loud mushroom-shaped dust cloud being formed in the sky!

...

"Was that Milizaus who fell from the sky? He is severely wounded‽"

Han Xiao, Beyoni, and Austin were shocked upon witnessing such a scene.

This shouldn't be the case! Milizaus' strength is sufficient to deal with Sagman and Ninjia, and he shouldn't have been defeated so quickly and with such severe injuries!

The three of them were full of shock and edged toward Milizaus' position, dragging the battle to the ground. Psyker's group of four followed closely behind.

The next moment, Han Xiao and Beyoni landed beside the gigantic crater, and Austin controlled the Palace of Hidden Spells to float in midair. Upon looking at Milizaus' present state, the three of them were shocked.

Milizaus' gigantic dragon body was in an extremely pathetic state. A huge hole had opened up in his chest, and his fractured bones and innards could be seen.

This frightening injury seemed to have been inflicted in a single attack, and Beyoni was truly shocked. He could not imagine just what kind of a frightening attack would be able to cause such damage to Milizaus' robust body.

These were not his only injuries. New cracks can be seen on Milizaus' body as though there was a sort of energy continuing to cause damage to his body and destroying his cells.

Upon seeing that, Han Xiao took out a syringe from his mechanical suit and injected Milizaus with Aurora's life potion. However, it only slowed down the worsening of Milizaus' injuries; he still showed no signs of recovery.

Because Han Xiao injected the wound, a notification popped up on his interface.

The interface showed Milizaus' present situation. His health was currently at sixty-three, and it was still falling. There were a few negative statuses on Milizaus, with two of them being the most frightening.

[Cell Activity Inhibition - High]: All recovery methods will have their effects reduced by 70% (From Ninjia).

[Double Corrosion]: Suffer 12,582 physical damage and 15,733 mental damage every second (From Ninjia).

"Ooh..." Milizaus let out a groan and said to Han Xiao's group of three weakly, "Be careful. They brought the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter."

Before he could finish, Sagman and Ninjia descended, and the six enemies Beyond Grade As were gathered!

Han Xiao raised his head and immediately saw the weapon that had injured Milizaus. It was the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter that was floating beside Sagman.

To think that it would be this infamous Universal Treasure... Han Xiao's expression sank.

The Arcane Church had truly gone all out this time!

"They've even brought this item out?" Austin's expression changed greatly and immediately thought of escaping.

He had already fulfilled his promise and felt that he had done all he could. He did not want to die there because of a promise. It was because of his Palace of Hidden Spells' defense and mobility that he dared participate in such an imbalanced battle. However, the attack of the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was extremely queer, and it was capable of ignoring most physical defenses and shields. The attack could only be avoided but not blocked, which meant that the Palace of Hidden Spells would not be able to help him block the attack.

Austin's thoughts were extremely clear. The Arcane Church's targets were Black Star and the dynasty. Since he was not the enemy's target, the enemy definitely would not waste their Beyond Grade A combatants to chase him if he wanted to escape.

He did not want to experience the feeling of a weapon that could threaten a Beyond Grade A.

This darn old man is thinking of escaping...

Although he did not know how to read minds, Han Xiao knew what Austin was thinking upon seeing his look of hesitation.

The appearance of the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was out of his expectations. If he had known that the enemy had such a trump card, he would not have allowed Milizaus to separate from them.

Han Xiao had a solemn expression and injected Milizaus a few more times. Only then did his injuries stop worsening with signs of recovery.

[Cell Activity Inhibition - High] only weakened the effect of Aurora's life potion, but with a large stock in his possession, Han Xiao only needed to give a few more injections for the same effect. It was just that the recovery time needed would be longer.

However, the six Beyond Grade A enemies definitely would not give them so much time.

Whoosh!

The six of them floated in midair and looked down at Milizaus, Beyoni, and Han Xiao. A shocking pressure descended from the sky, but Austin was actually blocked out by their pressure.

Psyker looked at Austin and said, "Stop interfering with us. This is the final warning."

"..." Austin looked at Han Xiao and twitched his lips, not daring to make another move.

The Ten Thousand Deity Scepter then floated in front of Sagman and aimed at the immobilized Milizaus.

A look of despair could be seen in Milizaus' eyes. He was extremely clear about his current situation. Although Han Xiao had managed to help him recover with some magical potion, he would definitely be driven to the brink of death if he took another attack.

Just as Sagman was about to activate the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, Han Xiao took a deep breath and said loudly, "Do you guys want the Evolution Cube‽"

Sagman stopped moving and narrowed his eyes.

"You want to hand it over in exchange for a chance to survive?"

"That's right." Han Xiao let out a deep breath and deactivated the Spacetime Amber sealing effect.

The six of them then looked at the silver cube in Han Xiao's hands.

Right then, Psyker's psychic connection to the Evolution Cube was restored, and he said with confirmation, "It's the real deal."

Sagman nodded upon hearing that and said to Han Xiao.

"Do you even have the right to negotiate? We can still get the Evolution Cube if we kill you. Why do we have to agree to your demands? The choice to kill or capture you is in our hands. Do you even have the right to choose?"

"No, you are wrong." Han Xiao tightened his grip on the Evolution Cube. "If I destroy the outer covering of the Evolution Cube and release its gigantic main body... Haha, do you think that you can take it away before the dynasty's reinforcements arrive?"

Sagman's eyes narrowed, but he was not too surprised by those words.

Before they took action, the Arcane Church had already guessed that Black Star may choose to destroy the outer covering of the Evolution Cube and had already made preparations.

EsGod's chips for negotiating with the Arcane Church were information on the Evolutionary Civilization and the apparatus to allow the Evolution Cube to be carried around. However, EsGod would only provide information on the apparatus after their deal was completed.

Thus, it would save them a great deal of trouble if Black Star was willing to hand over the portable Evolution Cube.

With the authority to determine Han Xiao's life and death, Sagman said with an aloof attitude, "Alright, I won't kill all of you if you hand over the Evolution Cube and surrender. The upper echelons will definitely be interested in seeing the dynasty pay a hefty price in exchange for all of you."

He was the representative among the six and had the authority to make decisions on the ground. Capturing them was better than killing them. Although it would still anger the dynasty, they would have more chips to bargain with the dynasty.

Although Milizaus was frustrated about the crisis that Han Xiao had brought to him, he could not help but feel a sense of desolation in his heart upon seeing Han Xiao take out the Evolution Cube to save their lives.

At this moment, he suddenly felt Han Xiao stepping on him secretly and knew that Han Xiao had a plan. Thus, he connected the three of their minds with magic.

Han Xiao then heaved a sigh of relief and said, "As proof of my sincerity, I shall tell you the secret password to activate the portable Evolution Cube."

As he said those words, he didn't wait for Sagman's response and quickly activated the sequence.

There was indeed a special method required to activate the Evolution Cube, and Han Xiao's words were not wrong. Showing it to them on the spot would prevent them from being fooled by EsGod's information.

"Hmm? You'll have more than enough time to show us after you become a captive..." Sagman did not realize anything at the start and only frowned. However, he immediately noticed something and roared, "No! Stop!"

Han Xiao ignored those words and completed the sequence.

Hu!

The next moment, he activated the evolution energy within the cube and sent it toward the six in the sky.

The six of them immediately raised their shields. If they were struck by the evolution energy, they would become a black cocoon and start the evolution process. Although they could forcefully stop the process and recover their movement, they would still be restricted for some time.

Sagman's murderous intent toward Han Xiao immediately exploded.

You don't know how to treasure the opportunity that I have given you and tried to ambush us!

Without any hesitation, Sagman activated the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter and aimed it at Milizaus. After killing Milizaus, they would have more than enough time to slowly torture Black Star!

Ohm!

The Ten Thousand Deity Scepter shot out an energy pillar.

Milizaus thought about Han Xiao's words and could only choose to trust Han Xiao. He then ignored the attack from the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter and unleashed his magical attacks at Sagman's group of six.

Beyoni also did the same thing and unleashed his attacks to restrain them.

The mechanical army also received the order to open fire!

On the other side, Han Xiao released a few machinery balls, which floated in the path of the energy pillar. The machinery balls formed two layers of barriers in front of him.

Following which, these machinery balls underwent nano transformation and revealed a half transparent amber ball within them.

After spending half a month on Planet Lighthouse, Han Xiao had already made use of the Spacetime Amber to craft plenty of amber balls!

The six from the Arcane Church retreated to avoid the evolution energy while dealing with the attacks from Han Xiao's group of three.

Looking at this scene, a mocking look could be seen on Sagman's face.

"A shield? A shield is completely useless... what‽"

Before he could finish his sentence, the scene before their eyes shocked the six of them.

The energy pillar of the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter did not go through the half transparent spherical shaped shield but shot in all other directions like a pillar of water landing on a lotus leaf. Not a single bit went through!

Milizaus and Beyoni also had looks of disbelief on their faces. Han Xiao had previously said that he would be able to block the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, and they could only choose to believe him. Upon seeing Han Xiao's success, they could not help but be stunned.

The reason Han Xiao was so certain was not because of blind confidence in the Spacetime Amber. In his previous life, during the World Tree Civilization war, the Arcane Church had used the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, which failed because of the Spacetime Amber!

Boom!

Just when the enemy was in shock, Han Xiao, who already knew that the Spacetime Amber would be able to stop the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, scattered the amber ball shields and shot them toward the enemy.

Sagman's group of six had already snapped out of their shock and wanted to retrieve the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter.

However, the scattered amber balls disrupted all the enemy's psychic, magic, and light attacks!

The six of them could not imagine that these half transparent shields were capable of blocking all their attacks without being damaged in the slightest.

"Just what is this strange item? It is actually able to stop all attacks‽"

Just when they discovered that, despite physical attacks being useless against these amber balls, they were still able to send the amber balls flying through the force of their attacks, it was far too late!

Han Xiao activated his Void Hyperdrive and held onto the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter before charging into the air!

With the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter being snatched, Sagman's group of six abandoned the others without any hesitation and gave chase to Han Xiao.

With one running and six chasing, the six of them caught up in less than a minute.

The combined attacks of six Beyond Grade A was not something that he could block, and he was sent flying helplessly.

His health fell rapidly, and Han Xiao threw the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter away.

Sagman immediately stretched his hands out to catch the scepter and snatch it back.

But before he could even heave a sigh of relief, he realized that the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was sealed into a half transparent spherical ball.

Energy was not capable of passing through the ball, and the shape of the ball was the same as those shields that blocked the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter!

Sagman's expression changed greatly!

"Just what did you do‽"

Chapter 849: The Scheme Deepens as EsGod Appears!

Light energy impact, magic energy rays, pugilist fluctuations, psychic bombs, and more Beyond Grade A attacks were concentrated. Han Xiao's psionic shield collapsed, his mechanical suit shattered, and he flew backward uncontrollably.

His gaze spun, and the stars in the universe seemed to all turn into shooting stars. It took him a lot of effort to finally stabilize, hovering in outer space. His entire body was wracked in pain, and his cells were constantly annihilating yet regenerating.

Not far behind him was the huge interstellar battlefield where the fleets were fighting. Beneath him was the outline of a gray planet. Sagman retrieved the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, and upon noticing Han Xiao's tweaking to it, his expression contorted.

Upon seeing his opponents' expressions, Han Xiao smiled even though his body was convulsing in pain.

This was worth it!

Due to the threat the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter posed, even if one could only fire off a single shot in a short period of time, having six of them meant that the scepter would be fired six times. If he had left them alone, his side would not even have had the opportunity for a comeback. The only method was to freeze the enemy's Ten Thousand Deity Scepter.

And the core of this plan lay in the Spacetime Amber, which could lock up the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter!

What occurred previously was truly a desperate situation for him. He had first pretended to surrender, taking out the Evolution Cube under their supervision, before causing trouble. Then, his teammates as well as his mechanical army added on to the chaos. From his experience in his previous life, by allowing his barrier formed from amber to ward off the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, the opponents would reveal flaws due to their surprise and shock. Then he used the Spacetime Amber to prevent the Arcane Church from retrieving the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter.

For the first time, the Spacetime Amber showed its prowess in the universe. The enemy was unaware of its effects and was rendered speechless. Only then did he get the opportunity to brief grab the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter.

Because of the soul link, the production efficiency of Spacetime Amber was accelerated. The scepter was not a large object, so the delay was enough to seal it!

Now that the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter has been sealed in amber, it has been cut from their energy. They are not able to open the amber, and thus, for this battle, they will not have such an overpowered killing weapon!

Han Xiao clenched his fists in excitement. Having disabled the enemies' ultimate, they could still make a comeback!

Sagman grabbed hold of the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter sealed in amber. His hands shone with a bright light as he pressed it on the amber, but it was useless as the amber would not budge. The light particles flowed around the surface of the amber, turning it into a golden egg.

The other five by the side could not sit still and joined hands, but even then, the amber remained intact. They could only stare at the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter encased within.

"What sort of nonsense is this thing? How could it not break‽" Sagman stared at Han Xiao, and relying on Psyker's mental waves, he bellowed, "B*stard, what have you done‽"

There was no mention of such a skill on Black Star's intelligence. They had been caught unprepared. To think that Black Star still had such a trick up his sleeves!

Han Xiao chuckled in his heart.

Having only obtained the Spacetime Amber in the Flickering World, he had yet to reveal it, and thus, the intelligence from the universe was naturally behind.

Han Xiao chuckled to himself before speaking in a jovial manner. "What have I done? This Ten Thousand Deity Scepter of yours is such a precious thing. I even added another layer of locks so that it will be completely safe. No need to thank me. It's free! Are you satisfied with the service provided?"

His sarcastic tone infuriated Sagman, causing the flames in his heart to soar.

He had originally thought that Black Star and the rest had no way to resist, that their victory was set in stone. But to think that they got fooled!

Even after using all their methods, they were unable to unlock the amber. Sagman gritted his teeth, passing the scepter to Ninjia.

"Keep it. We can't break through Black Star's methods now. But at least the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter is still in our hands. When we return, we'll let the Arcane Church research how to get it out."

Ninjia could only helplessly follow.

The Arcane Church had passed this Universal Treasure to them in order to allow them to handle Milizaus quickly, but right now, not only were he and Sagman sapped of the majority of their strength, the situation had gone downhill. They did not even manage to get rid of one of the three pillars of the dynasty. What a loss!

Not only that, the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was sealed through some unknown means by Black Star, and their hidden ace had been rendered temporarily unavailable. It was impossible to quickly resolve this battle now, and their best form of deterrence against EsGod was also gone. This was like going to steal a chicken but not even getting rice!

Seeing Ninjia stow away the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, a mocking expression appeared on Han Xiao's face. He knew that this bunch would definitely think that the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was only temporarily rendered unusable. They thought that by returning, the Arcane Church would be able to find out a method to remove the Spacetime Amber.

Heh, they still do not understand the severity of this matter...

The corners of his mouth rose up. The Spacetime Amber was the remnant of Spacetime Freezer, and its ability was derived from that Esper's own ability to freeze spacetime. However, because of it drifting through the universe, it had absorbed all sorts of strange cosmic radiation, which had allowed it to evolve into a Space Wonder.

To be classified as a Space Wonder, they had to be unidentifiable by current theories. Thus, if the Spacetime Amber could be broken apart so easily, there would not have been so many Beyond Grade As fighting over this thing in his previous life.

These thoughts flitted through his mind, and Han Xiao kept his smile as he focused on the six opponents.

While he had sealed the trump card of his opponents, six Beyond Grade As were still a force to be reckoned with.

He had only completed a staged counterattack, and the battle had far from ended.

The several people confronted each other for more than a minute in outer space. Beyoni, Austin, and Milizaus quickly caught up.

Seeing that this plan had succeeded and Han Xiao had restricted the opponents' scepter, a praising glow could be seen in Milizaus' eyes.

You're really reliable, brother!

While you might be the source of this dangerous situation, causing me great injury, seeing that you saved my life, I shall no longer be angry with you!

The gathering of Beyond Grade As had already broken past single digits. The energy fluctuations given off by them clashed with each other, displaying their zone as a region with the highest energy. Just like the scene of countless supernovas, the energy response kept soaring.

"Do it!"

Sagman and others did not wish to procrastinate and attacked. Han Xiao originally wished to trash talk and waste more time, but seeing this situation, he could only retaliate as well.

The ten Beyond Grade As clashed together, moving through the interstellar battlefield and crushing all warships in their way, leaving behind a wake of explosions.

...

At the same time, in the Constellation Corridor, Ruler Urranrell suddenly received the urgent report from Tarrokov and burst into anger when she discovered that the Arcane Church was attacking Planet Lighthouse.

"Arcane Church, Federation of Light..." Urranrell's expression was grim.

It was not that she did not know that these two old enemies of hers would make things difficult when they explored the Flickering World, but she had thought that it would stop at the level of tricks. To think that they really tried to invade the outpost of the dynasty, attempting to kill off three of their Beyond Grade As!

Did they think the Crimson Dynasty was so easy to bully‽

If it was a conspiracy, there was nothing to say, but in a frontal battle, the dynasty would never be afraid!

Urranrell immediately issued dozens of orders to mobilize the dynasty's army. She did not think that there was a chance of survival on the side of Planet Lighthouse, and thus, she began to prepare for the counterattack instead.

The style of the dynasty was always to repay a tooth with a tooth and blood with blood. This was their tradition. If they were not vicious enough, their position would not be stable.

Now that they had been taken advantage of, if they did not produce a reaction similar to that of a rabid dog retaliating, others would think that the dynasty was strong on the outside but weak within.

...

Originally, the players were all exploring outside, but because Han Xiao was situated on Planet Lighthouse, a portion of the players would occasionally head over to check it out. When the battle broke out, there were a few players present on the planet, and one of them was Bun-Hit-Dog. He immediately issued a post on the forums.

"Big event! Planet Lighthouse has been assaulted by an unknown force! There are ten Beyond Grade A NPCs fighting!"

The moment he posted, the players exploring outside were all stunned.

Ten Beyond Grade As, my god, what sort of grand event was this‽

It's only been a while. Why would there be such a big event!

...

On the battlefield, the ten Beyond Grade As exchanged blows. Because of the arrival of Austin as well as the sealing of the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, the Arcane Church's strength had been reduced quite a bit. While Han Xiao and the rest were having a bad time, they would not be defeated in such a short period.

"Do you have any other plans?"

Milizaus was thoroughly convinced by Han Xiao's strategies, and while battling, they were conversing on their mental network.

"There are six of them, and we are still at a disadvantage. Our objective has not changed. We can only wait for reinforcements."

Dodging an energy ray, Han Xiao controlled his army to return fire to repel Sagman.

"The enemies also know of this point... so they want to end this battle quickly. Milizaus might be injured, but he can put up a strong fight. Austin has the shelter of the Palace of Hidden Spells and will not fall easily. As for me, there's no need to talk. The term 'Indestructible Body' is not just empty words. Thus, the enemies are likely to focus on Beyoni. With him being so brittle, he'll probably be the first to die."

"..." Beyoni.

How vicious, to actually leave him with no way to retaliate!

I'm not like you guys, you perverted meat shields. I'm a true Beyond Grade A!

Milizaus was helpless. "Then let him stay behind me. I'll help him to divert the majority of the blows. Do you have any other plans?"

"How about you guys all stay and I escape?"

The three of them had nasty expressions. Brother, the f*ck are you talking about?

"Cough cough, slip of the tongue." Han Xiao dryly coughed before sighing. "There's nothing much I can come out with. We can only fight it out. EsGod is still en route, and if he arrives, the situation will get even more unfavorable..."

Everyone went silent. Upon thinking that there was still EsGod to come, everyone felt their mood darken.

At this moment, Han Xiao made up his mind and solemnly spoke. "Everyone, I have a request. Please protect me for five minutes. I will withdraw from this battle for the next five minutes."

"What are you going to do?" Milizaus stared at him.

"I have an ability to draw out and improve my combat power, but during this period of preparation, I cannot be disturbed. I need you to hold them off for five minutes." Han Xiao naturally would not reveal the presence of his promotion missions and had to come up with an excuse.

Milizaus was helpless. You just said that the situation was grim, but you suddenly chose to withdraw? Also, what kind of ability requires a Beyond Grade A to prepare for five minutes?

"How much combat power can you raise?" Austin suddenly asked.

"It should be quite a bit." Han Xiao did not know exactly.

"Are you sure?" Milizaus spoke in a deep voice. "Even if you do this, you can't become overpowered. Your strength will definitely still be below mine, and this will not affect the current scenario. Without your strength for the next five minutes, we'll be in grave danger. You also know that EsGod has not arrived, and we cannot be inflicted with heavy injuries at this point..."

"It's because the EsGod is not here. That's why I chose to give it a shot! If we wait for EsGod to arrive, the five minutes will be even more dangerous. Before he arrives, I'll increase my combat strength and see if it can give us a chance." Han Xiao gritted his teeth.

This was one of the reasons. The other unspoken reason was that this advancement was no small matter!

Not only was it a Class Advancement, he also had a chance to undergo another Race Evolution, which could bring him new abilities! Furthermore, as long as he broke past this barrier, he would be able to continue levelling up.

His improvement was definitely not small!

At this time, Austin suddenly nodded. "Good, then you enter my Palace of Hidden Spells. I'll protect you for five minutes."

"Can you?"

Han Xiao had an unsure tone. Not too long ago, Austin had still thought of retreating. Now that the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter had been sealed by Han Xiao and there was no immediate danger to him, why did he choose not to escape? To think that someone like him would volunteer to take on such a difficult mission. This was totally different from his impression of the old man that avoided danger.

Could it be that, over time, their relationship had become so good? Or did this old man value credibility?

As though reading Han Xiao's thoughts, Austin revealed a smile.

"The moment that you sealed the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, I suddenly thought that keeping you alive might be a good thing."

Han Xiao paused, thought for a bit, and said, "If I survive this, then I'll give you a bit of Spacetime Amber... I used that previously to trap the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter."

"I was waiting for that!"

Austin burst into laughter. While he wanted to appear magnificent, his soft laugh made him appear more like a newborn than a man.

He was indeed moved by the Spacetime Amber and wished to research what sort of thing it was. But that was not the whole reason.

The Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was defeated against his expectations. The situation now was clear. If he stayed, they could still fight, but if he chose to run, the strength of the dynasty's side would flag, and the rest would be defeated.

Since he had already stepped into this dump, if he ran halfway, he would offend both the Arcane Church and the Crimson Dynasty. However, if he chose to stay and assist Black Star, he would only offend one side. The most important factor was that Austin wished for Han Xiao to continue living. He found this fellow more and more likeable, with all sorts of surprises.

"Isn't it just five minutes?" Austin's eyes glowed. "I'm not so weak that I can't even hold on for that amount of time!"

Han Xiao opened his secondary dimensional army box and collected all his troops. After that, he flew over to the Palace of Hidden Spells, where an opening appeared in its barriers, granting him entry.

No further words were needed. Han Xiao rushed into the palace, summoning a mechanical troop before sealing himself in Spacetime Amber. Since obtaining the amber, he had done a few experiments, which included sealing himself to discover the effect of freezing the Spacetime Amber gave.

His status would appear as [Frozen], and while he could think and sense the outside world, he was unable to communicate or even connect to the Quantum network.

Phillip followed the commands Han Xiao gave and controlled the troops to surround Han Xiao, ready to utilize the Spacetime Amber to unseal him.

Sealing himself was insurance to prevent any disturbances from affecting him.

With only three people left in the battle against the Arcane Church, the pressure increased.

Seeing that Han Xiao had stopped attacking, Sagman and the others did not know what he was planning, but with the example of the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, they were not about to let Han Xiao's actions continue. They concentrated fire on the Palace of Hidden Spells.

Under the intense assault, the shields on the Palace of Hidden Spells were broken one after another in just three minutes, bursting in a splendid display of fireworks.

The entire palace was shaking nonstop, with all sorts of cracks, and many functions were destroyed.

While Austin continuously utilized his Forbidden Sorcerer arts to repair the arrays, the rate of repair was far below that of its destruction. After all, the enemies outnumbered them two to one, and on their side, Milizaus' injuries were steadily accumulating.

The situation was getting more dangerous, but the trio continued to give it their all, dragging out as much time as possible.

Austin's Palace of Hidden Spells was worth its weight in gold and was extremely sturdy. Although its durability kept plummeting, it had indeed blocked out all the enemy attacks.

...

On the other side, the dynasty and Arcane Church's fleets were still fighting fiercely. High energy beams were exchanged rapidly and exploded on the shields of the spaceships in dazzling arcs one after the other.

Tarrokov had long taken control of commanding the battlefield and was strongly resisting the crazed invasion of the Arcane Church.

The Arcane Church's troops outnumbered the dynasty's by a few times, and their dark energy furnace expanded and contracted as though it were breathing, consistently releasing red beams of dark energy rays to batter at the dynasty's barriers.

Their butterfly-model main flagship had already finished combining into a single entity, and its hundreds of pairs of highly ductile 'butterfly wings' opened up, giving the flagship the appearance of a rising sun. On the edge of each pair of wings, faint red light was shining, and a series of light blades were continuously fired, akin to slashing attacks. If one looked closely, the edges of the wings were filled with dense cannons, and they all fired together, like a light blade being activated.

The Crimson Dynasty's reloaded main flagship instead sported a neat formation and orderly artillery fire. It seemed to be able to tear into the universe with an energy beam. All three Universal Civilizations had many different types of warships, and the Crimson Dynasty's were famous for their strong firepower and tough armor.

"How much longer before the troops outside return?" Tarrokov asked while still staring at the star map.

"The first batch should be back via hyperdrive in around four minutes," the Vice commander immediately replied.

Tarrokov nodded. With Planet Lighthouse besieged, he had decided to recall all troops outside, which amounted to another three million warships. With their support, their numbers would be even with the Arcane Church, and their pressure would lessen.

If not for him leading the fleet to withstand the Arcane Church's offensive, they would not even have had the opportunity to wait for reinforcements. He had no extra energy to pay attention to the Beyond Grade A battles and only prayed that Black Star would not fall too quickly.

"Where's the army of the Fallen Ark?"

"Commander, the fleet we sent out is still tangling with the Fallen Ark fleet. I estimate another twenty minutes before they enter."

As Tarrokov nodded, a piercing alarm blared from the radar.

"Warning! Unknown high-energy response source detected! Comparing with database... Comparison completed, target identity: EsGod!"

Tarrokov jumped up and cast his eyes over. On the outskirts of the battlefield, a humanoid silhouette appeared, floating in the vast universe.

EsGod!

"Didn't you say twenty minutes? Why is he..." Tarrokov was about to shout, but he abruptly realized that EsGod had shown up alone, and he immediately understood.

This guy had abandoned his troops and arrived at the battlefield ahead of them!

...

The EsGod turned around, his gaze fixed on the battlefield of the Beyond Grade As.

He was totally unsatisfied with the speed of his fleet and decided to just ditch them, utilizing his Esper Ability to warp large distances, teleporting straight to Planet Lighthouse.

Surveying the entire battlefield, EsGod suddenly narrowed his eyes.

Where did Black Star go‽

Chapter 850: The Key to Victory!

The next moment, EsGod teleported right into the battlefield of the ten Beyond Grade As. As soon as he appeared, everyone's expression changed drastically.

Milizaus' side felt much more pressure. EsGod had arrived so quickly; it had not even been five minutes yet.

The Beyond Grade As of the Arcane Church were also alarmed except one—Psyker who was bombarding the Palace of Hidden Spells with his psychic energy. All seven of his eyes opened wide; he was stunned.

"Why are you here‽"

Due to the hatred born from what happened on Planet Avitan, the Arcane Church had hidden EsGod's involvement in this from him. Seeing that his mortal enemy had appeared, Psyker was furious.

EsGod turned to look at him and smiled faintly, which equated to provocation in Psyker's eyes.

"Calm down," Sagman said with a deep voice in their psychic communication channel. "EsGod is our temporary ally."

Psyker was shocked. His tone became cold. "So, you guys all knew about this?"

The other five kept silent. This was an order from the Arcane Church, but it was indeed not honorable to hide this information together from their ally.

"Dylan, you knew about this too?" Psyker snorted.

"Sorry, I only knew moments before departure..."

Dylan did not want to face the questioning from his good friend, so he vented his unhappiness in his attacks. He closed his palms and aimed at the Palace of Hidden Spells. Water streams flowed around his arm, turning into high energy beams under the effect of his Esper Ability and shot out at the Palace of Hidden Spells.

"Psyker," Sagman said, "the mission is more important."

With gloomy eyes, Psyker decided not to even look at EsGod and focused on attacking.

The middle of a battle was no time to look for revenge. He had to think of his race, so he could not mess up the Arcane Church's plan at such a crucial moment. Therefore, he had no choice but to endure it.

Seeing this, EsGod took his eyes off Psyker, too. Truth to be told, although Psyker was someone significant in the entire universe, he was nothing worth noting to him—those Beyond Grade As he had killed in the past were no weaker than Psyker.

Among all the Beyond Grade As here, only Milizaus and Sagman were worth paying attention to in his eyes. As for Austin, he had only heard of his name but never had any contact with him.

Milizaus was the only one who had killed a Beyond Grade A before like him. EsGod had fought with this old dragon many times and knew how strong he was. Therefore, when he saw Milizaus' wounds, shock flashed through his eyes.

"That wound came from just one attack. The Arcane Church definitely used some kind of special weapon, or he would not have been wounded this heavily so quickly." EsGod narrowed his eyes and increased his caution of the Arcane Church.

However, at the moment, he was still on the same side as the Arcane Church. He observed the battlefield and could not find Black Star and his army. Confused, he connected with Sagman's mind and asked, "Black Star isn't here. Have you guys let him escape?"

Sagman shot out a pale gold impact wave that penetrated Milizaus' magic defenses and exploded on his back, tearing off a huge portion of his flesh and scales. He then replied with a deep voice, "Black Star has exited the battle and hidden in the Palace of Hidden Spells. No idea what he's trying to pull."

"He's hiding?" EsGod paused and asked, "Has the Evolution Cube been confirmed to be on him?"

"Yes, he took it out and used it earlier."

"Okay." EsGod nodded. The next moment, he teleported right above the Palace of Hidden Spells and stepped on the surface of the defense spell. The flow of magic from the spell did not affect him at all.

Austin, who was sitting atop the Palace of Hidden Spells, looked up and saw EsGod. The two of them were separated by thick layers of defense magic arrays.

Austin's eyes became focused. He opened his arms, and the dozens of magic books around him started flipping their own pages.

Swoosh!

As the pages of those books turned, colorful magic runes appeared from within and quickly landed on the Palace of Hidden Spells. They then teleported into the control core of the Palace of Hidden Spells—this was how the Palace of Hidden Spells was operated.

The next moment, the arrays within a thousand meters under EsGod's feet suddenly changed color. Magic energy turned violent, and a magic impact wave shot up from below EsGod like a fountain and devoured him.

As Austin looked up to observe the result of this attack, a stranger's voice appeared behind his ears. The voice was like a thunder in his mind.

"The Magus, Austin. I see, you're not too bad."

Out of nowhere, EsGod suddenly stood behind him. Using Energy Reflection, Plasma Body, Dimension Crack, and Teleportation simultaneously, he directly passed through the defense array of the Palace of Hidden Spells, which the six of the Arcane Church Beyond Grade As had failed to penetrate for a long time! EsGod's strength did not just come from his raw power. What was more horrifying was the variety of Esper abilities he had.

"Sh*t!" Austin was shocked. Although there were also tons of defense measures inside the Palace of Hidden Spells, they were not as strong as the exterior defense array. Now that EsGod had slipped in, he would not be able to stop him from destroying the Palace of Hidden Spells from the inside!

Boom!

Austin's defense spell was shattered by EsGod with just one kick enhanced by [Strength Esper Ability—Star Toss], and his tiny body was blasted away like a cannon.

The red robe Mages around Austin hastily cast spells, trying to stop EsGod. However, the next moment, their bodies started crumbling and turned to dust one after another.

Seeing the strange way their comrades had died, the Mages further away were all stunned. They backed away in a panic having seen their own body started showing signs of turning into dust too and did not dare get close to EsGod.

EsGod lowered his hand and looked satisfied. The Esper Ability he used indeed came from Ember. It was a god-tier area-of-effect Esper Ability when used on targets weaker than himself.

Then, EsGod activated a sensing Esper Ability and scanned the entire Palace of Hidden Spells in an instant.

To his shock, he did not sense the energy presence of Han Xiao. His senses were blocked by the Spacetime Amber.

This made him frown.

"Where did he go... hmm?"

Austin regained his balance far away. He would not be so easily wounded by EsGod. Remembering his mission of stalling for the time, he instantly struck back and disrupted EsGod.

Bang bang bang!

The two of them fought within the Palace of Hidden Spells, and the aftershock shattered the buildings around them.

Although Austin was no match for EsGod, he could go all out to stall him for some time at the very least. However, the wounds on his body grew rapidly, and he had no time to even control the Palace of Hidden Spells.

Without Austin's control, the Palace of Hidden Spells' responses became slow and faced even more intense focus fire. Although the surviving red robe Mages were doing their very best to control it, they had no chance of hanging on against the attacks of so many Beyond Grade As.

Kaching!

The defense array was broken one layer after another and finally reached its limits, shattering into pieces. A huge hole appeared on the defense barrier of the Palace of Hidden Spells and emitted a strong suction force. The space inside the Palace of Hidden Spells was a sealed space, and the air inside was all sucked out.

"Finally!"

Sagman rushed in hastily, worrying that EsGod might snatch the Evolution Cube before him.

At this time, before everyone could observe the situation, a familiar energy impact gushed out from within the Palace of Hidden Spells!

A tower inside the Palace of Hidden Spells suddenly exploded. A man dashed out, and a fist expanded rapidly in EsGod's sights!

Bang!

The fist crashed into EsGod's arm. The enormous impact penetrated his body and formed an air cannon behind him, which exploded on the inside of the defense array, stirring up a violent tornado.

This man was indeed Han Xiao. As his fist pressed against EsGod's arm, their energy clashed time after time.

Feeling the astonishing amount of power from his arms, EsGod's brows raised slightly.

"Compared to the last time we fought, you've become much stronger."

The last time he fought with Black Star in the Central Galaxy, he had an overwhelming upper hand. However, the energy level that Black Star was now showing made him uncontrollably shocked—Black Star's improvement was too obvious.

What he did not know was, the last time they fought, Han Xiao had only been level 240 and was just on the doorstep of Beyond Grade A. Now, Han Xiao was level 260 and much stronger. Han Xiao had yet to go through Promotion at this moment.

However, he had completed the Promotion Mission, and he could claim the reward anytime!

"That was close."

As Han Xiao clashed with EsGod, he felt relieved in his heart. EsGod's early arrival had caused the situation to worsen tremendously, but luckily, this guy had spent some time observing the situation and then was stalled by Austin with everything he had. Because of all that, he was able to stay out of battle for enough time.

At a close distance with EsGod, Han Xiao had hesitated for a moment and suppressed his impulse to use [EsGod Character Summon Card—Esper Silence].

Although he could carry out his Promotion at any time, the level difference between him and EsGod was still there. The effect of Esper Silence relied on the two sides' levels, energy, and Luck. If the duration was too short, the damage he could deal to EsGod would be limited.

The six Beyond Grade As of the Arcane Church were not scarecrows. Although EsGod and the Arcane Church were both cautious of each other, Sagman and the others would not be so shortsighted as to watch their external helper get heavily wounded. They would protect EsGod even if they were reluctant. In this situation, using this Character Summon Card would only waste it.

Knowing that, Han Xiao once again opened his secondary dimensional army box and released his mechanical army once more.

As Mechanical Force gushed out like lightning to enhance his mechanical army, Han Xiao directly opened the interface while still battling with EsGod.

Promotion!

Lv260 Promotion Mission completed!

+45 END Bonus!

1 END = 355 Health = 365 Stamina

In an instant, his cells underwent a drastic change. Immense agony exploded in his body and shocked every single one of his nerves.

Every Promotion required time to complete; they were not instant. Luckily, Han Xiao had gotten used to such pain by now. Furthermore, as a Mechanic, most of the time, he relied on his machinery to battle, so he could endure it.

EsGod's sharp senses noticed Han Xiao's change, and his pupils constricted.

This guy's energy is increasing during battle‽

The other Beyond Grade As noticed the strange situation and were equally shocked—they were not strangers to this situation. This was the ascension in life hierarchy!

"This is what this guy meant?"

Austin was stunned. He did not expect Han Xiao to mean the ascension in life hierarchy when he said that he could increase his strength.

Every Beyond Grade As had experienced this type of ascension in life hierarchy multiple times in their lives, but the process was slow and ongoing for them. Some even required decades to complete. However, ascending amid battle and compressing the evolution process of many years into such a short period was something that they had never ever seen in their lives!

"Could this be the reason Black Star broke the record of becoming a Beyond Grade A in the shortest time? Is this his special talent?"

They were bewildered and made their guesses.

As a notification popped up, Han Xiao quickly selected the options of Race Evolution and added some talents into the Black Star Race traits.

He was only able to hastily scan through the new talents and abilities during battle. He was already distracted by the pain and had no room to be distracted even more. He barely maintained his focus and continued to fight.

As the strength of Han Xiao's mechanical army increased visibly, the pressure he felt was reduced. He felt a little less worried.

Han Xiao was not hoping to turn the situation entirely around with just this Promotion, as they were fighting four against seven, including EsGod, who made the situation much worse.

He wanted to do the Promotion to increase the combined strength on their side so that they could stall for as long as possible. With such a wide strength difference, if the enemy did not show any flaws, there was absolutely no way to kill any one of the enemies head-on.

Han Xiao knew this very well and would not lose his cool due to his sudden surge of strength. Arrogance did not exist in his books.

In such a dangerous situation, there was no room to mess around.

Austin's Palace of Hidden Spells was heavily damaged, and Milizaus was not in a good state either. When Han Xiao returned to the battlefield, he had no choice but to take on the task of being the tank and guard against attacks for his teammates.

The Promotion made him visibly stronger. Together with the Aurora Character Summon Card that he had saved for many years, Han Xiao was able to take on about half of all the enemy attacks.

Although the situation was passive, they could hang on for the time being.

Compared to the main battlefield, the battlefield between the Beyond Grade As was tiny. While they were fighting, the situation on the main battlefield changed as well. Planet Lighthouse's exterior fleets returned one after another, and the situation became stable.

However, with the entrance of the Fallen Ark fleet, Tarrokov's fleet was surrounded, and they were in a passive situation again.

The garrison of Planet Lighthouse were being slowly chipped away bit by bit. With a grave expression, Tarrokov never took off his eyes from the 3D mini-map of the battlefield. He quickly gave out orders one after another, doing everything he could to slow down the rate of his troops' death.

He took a moment and glanced at the situation of the Beyond Grade A battle. That made him somewhat relieved. Luckily, Black Star and the others were holding their own against the enemy Beyond Grade As, otherwise things would have been tremendously worse.

Despite the fact that the battle between the Beyond Grade As were the enemies' focus and had the highest possibility of suffering an overwhelming loss, they somehow barely held on. Although Tarrokov was not a Beyond Grade A, he could imagine how much pressure Black Star and the others were under.

Tarrokov clenched his teeth and yelled, "Where are the reinforcements? When will they arrive at the stargate entrance?"

The deputy hastily looked at the messages, covered in sweat. He suddenly yelled, "Chief commander, the reinforcements sent by the two closest strongholds have already arrived at the stargate entrance. The border stronghold reinforcements of the Garu, Renault, and Crown Star Clusters have already gathered a total force of more than three million battleships. Also, Their Excellencies Maximiler, Heber, and Ravenlaude are almost in position!"

The reinforcements were finally arriving!

Tarrokov's eyes became bright. "Engineering team, assemble the stargate immediately! Reactivate the tunnel and let the reinforcements in!"

The dynasty's fleet changed formation immediately, using the fleet as the line of defense to assemble the portable stargate in the middle of the formation.

The commander of the Arcane Church saw this and was not happy. The resistance the dynasty's fleet had shown was much stronger than expected. Under the command of Tarrokov, an experienced commander, the defense army of Planet Lighthouse had fought extremely hard and rebounded time after time. Many times, the Arcane Church thought the dynasty's fleet was about to collapse, yet they still hung on.

The situation was the same on the Beyond Grade A battlefield; the four Dynasty Beyond Grade As were too tenacious.

He immediately contacted Sagman. "We can't let the dynasty's fleet assemble the stargate. You guys restrain the enemy Beyond Grade As and send one or two of you to cut into the dynasty's formation and destroy their stargate!"

Sagman looked at Black Star, who was very much alive even after receiving a ton of attacks. Unwilling, he clenched his teeth and made the decision.

"Mercer, you and Dylan go to destroy the dynasty's stargate. The rest of us will stay here to restrain the four of them!"

The two Mages had to deal with the Palace of Hidden Spells and could not be separated. Psyker had to sense the Evolution Cube and had to be here. Sagman had to stay there to restrain Milizaus and EsGod. Therefore, he could only send Mercer and Dylan.

Sagman had originally wanted to quickly eliminate the three of them, but Austin had suddenly appeared, and even the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter had been sealed. At this moment, he no longer had the confidence to quickly defeat the opponents.

Since the battle would not be ending soon, destroying the dynasty's stargate became a more important mission.

Mercer and Dylan nodded and immediately left the battlefield to head to the dynasty's fleet.

With two opponents leaving, Han Xiao and the others faced much less pressure. However, they were not relieved at all. Only the reinforcements would be able to turn the situation around. They could not let the enemies destroy the stargate no matter what.

"This is the key to winning..."

This thought appeared on everyone's mind.

Han Xiao's energy clashed with EsGod another time. His mechanical suit shattered, and he instantly donned his seventh backup mechanical suit. He then turned to look at Mercer and Dylan, who were getting further away. A sharp glint flashed through his eyes.

"Someone finally split off!"

Chapter 851: New Talent!

The fleets were the absolute main forces of the civilizations. The efficiency of a Beyond Grade A could not compare with millions of official military battleships. However, individual power and collective power were different concepts. The individuals with great power possessed irreplaceable special effects on the battlefield.

Compared to whole fleets, Beyond Grade As were smaller and more mobile. They could both fight fleets head-on and easily penetrate the defenses of the fleets to achieve their goal, such as eliminating the enemy's leader.

During battle, Han Xiao had already analyzed how the situation would play out. As long as the dynasty could hang on to the stage where they had to build stargates, the Arcane Church would undoubtedly attack the stargate.

At that time, the six enemy Beyond Grade As would very likely change their strategy from aggressively attacking to holding the four of them back while sending a few to attack the stargate.

This was the exact opportunity he was waiting for!

After fighting for so long, the agony of Promotion had gradually diminished, and Han Xiao had gotten used to the changes in his body.

He was given five Race Evolution options to choose two from and then one Racial Talent each from these two races from all their talents to add into the talents of the Black Star Race.

Compared to the previous Race Evolutions, the Race Evolution at the Beyond Grade A level was less random and gave more choices.

The two races Han Xiao chose this time were [Void Saint] and [Void Juggler].

Other than giving him the forty-five Endurance bonus, these also gave him bonus attributes of 266 Strength, 310 Dexterity, 454 Endurance, 537 Intelligence, 372 Mystery, 177 Charm, and 1,600 Energy!

With the Grade S Bonus, [Advanced Strengthened Life], [Eternal Body], and [Extraordinary Physique], Han Xiao's health was now more than three million!

Other than the help of his teammates, the ten-percent bonus to all attributes given by [Advanced Strengthened Life] was an important factor that allowed him to hold on under the violent attacks of the enemies.

Things were the most dangerous at the start, and he had to use the Aurora Character Summon Card two times to get through it. When his attributes stacked higher, only then was he able to hang on.

His main class turned from [Emperor Mechanic] to [Lord Mechanic], and his Machinery Affinity increased once again. With the bonus of the [Perfect Mechanical Sense] Character Summon Card, the strength of his mechanical army increased visibly.

From the various talents of the two new races, Han Xiao chose two talents that would provide the most help to the current situation. From the way he looked at it, if he could snatch the opportunity, these two abilities were more than enough to turn the tables... And that opportunity was the moment when the enemy Beyond Grade As split up.

Dylan and Mercer penetrated the dynasty fleet's formation like a drill and headed right to the stargates that were being built, while Sagman and the other three stayed to restrain Han Xiao and the others.

Milizaus could only watch the enemies split up. He tried to back up the dynasty fleet but was stopped by Sagman and the others.

Only Han Xiao was able to send a part of his mechanical army to chase after Dylan and Mercer.

The quantity of the mechanical army was too high; even Sagman and the others were not able to stop all of them. However, they were not too worried as two Beyond Grade As would definitely be able to deal with that.

Seeing Dylan and Mercer heading his way, Tarrokov immediately adjusted the fleet's formation to continuously block the path of the two of them.

Although this was able to slow the two of them down, it was not able to prevent the fact that the distance between the two of them and the stargates was slowly decreasing.

"Black Star, this won't last. Austin and my magic energy is still decreasing. We won't be able to last forever. We can't let the Arcane Church stop our reinforcements." Milizaus was anxious.

"The enemies have the numerical advantage and are forcing us to be on the defensive side," Han Xiao said with a deep voice. "The only way to reduce the pressure we're facing to the largest extent is to make them lose one Beyond Grade A."

"They have been maintaining their cooperation; we have no chance."

"No, I have a way to deal with those two who have split up from the rest. Maybe it's worth the risk." Han Xiao's tone was serious. "However, EsGod is only chasing after me alone. His ability can stop my plan."

"What's the success rate?"

"If EsGod interferes, maybe there's only a twenty-percent chance of succeeding. However, if I'm willing to give it all, there's more than seventy-percent chance to succeed!"

"What do you mean?"

"EsGod's goal is evolution, and his alliance with the Arcane Church is definitely based on that. I know what he wants, and if I give that to him..."

"Got it. Do that then. This isn't the time to hesitate. It's better than dying a slow death." Milizaus expressed his approval.

"Okay!"

Han Xiao clenched his teeth and made up his mind. He glanced at EsGod and suddenly opened his arms, using one of his new talents.

"Void Prison!"

All four Mages present noticed the large amount of Void Energy released from Han Xiao's body that quickly filled the battlefield everyone was in.

The next moment, everyone felt that this part of cosmic space became viscous, and their movements became slower.

After sensing around, the four Mages all discovered that this was not just an ability that reduced their speed. The Void Dimension had descended on this part of the cosmic space and temporarily changed the space attribute of this area, forming a strange territory that slowed everyone down.

"He changed this space with the power of the Void Dimension?" Ninjia frowned and tried to get rid of Void Prison, only to realize that his magic energy flowed slower, too.

This type of ability was not rare, but the difficulty of getting rid of it differed based on the ability's properties. The [Void Prison] talent from [Void Saint] formed a special territory using the power of the Void Dimension, which could last quite some time.

Beyond Grade A Mages could break this territory, but it was very troublesome. Even if Ninjia and Taylor worked together, they would need some time.

This ability even affected Milizaus and the others, as well as the mechanical army. There were only two people that could move freely—Han Xiao, who was very comfortable in this territory due to his Void talents, and EsGod, who had the Dimension Crack Esper Ability.

With another teleportation, EsGod appeared right behind Han Xiao with a mocking smile. His strength Esper Ability enhanced fist headed for Han Xiao's back.

"This isn't our first fight. You didn't think that this kind of ability would work on me, did you?"

"Is that so? Then what about this?" Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

EsGod's fist was closing in on his back, but Han Xiao did not even look behind. Instead, he looked at the fleet battlefield faraway and focused on Mercer.

EsGod noticed a subtle space ripple on Han Xiao's body. The next moment, with a flash, Han Xiao switched places with Mercer.

Before Mercer could react to how he suddenly appeared there, he was blown away by EsGod's punch.

After being stunned for a second, EsGod immediately realized what had happened. He quickly looked at the fleet battlefield faraway. Mercer, who had previously been there, had been switched for Han Xiao—the location of the two of them had swapped instantly.

[Void Swap], a talent from [Void Juggler], used fifteen percent of his health and energy. It would forcefully swap his location with the target and had a 320-second cooldown.

[Void Prison] and [Void Swap] were two abilities Han Xiao deliberately selected to create this situation.

"Space swapping type ability..." EsGod was a little surprised. It was not that he had never seen an ability like this. In fact, he even had one. However, his Esper Ability could only swap him with objects and not someone who had the same Grade as him. It was not even as good as his teleportation.

Sagman and the others were shocked too—when did Black Star obtain this ability? There was no information about this anywhere!

They looked far away, and their expression changed slightly. The fact that Mercer had been swapped over meant that Dylan was now alone against Han Xiao!

The two of them were deep into the dynasty fleet's formation and were very far from the others. With the restriction of the Void Prison, they could not assist Dylan immediately.

"Black Star has been hiding this ability all along." Ninjia was shocked.

"We have to quickly break this ability and send people to assist Dylan," Sagman said with a deep voice.

If Dylan was held back, the dynasty would be able to successfully assemble the stargates—in their eyes, this was Han Xiao's goal.

However, none of them had guessed that Han Xiao's true shocking goal was to reduce the Arcane Church's numbers.

In their eyes, Black Star did not have the ability to defeat Dylan in a short time. Therefore, not a single one of them thought that Han Xiao had done this to defeat Dylan. Even if they did know Han Xiao's goal, they would not think that Han Xiao would be able to do it. After all, Dylan was a Beyond Grade A who excelled at defense and control; he would not be defeated so easily.

Han Xiao's vision flashed as he swapped with Mercer and appeared not far from Dylan.

Although Dylan was surprised by Han Xiao's sudden appearance, he did not panic. In his eyes, Black Star would not be able to do much to him alone.

However, Dylan had no idea how terrifying Han Xiao was if he did not hold back.

"This is the only opportunity!" Han Xiao's eyes focused. Without the interference of other enemies, only now did he have an opportunity to go all out.

The next moment, Han Xiao aimed his hand at Dylan, who was covered in his water barrier, and activated his Ames Character Summon Card.

A powerful force field appeared and shattered the water barrier. To Dylan's shock, he realized that he was restrained by the force field.

Ames Character Summon Card—Gaze of the Dragon!

Han Xiao had used Ames' Character Summon Card once when he was at the Calamity Grade. He had obtained a new Blank Character Summon Card later and used it on Ames again. He had never met a situation where he needed to use it, until now.

This powerful control ability could not restrain someone at the same Grade as him for too long; Dylan could escape anytime.

Han Xiao was just about to continue his plan when EsGod arrived using teleportation again.

His Dimension Crack and Teleportation ignored the Void Prison. He was the only one who could break Han Xiao's plan. However, he did not come to protect Dylan; Han Xiao's Evolution Cube was the only thing that mattered.

"This guy..." Han Xiao expected this from EsGod. Having made up his mind, he activated the Evolution Cube and instantly shot out a beam of Evolution Energy at EsGod.

"Hmm‽" EsGod's expression changed as he stopped midair.

However, his response was completely different from Sagman's and the others.

Not only did EsGod not dodge it, he instead deliberately headed right toward the beam of Evolution Energy. The black Evolution Energy flowed into his body, and a black cocoon started growing on his skin.

The terms of him working with the Arcane Church were to help the Arcane Church obtain the Evolution Cube in exchange for one chance to use the Evolution Cube. Now, however, Han Xiao had directly sent him the Evolution Energy that he had been dreaming of. He immediately stopped bothering about everything else and directly took it in.

This was Han Xiao's plan.

Isn't this Evolution Energy the reason you're targeting me? I'll give it to you then. Will you continue to fight me or achieve your goal first?

EsGod was controlled by Han Xiao with this immediately and did not continue to stop Han Xiao.

While Dylan was still controlled by the Ames Character Summon Card, Han Xiao instantly arrived right in front of him using Void Hyperdrive. He threw a Luck Curse, grabbed onto Dylan's shoulder, and activated the EsGod Character Summon Card!

Esper Silence!

This time, the force field had just disappeared. Dylan was just about to push Han Xiao away using his Esper Ability, but to his absolute shock, he realized that he could not sense the existence of his Esper Ability anymore. His expression changed drastically.

"You..."

Han Xiao activated all his explosive abilities including [Gene Liberation] immediately and yelled in the quantum network, "Fire!"

The next moment, the mechanical army around them fired right at the two of them, and beams of psionic attacks landed on their bodies.

Dylan was an Esper. Without his Esper Ability, he was nothing but a target that could not resist.

Furthermore, he was not immune to True Damage!

The blue cluster of light expanded and exploded!

As the light dissipated, Dylan became covered in blood and on his last breath. Nanoparticle tentacles extended from the mechanical soldiers around, forming a few enormous chains that locked onto Dylan's arms and legs, controlling his body tightly.

All kinds of mechanical traps circled around Dylan and restricted his movements, while the barrels of all the mechanical soldiers aimed at him and were ready to fire anytime.

Han Xiao was right behind Dylan. His arms locked around Dylan's neck tightly, and his eyes were coldly staring in the direction of Sagman. It was clear that he was threatening them with Dylan's life!

Sagman and the others' expressions changed dramatically!

This was beyond all their expectations!

Dylan had been captured by Black Star so quickly!

How could Black Star possibly have such combat capability‽

"Im—Impossible!" Psyker's eyes widened with disbelief.

Sagman was shocked. Only now did he understand that Black Star's goal was not to stall Dylan but to eliminate him to reduce their numbers!

This time, the two Mages of the Arcane Church finally broke the Void Prison. Be it friend or foe, everyone looked at Han Xiao with shock.

How did he capture a Beyond Grade A in such a short time‽

Sagman and the others did not dare continue attacking Milizaus and the others; they were afraid that Han Xiao would kill Dylan instantly.

Milizaus and the other two were also shocked and did not move.

"Sh*t..." Sagman was troubled. Dylan was clearly heavily injured, and his life was in Black Star's hands. If they continued fighting, not mentioning whether they would still be able to complete the mission after losing one Beyond Grade A, Dylan would definitely die.

Dylan was a Beyond Grade A, not someone they could just give up.

Afraid of the repercussions of their actions, both sides stopped fighting, and the situation seemed to have come to a stalemate.

Sagman clenched his teeth. He secretly gave Ninjia a look. Ninjia understood his meaning and sent a psychic message to EsGod.

"EsGod, continue moving and destroy the dynasty's stargate!"

It was not that Sagman did not want to save Dylan, but Dylan had already been captured, and if they wanted to break this stalemate and have a chance at completing the mission, the only way was to let go of Dylan.

However, he did not want to express his decision of giving up his teammate, so it was best to let EsGod do the work. EsGod did not belong to the Arcane Church. If Black Star killed Dylan because of that, they would have nothing to do with it. This was the only solution.

However, EsGod ignored him completely and left the battlefield via teleportation, returning to the main ship of the Fallen Ark fleet where Fakisen was waiting.

Hearing movement, Fakisen turned around but was shocked by EsGod's appearance. Black lines were swimming on EsGod's body like snakes under his skin. It was somewhat horrifying.

"Your Excellency EsGod, are you injured‽"

"Injured? No, no... I feel amazing!"

EsGod forced out a smile. He had temporarily suppressed the Evolution Energy in his body, which was why he did not turn into a cocoon on the spot.

"Send my order, retreat immediately!"

"Ah? Are we not continuing the battle?" Fakisen wondered.

"The goal is achieved. Let the Arcane Church restrain the dynasty's fleet. We'll retreat!"

Having received the Evolution Energy, EsGod had already achieved his goal. There was no longer a need for him to continue working together with the Arcane Church.

Right now, he could not wait to find a peaceful place to complete his evolution and did not care about helping the Arcane Church at all.

EsGod knew that this was Han Xiao's plot, but he did not mind falling for it if he could achieve his goal.

His combat capability would be affected while suppressing the Evolution Energy. To him, completing the evolution was much more important than dealing with Black Star.

As for trustworthiness... when did he have that?

The Fallen Ark fleet stopped firing immediately. Now matter how much the Arcane Church commander roared, their retreat out of the battlefield could not be prevented.

Seeing this, Han Xiao's mouth twitched.

EsGod's reputation did not disappoint him.

Han Xiao had no choice but to satisfy EsGod's need. EsGod was the strongest of everyone present. As long as he was there, Han Xiao would always be at a disadvantage. EsGod's teleportation was too great a threat to the stargates; he had to find a way to make him retreat from the battlefield.

"Get through this danger first, find a way to deal with EsGod later... He participated in this attack and worked with the Arcane Church. The dynasty won't let him get away with it easily." Han Xiao did not dwell on it.

On the other side, EsGod's retreat shocked the people of the Arcane Church.

"EsGod!" Sagman was furious.

In such a short period, the upper hand that they had firmly held disappeared completely. One of them was captured, and another fled. The seven Beyond Grade As that they originally had become five in the blink of an eye!

And the root of all of this was Han Xiao!

Sagman gritted his teeth so hard to the point his teeth almost cracked.

Chapter 852: Forced Retreat

As the Fallen Ark fleet stopped firing, their millions of spaceships turned into streams of light and left Planet Lighthouse, disappearing without a trace in the blink of an eye. It was clear that they were familiar with betraying their teammates and were experts at it.

As the EsGod's fleet departed, the situation of the battle changed instantly.

Without the powerful exterior help, the number of battleships on the Arcane Church's side reduced by almost half. By this point, the Planet Lighthouse army had already recalled all its fleet. The number of battleships on both sides was even; the Arcane Church could no longer obtain the upper hand.

"Damn it..." Sagman looked at this with clenched teeth, but his heart was filled with helplessness. He was not in the mood to even blame EsGod for breaking their alliance.

He knew that although they were working together, the Arcane Church upper echelons did not have much hope in EsGod. It was indeed because these upper echelons were confident about EsGod's negative reputation that they gathered six Beyond Grade As to attack with the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. They planned to be done with the battle before EsGod arrived all along.

In fact, according to the Arcane Church's calculations, the success rate of this operation was indeed exceptionally high. It was a battle of six versus three to begin with, and if they had rendered Milizaus incapable of fighting with the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, the plan would have already been eighty percent complete. It was not impossible to capture three Beyond Grade As of the dynasty at that point.

However, what they did not expect was Austin's appearance, which turned the six against three situation into six versus four.

Although it was just one more person, it greatly reduced the strength advantage of the six Arcane Church Beyond Grade As.

More importantly, the powerful destructive weapon, the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, was countered by Black Star using a strange method and was even sealed!

If not for that, we would have already captured Black Star, obtained the Evolution Cube, and retreated with the fleet by now... This thought flashed through the minds of Sagman and the four others, making them frustrated.

Observing the disadvantageous situation, Sagman could only feel a strong headache.

If it was just EsGod retreating, the six of them would actually still have had a chance at completing the mission.

After fighting for so long, Milizaus was heavily injured, Austin's Palace of Hidden Spells was damaged, and Beyoni was not in a good state. Black Star was the only one still hanging on strong... but his mechanical army had also suffered enormous damage.

Comparatively, the six of them were in good states. If they continued to fight, they would still have a high chance at winning.

However, now that Dylan had been captured by Black Star, Sagman's plan completely went to waste.

In this battle, Black Star had once again showcased new abilities that no one knew of. Sagman had no choice but to admit that he did indeed fear Black Star for the fact that he did not know what other trump cards this guy was hiding.

Ninjia frowned and asked in the psychic communication network, "What now?"

Sagman looked at the enormous battlefield and saw that the Arcane Church's fleet was now at a stalemate with the enemies, not able to prevent the dynasty fleet from assembling their stargates.

"Inform the commander, we're retreating!" He squeezed out the words from between his tightly clenched teeth.

"You're giving up Dylan?" Psyker's eyes looked hostile.

"Sagman is right." Ninjia nodded. "Dylan has been captured, and EsGod has retreated. It's now five against four, and they have a hostage. The plan of quick attack has failed. There are only two paths ahead of us—continue fighting or retreat.

"They're not in a good state. We will no doubt win if we continue to fight. However, time is a problem. Having lost two combatants, we won't be able to settle the battle quickly. Don't forget, the Flickering World is the dynasty's territory. We have no base here, and the secret stargate is our only way of retreating. The longer we fight, the higher the risk."

"Also, EsGod wants to use us to secure his retreat," Taylor added. "We can't let him have his way."

"Dylan..."

"The risk of saving him is too high and will very likely make Black Star kill him. We have no choice but to leave him behind. That way, at least he can stay alive. The only way is to have the Arcane Church negotiate with the Crimson Dynasty afterward." Ninjia shook his head. Even if the dynasty was willing to exchange the hostage, the Arcane Church would definitely bleed for it. Furthermore, the dynasty might not even be willing to.

Psyker was in an extremely bad mood. His good friend was in Black Star's hands. God only knew what the dynasty would do to him, but there was nothing he could do.

"While the dynasty is still building the stargate, we're retreating." Sagman paused before saying with resignation, "Inform the upper echelons that this plan... has failed."

Everyone's mood was down after hearing this.

Six versus four, yet one of them was captured. This was beyond embarrassing!

They had failed an almost infallible mission, and the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was sealed. How would the Arcane Church upper echelons see them?

Almost every step that led to the tables turning had been caused by Han Xiao.

Although they did not want to admit it, they knew that they were forced to retreat by Black Star!

Psyker exchanged looks with the heavily injured Dylan faraway. His eyes were filled with apology.

Seeing Psyker's eyes, Dylan knew that he had been abandoned. He felt a sting in his heart; it did not feel good to be abandoned. Thinking of how he would be treated as a captive, his heart kept sinking.

The effect of Esper Silence had already worn off, and Dylan's Esper Ability had recovered. However, a round of attacks including True Damage had all landed on him earlier. Without the defense barrier from his Esper Ability, he had been critically injured. If not because Han Xiao wanted to capture him alive, he felt that he would have been killed directly. Fear still lingered in his heart.

At this time, Han Xiao was right behind him. Han Xiao's arms that were wrapped around his neck had explosive power. Dylan was no Pugilist. Although his body was much stronger than Calamity Grades, it was nothing worth noting at the Beyond Grade A level. With all kinds of mechanical traps, Dylan could not escape at all. Resisting was playing with his own life.

Sagman and the other four retreated to the Arcane Church's fleet and entered the spaceships. The Arcane Church fleet then started to retreat orderly.

Relying on superior mobility, the Arcane Church's fleet gradually distanced themselves from the dynasty's fleet.

Milizaus and the other two came to Black Star. Beyoni had a feeling that he had just evaded death.

"Luckily, you captured one of the enemy Beyond Grade As, or they would not have retreated this easily... This guy is the Arcane Church's 'Sea Spirit' Dylan. He's not weak. What did you do to capture him so quickly?"

Han Xiao gave Beyoni a strange look. "Trust me. You're no stranger to this ability."

Back when they fought EsGod alongside each other, Beyoni had been hit with the authentic 'Esper Silence' and still remembered that feeling vividly. Only, he did not know that Han Xiao was talking about that.

Esper Silence was the nemesis of Espers. There were probably not many Espers in the entire universe who could beat EsGod one on one. Han Xiao's EsGod Character Summon Card had two usages.

He had used one on Dylan, and he planned to use the next one on EsGod.

Before the start of the battle, he obtained two Blank Character Summon Cards from the Random Reward. However, he did not use them on EsGod. After all, EsGod had way too many Esper Abilities; the chance of getting Esper Silence again was too slim, and the other random abilities were not too useful to him. He needed to use them to obtain Reynold's Perfect Mechanical Sense.

On the other side, Milizaus watched as Sagman and the others retreated. He then asked with a deep voice, "They're fleeing—should we chase?"

"Don't count me in on the chase," Austin said calmly. "Black Star, I've returned the favor. You now owe me a big favor."

"Got it." Honestly, if not because Austin maintained his moral principles and kept his promise, someone on the dynasty's side would definitely have died.

Austin nodded with satisfaction. He then turned to look at his Forbidden Sorcerers, who had suffered heavy casualties, and felt a heartache. These were all his elites and were very tiring to train.

As for the heavily damaged Palace of Hidden Spells, Austin did not care at all. He just had to spend some time to repair it, and the material fees for that were nothing to him. To a Mage at his level, earning money was as easy as breathing.

Austin was not a dynasty ally, so Milizaus could not ask him to do anything. He then looked at Beyoni and asked, "What about you?"

"Don't come to me again for something this risky." Beyoni rejected him on the spot.

After finally surviving this lethal threat, he was not planning to throw himself into danger again. He much preferred to stay there and wait for reinforcements.

"You really are a wimp." Milizaus despised him.

"I'm the most vulnerable, and I'm afraid of dying, okay?" Beyoni snorted before turning to look at Han Xiao. "Are you chasing?"

"What do you think?" Han Xiao's mouth twitched. Neither you nor Austin are not going, so why the hell would I go? Do you think I'm tired of living?

"Since you're all not going..." Milizaus' tone suddenly changed as if he was relieved. "I feel much better."

The other three looked at him simultaneously.

"What, see this hole in my chest? I'm the most heavily injured. Are you guys going to force me to chase them and take more beatings? Show some care for an elderly dragon, will you?"

Han Xiao was speechless.

You're not going yourself, so why the hell did you even ask the others?

However, it was true that other than him, the other three were not in good states. The risk of chasing was too high; no one could blame them for not wanting to.

This time, Tarrokov contacted them, and his tone was surprised.

"Black Star, you've captured an Arcane Church Beyond Grade A?"

"As you can see." Han Xiao turned to look in the direction of the main fleet and casually grabbed Dylan's head. It was wet, slippery, and quite smooth.

"Great! You've made the Arcane Church pay the price! This way, we will have chips to negotiate with!" Tarrokov's tone was excited for a moment. He then paused and became serious again. "The Arcane Church is retreating. I'll send out troops to track them. You guys stay here on standby. Do not chase after the enemies on your own accord."

"Don't worry, we won't even if you beg us to." Han Xiao sighed.

"That's for the best." Tarrokov nodded.

The Arcane Church's surprise attack was resolved. Not only did they not lose any high-level combatants on their side, but Black Star even captured an enemy Beyond Grade A.

Tarrokov did not want them to chase. The stargates were being built near Planet Lighthouse and could not be built while moving. If the Arcane Church suddenly attacked back after they left Planet Lighthouse, the upper hand that Black Star had fought so hard to obtain might be lost.

Tarrokov was not in a hurry to chase the Arcane Church and maximize the results. As an experienced commander, he preferred to take one step at a time.

Therefore, he only sent out troops to track the Arcane Church and lock down their escape route. Black Star and the others would wait at Planet Lighthouse for the reinforcements. This was the safest strategy and would not give the enemies any chances.

The Arcane Church's fleet left the battlefield and turned into streams of light, disappearing from their sights.

Tarrokov sent out a small team to track them, leaving the rest to guard the engineering team as they assembled the stargates.

The enemies had retreated, and the battle had finally ended. Han Xiao and the others were all relieved. They flew toward their own battleships and counted their losses.

At the same time, Tarrokov contacted the dynasty's upper echelons to report the situation there.

After the news of Planet Lighthouse being attacked by the Arcane Church reached the dynasty's mother planet, it caused a storm among the military's upper echelons.

Urranrell immediately summoned all the military heads in the conference room; those not present attended the meeting via remote projections.

The first battlefield status Tarrokov sent back showed that they were facing the attacks of seven Beyond Grade As, the Arcane Church, and the Fallen Ark. The difference in strength was too large, and the situation was dire.

The military upper echelons in the room had already analyzed the situation. Most people, including Urranrell, were sure that Planet Lighthouse had no hope and would most likely be wiped out by the Arcane Church. The three dynasty Beyond Grade As would end up either dead or captured alive by the enemies.

Currently, they were discussing how the dynasty would respond to this matter.

"Her Excellency is right. The Arcane Church and the Federation of Light attacked our troops together and killed three of our Beyond Grade As and Marshal Tarrokov. We have to take revenge."

Many military upper echelons expressed their approval. Tarrokov was very reputable among the military and would likely be killed this time. Flames of revenge lit up in the hearts of many of his old comrades.

Urranrell nodded expressionlessly as well.

The moment Urranrell received this news, she had already decided to enact revenge on the Arcane Church.

The dignity of the dynasty had been challenged, and they had suffered a heavy loss. They absolutely could not let this go, or the dynasty's dignity would be shattered, and their allies would lose all trust.

Most of the dynasty's military personnel were direct; the majority of them agreed with taking revenge.

However, even in such a powerful civilization like the dynasty, there were still different opinions. A small part of the people present objected to overly violent revenge. They were not against taking revenge, but they felt that the dynasty's military power was restrained by the Flickering World, and their counterattack should not be too violent. If they really triggered a universal war, the dynasty's situation would only worsen.

Just when they were discussing intensely, a new remote projection appeared in the conference room. It was Tarrokov.

The military upper echelons present all shut up immediately and looked at him.

"Your Excellency, we have successfully guarded Planet Lighthouse. We have forced the Arcane Church and the Fallen Ark to retreat. The battle has ended. The casualties and damages are still being calculated. Milizaus, Beyoni, and Black Star are safe." Tarrokov nodded at the people present.

All the upper echelons present were shocked.

"You forced all the enemies to retreat?" Urranrell raised her brows, and a slight tint of surprise flashed passed her eyes. "Tell me the details."

Tarrokov nodded and simply explained the battle without exaggerating anything.

While listening, everyone's expression changed multiple times. They all noticed how much Black Star had contributed in this battle—secretly calling for Austin's help, stopping the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, capturing Dylan... Almost every step of the Arcane Church's plan was countered by Black Star.

It could be said that if Black Star did not do the things he did, the three Beyond Grade As of the dynasty would probably not have survived, and the enemies would have succeeded.

The dynasty's upper echelons exchanged glances.

Han Xiao could even turn the tables in such a hopeless situation. This new ally... seemed a little too strong.

Urranrell narrowed her eyes. This battle had been caused by Black Star, which she had not originally been happy about. It was clearly not worth losing two Beyond Grade As for Black Star.

However, Black Star's results left her with nothing to say. He had even captured one of the enemy Beyond Grade As and given chips to the dynasty.

This battle result was flawless and wiped away the unhappiness she had. She could not help but praise Han Xiao in her mind.

However, Urranrell would not express that on her face. She slowly nodded without changing her expression.

"Send my orders. Have all the fleets in the Flickering World chase after the enemies. Also, move the troops in the Shattered Star Ring to attack the stargate stronghold of the Arcane Church in the Shattered Star Ring when needed. Try to eliminate them before they return to the Central Galaxy."

Urranrell paused. "Also, tell Black Star to talk with me directly later."

At the same time, the Arcane Church upper echelons also received a report from their fleet...

Chapter 853: Report

A few minutes earlier, on Silver Arm, the Arcane Church's mother planet...

The Bishops once again gathered in the hall, sitting in their respective seats and resting with their eyes closed.

The Arcane Church's religion and authority were united; their faith and politics were inseparable. The Bishops controlled enormous power. The robe of every Bishop was luxurious, and their styles differed drastically in color and pattern, which represented the faction each of these Bishops oversaw.

The influence of this operation was enormous, so the Bishops were directly in charge.

Quite some time had passed since they sent the fleet over with the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device. The Arcane Church did not have a quantum communication network in the Flickering World, so messages could only be sent back through special methods. Therefore, the Bishops were still waiting for the good news from Sagman and the others.

One Bishop looked at the time and nodded. "They should have already succeeded."

"The time fits, but why haven't we received any messages?" another Bishop wondered.

"Maybe they're counting the gains."

With someone starting the topic, they discussed softly. They were patient and did not think any accident would happen to this operation.

In their perspective, the forces on their side had an overwhelming upper hand. There was really no reason to fail.

The door of the room suddenly opened.

The ceiling of the round table conference hall was very high, and the door was also ten meters tall. It was pure white and did not look like it was made of metal but of white jade. There was no groove marking the door; it was perfectly smooth like a wall when closed. At this time, this white gate started to turn into a bubble from the middle and shrunk to the sides, like boiling liquid, but did not open completely and only showed a two-meter-wide gap. A person walked into the room, and the gap closed behind him.

The Bishops stopped talking and all stood up and greeted with their heads lowered with respect.

"Your Excellency, Pope."

This was the highest leader of the Arcane Church, the Pope.

The Pope grunted a greeting and walked up to the main seat. The seat was a hovering white sphere. As he sat down, part of this sphere was pushed down like it was soft and adjusted to his body shape, forming the most suitable seat according to his body structure.

Only then did the Bishops sit down. Seeing that the Pope had only come to wait for the news and did not plan on speaking, they did not continue discussing.

After waiting for a while, the remote projection of the fleet's commander suddenly appeared in the middle of the round table—he had finally come to report.

The fleet commander did a military greeting and said with a stiff face, "Your Excellency, respected Bishops... the battle has ended. We're now retreating."

"Hmm, bring the Evolution Cube back quickly. We will send out troops to assist you," a rather impatient Bishop said directly.

The fleet commander opened his mouth and had an awkward expression like he did not know what to say.

Seeing this, everyone was puzzled. The commander whom they had sent this time was an elite. Why was he acting this way?

"Is there an issue?" someone asked.

"...Yes. We could not complete the mission. This operation has failed," the fleet commander replied with a stiff tone.

The upper echelons used so many resources and gave them so many advantages. However, even with all that, they could not complete a single mission they were given. Not only that, they even lost a Beyond Grade A. The commander felt truly ashamed, and he knew that his future would likely end there.

"Failed‽" The Bishops were stunned and furious. Having used so many resources, how could he fail with such a large advantage‽

"Go through the details. How exactly did you fail? We gave you two missions—obtain the Evolution Cube and kill Milizaus and the dynasty's Beyond Grade As. Don't tell me you did not complete any of them."

"...Yes. We could not defeat Black Star and the others, did not snatch the Evolution Cube, and did not kill or capture any of the Dynasty Beyond Grade As..."

The Bishops' faces were twitched.

Did not snatch the Evolution Cube? Fine, after all, Black Star stopped Psyker's psychic senses, so it was not impossible to fail. But you must've killed at least one Beyond Grade A, right? How could you not even achieve this basic goal? Do you think that we worked with the Federation of Light and paid a huge price to borrow the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device just to send you lot there for a tour‽

A Bishop could not help but asked, "You guys even took the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter this time, so how could you have not even killed a Beyond Grade A? Did Sagman and the others not use it?"

"No, they did..."

"Then what happened?"

"It's Black Star. Sagman and the others used the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter to heavily injure Milizaus, but Black Star used an unknown method to block the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter's attack directly!"

The Bishops frowned. The Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was not impossible to block; it was just that most of the methods would be useless. They had read about Black Star before and knew Black Star's abilities. He did not seem to possess means to block the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter's attacks. Furthermore, this was the first time that they had used the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter on him, so Black Star did not know what the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter's attacks were like before this, nor did he know that they would use this weapon. Therefore, it was very unlikely for Black Star to have made preparations for it.

"One more thing... the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was sealed by Black Star using an unknown method. Sagman and the others said they can't break it. This is what it's like..." Then, the fleet commander showed the current state of the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter to them.

The Bishops' expressions changed. The Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was their destructive weapon against Beyond Grade As, but it had been sealed by some kind of material. Even Beyond Grade A Mages could not get rid of it. What kind of strange material was that?

A Bishop endured his rage and said with a deep voice, "Useless... Bring the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter back to be studied."

This time, another person knocked the table. "Even if you couldn't use the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, there were still seven Beyond Grade As, and that's plenty to eliminate the enemies. Why retreat before the mission is complete?"

The fleet commander clenched his teeth and said, "There were more than three Beyond Grade As on the enemies' side. We did not know that Black Star partnered up with Austin, and Austin was waiting near Planet Lighthouse. He interfered in this battle, and then EsGod was bribed by Black Star and fled, leading his troops away. Dylan was captured by Black Star too. If we continued to fight, the dynasty's reinforcements would have arrived. We were forced to retreat..."

After hearing the brief description of the battle and results, the Bishops were enraged.

It was infuriating enough that the operation had failed, but not only did you not complete the mission, you did not kill a single enemy with the numbers advantage and even lost a Beyond Grade A‽

A bunch of incompetent fools!

If not because they had to give face to the Beyond Grade As, a few Bishops might have lashed out.

This time, the Pope, who had been quietly listening, spoke with an expressionless face.

"Dispatch troops to assist the Shattered Star Ring to prevent the dynasty from destroying our local stargate stations. You must bring Sagman and the others back to the Central Galaxy. Send reinforcements to prevent the dynasty from intercepting them. At the same time, strengthen Silver Arm's defenses to prepare for the dynasty's possible revenge. Inform the garrisons of the various Star Fields to enter full alert state."

Then, the Pope stood up and left. Although he did not show any emotion, the Bishops knew the Pope's personality and were certain that he was furious to the extreme.

...

At the same time, the Federation of Light received the message as well.

"The Arcane Church failed?"

President Bader was shocked. He browsed through the information and narrowed his eyes.

"How unexpected..." the Chief Elder said with a weird tone. "The Arcane Church was defeated by Planet Lighthouse even in this situation. Aren't they too useless?"

Bader did not immediately reply. His fingers swiped a few times on the virtual screen, bringing up Black Star's information. "Instead of saying that the Arcane Church was forced to retreat by Planet Lighthouse, the Arcane Church basically lost to Black Star. Tarrokov is famous as a Crimson Dynasty commander who excels at defenses. It's not weird for him to last a period of time with a fleet less than half of the size of the enemy. The real breakthrough is at the Beyond Grade A battlefield. Black Star turned the situation around on the Beyond Grade A battlefield, which was what caused the entire situation to change."

"The Arcane Church lost a Beyond Grade A, tsk tsk..." The Chief Elder grinned. "They really suffered a huge loss this time."

Bader smiled faintly too. Although they had worked together with the Arcane Church, he was more than happy to see both sides suffering losses. No matter how much the Crimson Dynasty and the Arcane Church fought, the Federation of Light would definitely gain from it.

After all, they did not send out any troops and only lent their Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device once. Even if the dynasty wanted revenge, they would mainly focus on the Arcane Church and would not do too much to the Federation of Light.

"Your Excellency, what are you planning to do next?"

Bader pondered for a moment before saying, "The Crimson Dynasty will not easily let go of this Arcane Church team... Dispatch our troops and allies in the Shattered Star Ring to interfere."

"Are you planning to help the Arcane Church to escape?"

"No, the partnership between us and the Arcane Church is only limited to lending them the transportation device. That was just a deal, and now the deal has ended, so there's no need to continue the partnership... Help the dynasty intercept the Arcane Church's fleet!"

The Chief Elder shook his head with resignation.

How horrible, selling their partner right afterward... However, they were never allies to begin with; they only targeted the dynasty together while the dynasty was exploring the Flickering World. The three universal civilizations were all competitors to each other. They would work together if there was something to profit from and fight each other the rest of the time. They were all used to it.

The Chief Elder suddenly thought of something and chuckled. "By the way, the biggest winner this time seems to be EsGod."

"I don't really think so. It's just one chance to use the Evolution Cube." Bader looked at Han Xiao's data again. "The Arcane Church have the moral low ground, so the dynasty will definitely make announcements regarding this matter. This means that Black Star's achievements in this battle will be spread across the entire universe. A Beyond Grade A who has killed or captured another Beyond Grade A is very different from one who has not.

"Furthermore, he was the main target of the Arcane Church this time, but he forced them to retreat. He basically made the Arcane Church his steppingstone. His influence will see explosive growth. Not only that, having achieved so much in this battle, his position in the dynasty will increase tremendously.

"Black Star is the biggest winner this time."

...

The battle had just ended. When the three civilizations' upper echelons were receiving the news, Han Xiao flew into a Black Star Army battleship and told Phillip to count the losses as well as gather the officers.

The Black Star Army did not leave many ships on Planet Lighthouse. During the battle, the dynasty's fleet was the main force, so the battleship damage incurred was not much. However, the Calamity Grade Black Star Guards all took part, and he wanted to know if there were any casualties.

Aurora waiting in the cabin. The moment she saw Han Xiao, she immediately dashed to him.

Aurora hugged him on her tiptoes around his waist.

"It's great you're okay. I was so worried!" Aurora buried her head in Han Xiao's arms.

Smelling the refreshing aroma from Aurora, Han Xiao's tensed nerves finally relaxed.

Facing seven Beyond Grade As was extremely dangerous. Not only was he getting beaten up, but he had also been enduring the pain from his Promotion. Now that he was relaxed, only then did he feel tired and pain all over his body. The pain from the Promotion had yet to fully disappear.

Han Xiao looked down at Aurora. Sensing the softness in his arms, he felt much better. He patted Aurora's head and asked, "Where's your sister? Is she okay?"

"Hmm, I sent her life force a few times; she's still alive."

At this time, the hatch opened again. Hila and the other Black Star Guards all walked in. Everyone was wounded, but no one had died. This was all thanks to the potions that Aurora had made. Every Black Star Guard had some of Aurora's potion with them. They were extremely effective and more than enough to guarantee the lives of these Calamity Grades.

Aurora turned around and looked through the gap between Han Xiao's arms. Having realized that Hila was wounded and bleeding, she quickly left Han Xiao's embrace and ran over.

"Sis, you're wounded. Let me heal you."

Hila waved her hands and rejected her. "The battle has ended. Such a small wound will recover in no time. Don't waste your life force."

Then, she turned around and looked at the Black Star Guards behind her. "You guys aren't allowed to do that either... Hmm, except Feidin."

Hadavy and the others were originally hoping for Aurora to heal them, but hearing what Hila said, they had no choice but to let go of that thought.

"Why except me?" Feidin pointed at his head with resignation. "Don't misunderstand, Chen Xing told me to ask."

"Black Star said that you're lucky and told us to benefit from your luck from time to time." Hila told the truth.

Then, Hila turned and looked at Han Xiao. She sized him up and saw that he had not lost an arm or a leg; she was relieved. Her lips moved slightly like she wanted to say something, but in the end, she only nodded.

This time, Hadavy suddenly said, "I just heard you captured a Beyond Grade A. Where is he?"

With that brought up, everyone was curious. This was the first time their Army Commander had defeated a Beyond Grade A head-on, so they all wanted to see the Beyond Grade A captive.

Han Xiao smiled and told his mechanical army to bring Dylan in. Dylan was restrained by machinery all over his body like a metal mummy, only showing his face.

Such restraints could not limit the movements of a Beyond Grade A, but Dylan knew that he had been abandoned and that it was meaningless to resist deep behind enemy lines. He had no choice but to accept the fact that he was now a captive.

The Black Star Guards all approached and sized him up, talking about him right under his nose.

"Defeated in just one blow? You're so weak."

"What are you talking about? The Army Commander is just too strong!" Hadavy said with anger.

"Right, right, right!"

Dylan was furious. As a powerful Beyond Grade A, he was now being observed like a zoo animal. He almost wanted to use his Esper Ability to teach these Calamity Grades a lesson.

Even in this state, he could not endure being shamed by these people!

Having noticed energy flowing, Han Xiao said with a hostile tone, "You want to resist?"

"Tell your subordinates to piss off!" Dylan roared. "Don't think that you can humiliate me just because you captured me. Even in this state, I can still kill them easily."

"Oh, you reminded me. Tying you up like this doesn't seem safe enough."

Han Xiao smiled faintly. He took out the Spacetime Amber and made Dylan hover in midair.

The Black Star Guards knew the effect of this thing. They all backed away, sneering.

Seeing their expressions, Dylan suddenly had a bad feeling and asked, "What are you doing?"

"Don't worry, you're already a captive. Not only will I not hurt you, but I will also guarantee your safety." Han Xiao chuckled. "Trust me, I will absolutely not let you get hurt."

Han Xiao activated the Spacetime Amber. After some time, it finally surrounded Dylan entirely, and Han Xiao immediately cut off the energy supply. Dylan was a captive, so he had more than enough time to create plenty of amber.

The next moment, the spacetime solidified and formed an amber ball, freezing Dylan within. His puzzled expression was fixed on his face.

"This way, there's no need to waste manpower watching him." Han Xiao chuckled.

Hadavy knocked on the amber ball and giggled. "Can you kill me easily now?"

Dylan was frozen but could still sense the outside world. Realizing that he could not move his body at all, he was stupefied.

So, this is the ability that sealed the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. This isn't Black Star's ability!

Other than the Evolution Cube, Black Star has another Universal Treasure‽

After teasing the immobile Dylan for a while, the Black Star Guards left one after another. After a huge battle, they were all tired and went to rest.

Having watched everyone leave, Han Xiao opened the interface.

He finally had some time to check the losses and gains of this battle.

Chapter 854: Lord Mechanic

"The Arcane Church forced quite a number of trump cards out of me this time..."

The most dangerous stage had passed, but Han Xiao knew that the battle had yet to end. The Arcane Church had appeared out of nowhere using the Federation of Light's Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device, but they would have to cross the universe in their spaceships when returning. With the dynasty's way of doing things, there was no way they would let the six Beyond Grade As of the Arcane Church leave just like that...

Oh, it's five Beyond Grade As now.

Therefore, when Ty-Ty and the others arrive, it will be their turn to chase after Sagman and the others. There are billions of dynasty troops in the Flickering World, so this group of Arcane Church people will not be able to easily retreat.

Even if they were able to flee the Flickering World, the Shattered Star Ring was still waiting for them. The Shattered Star Ring was the base of the Klent Kingdom, the Bloodshed Land, and the Black Star Army. Having received such a huge gift, Han Xiao had to return a gift; he was not a petty person. He had already decided to use all of the Black Star Army's forces and his complex network in the Shattered Star Ring to do so.

While planning in his mind, Han Xiao looked at the interface at the same time to calculate the losses the Arcane Church had given him.

Rushing levels during the EXP penalty period cost him a ton of EXP. Even for Han Xiao, he felt a heartache thinking about this number. He did not like wasting. If the extra EXP had been used to level up blueprints, he would have gotten so many Potential Points.

In terms of Character Summon Cards, the usages of Reynold, Aurora, and Ames' Character Summon Cards had all been depleted. The EsGod and Heber Character Summon Cards each had one use left. They were both powerful trump cards. That was especially so for EsGod's [Esper Silence] Character Summon Card. It would be extremely powerful against EsGod. With one remaining use, this meant that he had fewer ways to fight EsGod.

Furthermore, EsGod was the winner of this attack. He had no choice but to satisfy EsGod's needs due to the Arcane Church's attack to force EsGod off the battlefield. With the Evolution Energy, EsGod would be more difficult to deal with and might even touch the doorstep of the 'higher level' that he sought. All things considered, his plan to deal with EsGod had been disrupted, and he was quite unhappy.

"Nonetheless, the mission rewarded three unknown Character Summon Cards. Together with the two Blank Character Summon Cards from the Random Reward and an Ability Upgrade Card, at least it somewhat made up for the losses." Han Xiao shook his head.

The damage incurred to his machinery was also quite large. A lot of mechanical soldiers had been destroyed. The mechanical lives were still alright, as Han Xiao purposely did not let them take part in the direct battle against the Beyond Grade As, so they did not suffer many casualties.

Compared to other machinery, the mechanical lives with the capability to grow had higher potential. It would be a pity for them to be destroyed in such a one-sided battle. The other machines were more than enough as pawns.

In some respects, Han Xiao was the cause of this battle. If any Beyond Grade As had died because of it, the dynasty would definitely not have been happy about it. However, luckily, with the help of Austin, they had just been wounded, which made things easier for Han Xiao.

This way, he owed Austin a huge favor, which was not a completely bad thing. Sometimes, owing someone a favor would lead to a better relationship.

Austin was originally neutral, but after he messed with the Arcane Church after this battle, it would be very difficult for him to continue to exclude himself from everything. Although he would not go so far as to immediately join the dynasty, all the forces in the universe would mark him as being on the side of the dynasty. He would no longer be able to keep a low profile like before.

Han Xiao then thought of Psyker, and his expression became weird.

"If that's the case... Austin is now close to the dynasty; Ames is my ally, so she's considered an indirect ally of the dynasty; Heber also belongs to the dynasty. Including me, four of the five Beyond Grade As in the Shattered Star Ring are related to the dynasty. Psyker will probably have to keep quiet in the Shattered Star Ring in the future."

With this thought, Han Xiao opened the mission list and claimed the [Completed] missions. He was only confident about claiming the reward after touching Feidin earlier.

[Cause and Effect] completed!

According to your performance, you have received 45,000,000,000 EXP, 3 Random Reward, [Character Summon Card—'Child of Light' Sagman], [Character Summon Card—'Star Pupil' Psyker], and [Character Summon Card—EsGod].

[Character Summon Card—'Child of Light' Sagman]: [Light Particle Stream—Infiltration]—Releases a powerful light energy particle beam that has high Penetrating, Explosive, and Burning Damage. The light energy will continue to deal damage and give the target [Energy Disruption] and [Energy Suppression] statuses. When the enemy uses energy attacks, the power would decrease, the cost will increase, and their accuracy will decrease. Uses: 0/5.

[Character Summon Card—'Star Pupil' Psyker]: [Psychic Energy—Heart Wall]—In 4.7 seconds, the actual damage taken from psychic attacks will be reduced by 85% after Psychological Resistance reductions. It grants immunity to all kinds of psychic control abilities. If the attacker is a Psychic, the INT and MYS of both sides will be calculated. If one of your attributes is higher than the attacker, 45% of theoretical damage will be reflected. If both of your attributes are higher than the attacker, 90% of theoretical damage will be reflected. If both of your attributes are lower than the attacker, damage will not be reflected. Uses: 0/3.

[Character Summon Card—EsGod]: [Esper Ability—Copy]—Through close contact, copy the target's Esper Gene and receive a one-time Character Summon Card of the target. Only effective on Espers. Uses: 0/3.

Receiving the maximum EXP reward was within Han Xiao's expectations. The effects of all three Character Summon Cards were decent, but he was not lucky enough to get EsGod's [Esper Silence] again. However, [Esper Ability—Copy] was not bad; it was basically three Blank Character Summon Cards for Espers. EsGod had a ton of random abilities, so being able to obtain this was already thanks to Feidin's blessing.

You have received 1 Legendary Point.

Universe Legendary Point: Enemy of the Arcane Church—Facing a despairing situation, you fought back and turned the situation around, forcing the Arcane Church to retreat and even capturing an enemy Beyond Grade A. Your name will spread through the entire universe with this battle and become a legend!

Enemy of the Arcane Church, the highest-grade Legendary Point, a Universe Legendary Point... Looks like this will become a new nickname.

Every Beyond Grade A had many nicknames that represented the legendary things that they had done. Han Xiao now had 'Indestructible Body', 'Indestructible Black Star', 'the Black Star Army Commander', and other nicknames. When word about this battle spread, he would probably also gain the nickname 'Enemy of the Arcane Church'.

The Arcane Church wanted to kill him, and he sealed their Universal Treasure as well as captured their Beyond Grade A. At this moment, the beef between the two sides was irresolvable.

Capturing a Beyond Grade A alive had extraordinary meanings. Back then, this was the reason Heber wanted to duel with him, but he sadly failed to do so, and now Han Xiao achieved this before Heber. This way, his reputation in the universe would become completely different, and his position would be much higher... He felt that Ty-Ty would be quite jealous.

Speaking of which, Heber was right on his way back to back him up. Having thought of the possible expression Heber might have, Han Xiao could not help but chuckle a bit.

The interface also showed that he could now create the Dungeon [Flickering World—Planet Lighthouse Battle]. A total of eleven Beyond Grade As had taken part in this conflict, which rarely happened other than in full blown wars. This would shock the entire universe. Although it happened in the Flickering World and had yet to be publicized, it was clear that news of this would stir up a violent storm.

With so much influence, being able to create the Dungeon was no surprise. Sadly, given the standard of this battle, the effect of this Dungeon would only be to widen the players' horizon and make them suffer.

Han Xiao opened the attributes interface and carefully read through his attributes after the level 260 Promotion.

Level: 260

Main Class: Mechanic

Race: Black Star Race

Attributes: 3,247 STR, 3,980 DEX, 5,889 END, 8,489 INT, 2,950 MYS, 1,163 CHA, 1 LUK

Free Attribute Points: 0

Potential Point: 33

Health: 3,854,550

Stamina: 3,521,025

Energy: 82,120 [Lv.17]

Lv.17 Energy bonus stats: +1,206 STR, +1,488 DEX, +1,890 END, +2,345 INT, +1,123 MYS, +311,520 Stamina Limit, +1,632% Machinery Affinity

Energy Rank: 49,975

Grade: S (Beyond A)

Grade S Bonuses: +50 END, +25 All Resistances. +25% Highest Attribute, +15% Other Attributes, +750 Free Attribute Points, +50 Potential Points

Remark: This seems to be a Beyond Grade A Mechanic who persists on the path of a tank.

"Almost 50,000 Energy Rank..." Han Xiao touched his chin. He could still remember that when he first reached Beyond Grade A, his Energy Rank had been about 43,000. Afterward, he had completed [Heber Stellar Furnace Cultivation] and [Mechanical Life Tinder], which gave him quite a lot of Energy Rank.

Heber's cultivation technique had given him more than 16,000 maximum energy. His maximum energy was only a little more than 50,000 when he first reached Beyond Grade A, but it was now more than 80,000. His Energy Level had increased from 15 to 17, which had given him two new layers of bonus attributes.

He did not forget about [Radiation Absorption], which gave him some attributes here and there.

"The next Race Evolution Promotion is at level 300, and the level limit of Lord Mechanic is also level 40, so the Class Advancement is at level 300 too. Therefore, there's only the level 280 Promotion in between."

Han Xiao pondered.

[Emperor Mechanic]'s limit was level 35, and the new [Lord Mechanic] was five more than that.

At the [Lord Mechanic] stage, the pros of Apostle and Emperor Mechanic were enhanced.

Same as the two previous Class Advancements, the abilities and talents of Virtual Technology were enhanced too, this time by sixty percent

There were four new abilities.

Talent [Mechanic Lord] gave +300% Machinery Affinity, +200% Virtual Intrusion and virtual defense efficiency, and some changes to the properties of Mechanical Force, which granted the so-called 'Lord Power'. The introduction was brief and blurry, only saying that this was the prerequisite of some new Lord Mechanic abilities.

Ability [Lord Machinery Affinity] gave +190% Machinery Affinity at max level.

Ability [Apostle Life Creation] was similar to [Emperor's Gift], also giving special enhancement to an individual machine. However, the effect was quite different. [Emperor's Gift] could only be used three times on the same target and did not limit the number of targets. While [Apostle Life Creation]'s effect was to use the so-called 'Power of the Lord's Dominance' Mechanical Force to turn a mechanical soldier into an 'Apostle Weapon'.

The enhancement was much stronger. It could basically turn a normal unit into a mini boss unit and a unit with better fundamentals into a big boss unit.

With such powerful enhancement effects, [Apostle Life Creation] restricted the number of Apostle Weapons. At max level, he could have twelve Apostle Weapons at the same time. The Power of Lord's Dominance in their body could be retrieved anytime and given to another machine. This ability also enjoyed enhancement from the various other enhancement abilities. Every level increased the maximum Apostle Weapon number by one.

The last ability, [Lord's Descent], was an ability to fight with a remote army. Through the special Mechanical Force of a Lord Mechanic, he could project his consciousness, mind, and power onto a mechanical soldier and turn this mechanical soldier into some sort of avatar. It would share a large portion of the main body's attributes, abilities, and talents and have Beyond Grade A strength.

This meant that, not only could Han Xiao provide Mechanical Force bonuses to the remote troops using Quantum Infinite Distance Transmission Channel when he was at home, he could also use this on one of them and fight personally. The restriction was that this could only be used on one target at a time.

The ability introduction also said that if [Lord's Descent] was used frequently on the same target, there was a chance to form a Soul Connection.

"These four abilities are all quite good, especially [Lord's Descent]...

"After this battle today, there should be very few who come to make trouble for me in the future. My combat method shall start to be focused on remote combat. This ability will be very useful to me."

After concluding the losses and gains, Han Xiao received a call from Tarrokov saying that Urranrell wanted to speak with him personally.

Even for Beyond Grade As, Urranrell was not someone they could see whenever they wanted to. It was clear that his achievements in the battle had surprised Urranrell, which was why she wanted to talk to him.

Furthermore, there were still some problems that needed to be discussed and solved regarding this matter, as well as the mission to chase after Sagman and the others.

"Got it, I'll wait for her online."

Han Xiao took out the communicator and made a lot of speculations while quietly waiting for the call to connect.

After achieving so much this time, if he requested new Ultimate Knowledges, Urranrell would not reject him, would she?

Chapter 855: Time to Counterattack!

Very soon, a cone-shaped projection beam shot out from the communicator and quickly scanned through the room. The environment of the room quickly changed into the conference room where Urranrell and the group of upper echelons were in as if Han Xiao was there.

Han Xiao looked around and realized that everyone was staring at him with different emotions such as curiosity, respect, and surprise. One thing those military upper echelons shared in common was they all looked very interested in him.

Urranrell looked at Han Xiao and said, "Black Star, you've made a huge achievement in this incident. The dynasty will reward you generously."

"I was just saving myself." Han Xiao could not help but be humble on such an occasion, and it sure felt good.

"You deserve the credit nonetheless." Urranrell then returned to the topic. "Tarrokov has already described this battle earlier, but I want to hear your version. Some questions need you to answer."

Han Xiao knew that explaining the battle from the perspective of a Beyond Grade A would bring new information to the table, so he described it from the start to the end.

Urranrell nodded and asked, "I want to know, was what you used to stop and seal the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter a new Universal Treasure?"

"Hmm, it's what I happened to discover while exploring the Flickering World. It's a Space Wonder."

"I see." Urranrell did not continue to ask about the name and uses of the Spacetime Amber. If Black Star wanted to tell her, he would, and if he was not willing to, she was not going to force someone who had just made such a huge contribution. Beyond Grade As had the right to keep their abilities a secret; all she had to know was that Black Star was on her side.

"I've sealed the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, and it will be very difficult for the Arcane Church to break that seal. Only, they don't know that yet... The Ten Thousand Deity Scepter is a Universal Treasure that's very important to them; they might look to negotiate with the dynasty privately."

Urranrell's eyes moved slightly, and she asked, "Are you sure it'll be very difficult for them to break the seal?"

"There are no absolutes. The Arcane Church might come up with something. However, in all likelihood, their odds of success are extremely low. It's very likely that I'm the only one that can help them break the seal of the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter."

"Understood. If what you said is true, we might have underestimated your contributions. Without the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, the deterrence they have on Beyond Grade As will be much lower. I've already decided to counterattack the Arcane Church, so what you've done has lowered the chances of the Beyond Grade As of the dynasty suffering from accidental casualties. Good." Urranrell paused. "However, what happened at Planet Lighthouse has made things tense between them and us. The Arcane Church will probably not negotiate with us privately but act as if they have already broken the seal."

"Hmm, you're right." Han Xiao thought about it. Indeed, since the dynasty was going to counterattack, the Arcane Church would definitely not easily take a step back. It was very likely for them to act confident on the surface while being extremely troubled by not being able to break the seal in private.

"Also, about EsGod. It's unexpected for the Arcane Church to actually work with the notorious Fallen Ark. The dynasty will make an announcement to the entire universe condemning the Arcane Church's actions..." Urranrell then changed the topic. "Don't worry, the dynasty has no problems with how you used the Evolution Cube on EsGod this time."

Han Xiao was stunned for a moment then understood—his plan against EsGod had worked, but technically, he had still made a deal with EsGod. However, the dynasty was very sensible about this. They understood that he had no choice in that situation. Therefore, Urranrell expressed that they would not hold him responsible, which represented what the dynasty's stand was on this matter. They were not going to allow anyone to use this matter to besmirch Black Star's name.

From this sentence, Han Xiao noticed that Urranrell was trying to woo him into becoming a member of the Ruler's faction. Complimenting and rewarding him were not the only reasons he was called to this meeting. It was more to express her intention on wooing him. Given how enormous the dynasty was, internal conflicts between the many factions were inevitable. Han Xiao had just earned a huge achievement, so there would not be any problems in the near future. However, after some time passed, some factions might bring this matter back up as leverage.

If one of the dynasty's Grade As was killed in action this time or I did not capture Dylan, someone might have used this to try and force me to give up the Evolution Cube... Han Xiao was secretly shocked. The battle had just ended for him, and he did not think too much about it. Since Urranrell had given him a subtle hint, he understood her kind intentions.

"Thank you, Your Excellency." Han Xiao bowed.

Urranrell then asked, "What do you plan to do with Dylan?"

"I've decided to hand him over to the dynasty," Han Xiao said slowly. "Now that the Arcane Church have failed once, they won't easily try to obtain the Evolution Cube again. However, If I keep Dylan as my captive, the Arcane Church, having to consider the opinions of their allies, will not sit by idly. They will definitely carry out rescuing measures. I don't want this incident to happen again, and if it does, I might not be as lucky as I was today. Therefore, I might as well give him to the dynasty to be used as leverage to negotiate with the Arcane Church."

Although he had forced the Arcane Church to retreat this time, it would be much more than just a slap on their faces if he imprisoned Dylan personally. They were a universal civilization no matter what, and making them completely furious was not a wise decision. Dylan was a hot potato; there were far more cons than pros if he kept him himself. Instead, if he gave Dylan to the dynasty in exchange for more merits and a ton of Faction Contribution Points, he could obtain Ultimate Knowledges.

"You've made the right choice; that's what I had in mind. I wanted to convince you to do it, but since you're already willing to, that's even better."

A very rare slight smile appeared on Urranrell's cold face, knowing that Han Xiao had accepted her kind intentions. "You've done well this time. Other than the support and generous reward the dynasty will give to you and your Black Star Army, if you have any other needs, do tell."

The dynasty would provide even more resources to the Black Star Army after this, which was a given. Therefore, Han Xiao requested what he wanted the most.

"I hope to obtain more Ultimate Knowledges."

"Hmm, no problem." Urranrell approved. "I will tell the officer of the dynasty's logistics department to contact you directly. Just request it from him."

There was no way the Ruler would be personally in charge of trivial matters such as exchanging knowledge.

Han Xiao nodded with a smile and pondered in his mind. His contributions this time would definitely give him more than one Ultimate Knowledges, and every single knowledge at this level would bring a huge boost to the combat capabilities of a Mechanic.

However, it was impossible to obtain all the Ultimate Knowledges at once. He did indeed make a huge contribution, but there were rules to follow when giving out rewards. Ultimate Knowledges were one of the important methods to attract Beyond Grade As to begin with. Even the Beyond Grade As directly under the dynasty had to slowly earn them with merits and contributions.

"The impact of this incident will affect the situation of the entire universe." Urranrell was back to her formal and serious tone. "The dynasty must retaliate against the Arcane Church's provocation. However, the Federation of Light has always liked to put bets on both sides, so the effort we put in exploring the Flickering World will definitely be restrained. While the three civilizations try to mess with each other, those Super Star Cluster civilizations will definitely make use of this opportunity to further infiltrate the Federation of Light. The dynasty will be forced to deal with multiple problems at once, which is exactly what the Arcane Church and the Federation of Light want to see."

Han Xiao knew that Urranrell had a motive for saying something like this, so he followed it up and asked, "So, what do you think we should do?"

"We need to intimidate the Super Star Cluster Civilizations, so we will call back some of the Beyond Grade As and troops stationed in the Flickering World. Of course, their forces will still be exploring in the Flickering World."

Han Xiao did not speak; he knew what Urranrell meant. There was no way the dynasty would let so many Beyond Grade As stay in the Flickering World for the long term, and this thought would have occurred long ago. However, he did not mind. Heber and his territory were both in the Shattered Star Ring, which was nearby, so he was not likely to be called back.

Urranrell changed the topic and asked, "Black Star, what do you think of the situation the dynasty is currently in?"

"As you know, the conflicts are mainly around the Flickering World, and not just anyone can take part in it. The aftershock of the Crimson Tide is slowly cooling down, so those Star Cluster and Star System civilizations will stay low for some time." Han Xiao shrugged.

"Maybe." Urranrell nodded slowly then suddenly asked, "Do you have any suggestions about the dynasty's counterattack plan?"

Han Xiao knew that although the Ruler was discussing the dynasty's plan with him, she might not take his suggestions. However, this was a gesture that represented the fact that his position within the dynasty had risen.

After some thinking, Han Xiao coughed and said, "Counterattacking is a must, but the focus can be readjusted. The Arcane Church is also a Universal Civilization, so retaliating against them is just a necessary reaction. I'm sure that you know this will not achieve great results, Your Excellency."

"Go on."

"In my opinion, we should focus on taking action against EsGod. EsGod took part in the Planet Lighthouse battle as well, and he is much easier to deal with compared to the Arcane Church. It just so happens that the desolate universe belt in the middle of the Central Galaxy is known to be the default battlefield to settle friction between the three civilizations, so dealing with EsGod will not require us to make any detours. If the Fallen Ark is eliminated, the dynasty will successfully showcase its thunderous retaliation and achieve even greater intimidation levels."

This incident was a great opportunity to convince the dynasty to deal with EsGod. If he could obtain help from the dynasty, the chances of eliminating EsGod would be much higher.

Urranrell, however, did not express if she accepted or rejected the suggestion. "I will have someone analyze your suggestion. The urgent matter at hand is to chase after the Arcane Church and EsGod's fleets. When the reinforcements arrive, you guys shall follow Tarrokov's orders and act with the dynasty's fleet... We're not going to let them escape this easily!"

Urranrell then nodded at Han Xiao and said, "Go rest. You'll need to continue fighting during the pursuit."

"Okay."

As the call ended, the projection in the room disappeared.

Han Xiao breathed a sigh of relief and was delighted. The contributions he had made during this battle brought him some sense of presence among the upper echelons of the dynasty. His position in those people's mind turned from a new ally to a dependable Beyond Grade A of the dynasty. He was even wooed by the Ruler, which also increased his position and influence.

After putting away the communicator, Han Xiao noticed a new notification on the interface.

You have received 1 Political Asset.

Political Asset (1): the Crimson Dynasty

You have made huge contributions to the Crimson Dynasty and received a certain amount of political influence. You can make suggestions to the Crimson Dynasty directly, according to the rationality of the suggestion, there's a slight chance the Crimson Dynasty will listen to it.

Your position in the Crimson Dynasty is higher. When interacting with certain organizations or characters, +30% Favorability gained.

You have valuable experience. +30% Experience gained from all sources.

Remarks: The above effects will only take place when the Faction Relationship with the Crimson Dynasty is maintained at [Reverence].

"Yo, I thought there would only be Legendary Point but no Political Asset." Han Xiao was surprised but then understood why—this was probably a bonus reward given because of the fact that Urranrell valued him.

However, maintaining the effect of this Political Asset was not easy, as he had to spend Faction Contribution Points in exchange for Ultimate Knowledges. He had to maintain the Contribution Points he had above 6,000, which was the cost of one Ultimate Knowledge.

Han Xiao looked at the following notification, which raised his brows.

You have received 10,000 Crimson Dynasty Contribution Points.

You have received a bonus 5,000 Crimson Dynasty Contribution Points.

"I only received the Contribution Points after I finished talking to Urranrell..." Han Xiao rubbed his chin. He had the NPC interface, so he could reward the Black Star Army members Contribution Points any way he wanted to. As a Faction leader, the way this worked for her was the same, just that Urranrell rewarded Contribution Points unconsciously.

Ten thousand Contribution Points was the reward for this battle, and the bonus five thousand Contribution Points was probably from him handing Dylan in. Including the more than three thousand Contribution Points he had saved up previously, he now had more than eighteen thousand Contribution Points.

"Three Ultimate Knowledges, just nice." Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Unlike Cutting-Edge Knowledges, the dynasty would not give Ultimate Knowledges for free. The kind intentions Urranrell had for him seemed to have been displayed in the way of receiving more Contribution Points.

"This way, I can buy two knowledges and keep the remaining six thousand to maintain the effect of the Political Asset. I'm not in a hurry to spend them all anyway."

Han Xiao closed the interface with satisfaction.

At this time, a blue light illuminated from outside the porthole, shining on his young and edgy face.

He turned to look outside the porthole and saw that not far from Planet Lighthouse, the stargate was finally assembled and activated. A dark blue space energy vortex formed inside the stargate and quickly started spinning.

"They're finally here."

As time passed, reinforcement fleets flew out from the stargate one after another from the various Beyond Grade A organizations.

These were mostly troops stationed around the strongholds at the edge of the three Star Clusters. If the Arcane Church wanted to attack Planet Lighthouse now, them being completely obliterated would be the only outcome.

"The battle has already ended‽"

Inside Tarrokov's main ship, Heber, who had left his main fleet behind and returned as soon as possible; Ravenlaude, who had rushed there through teleportation; and the remote projection of Maximiler had gathered and sat across from Han Xiao and the others.

Upon knowing the fact that Planet Lighthouse's troops had forced the enemies away without any reinforcements, Heber and the other two were all shocked.

They actually managed to defend Planet Lighthouse?

Not only did Black Star turn the tables on the Beyond Grade A battlefield, he even captured one of the enemies alive.

Heber and Ravenlaude felt conflicted. They had initially thought that they were saviors, but to their surprise, before they even arrived, Han Xiao had already forced the enemies to retreat. It was almost as if they were not even needed at all...

However, this thought did not linger too long in their minds. Although they came late, they knew that the Arcane Church had only retreated because of the pressure from their arrival. Thinking this way made them feel much better—at least they had contributed in some way.

Ravenlaude was getting a little fidgety and said, "Black Star, I heard you got a new Universal Treasure in the Flickering World and used it to stop the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter."

"That's right." Han Xiao chuckled.

Hearing Han Xiao confirming the matter, Ravenlaude was filled with regret. He was exploring the same Star Cluster as Black Star, which meant that this unknown Universal Treasure had been found in the Garu Star Cluster. If there was no Black Star, maybe this Universal Treasure would have become his.

Heber turned to Austin, frowned, and said, "Why are you here? Have you joined the dynasty too?"

"I came to help Black Star." Austin smiled faintly.

Heber's eyes circled around Han Xiao and Austin; he was not feeling great. When did the two of them form such a good relationship?

Both Ames and Austin had become Black Star's friends; now Heber felt like he was alone in the Shattered Star Ring.

However, when he remembered what situation Psyker was in, he felt much better.

Nonetheless, Heber could not be glad. The achievement of capturing a Beyond Grade A alive was something he had been chasing after for many years, but it had now been obtained by Black Star, who had only stepped into the Beyond Grade A level around a year earlier.

This time, Tarrokov spoke. "I have already dispatched the troops in various locations to lock down the escape route of Sagman and EsGod's fleets. His Excellency Maximiler has yet to arrive, but we won't wait any longer. We have already gathered six Beyond Grade As here, which is enough to start the pursuit."

What he meant by 'pursuit' was not simply chasing after them but dispatching all the troops the dynasty had in the Flickering World to stop the enemies from escaping.

On the star map, the fleets of the Arcane Church and EsGod were shown to be masses of red quickly getting further away, fleeing in different directions, while blue dots representing the dynasty's troops blocked their paths.

With the arrival of the reinforcements, Milizaus and Beyoni no longer had any issues with chasing after them.

Austin expressed his intention to go home to repair his Palace of Hidden Spells and not take part in the dynasty's operation, and Tarrokov did not force an outsider invited by Han Xiao.

Heber sorted out his feelings and suddenly realized that this was an opportunity—he might be able to fulfil his wish of eliminating one Beyond Grade A.

Having that thought in his mind, Heber was very motivated. He clenched his fists so powerfully that it broke the sound barrier with a loud bang. "Humph, Mercer, is it? I've heard of this guy before. Leave him to me."

"The dynasty's dignity is not to be challenged. Milizaus' wounds have yet to heal; leave Ninjia to me." Magical light appeared in Ravenlaude's eyes.

Exterior enemies were always great solutions to internal conflicts. As members of the dynasty, after temporarily putting aside their competitive relationship with each other, they now shared a common enemy.

"I shall use my remote mechanical army to support you guys." The only Beyond Grade A who was not there, Mechanic Maximiler, looked at Han Xiao and said, "Black Star, your mechanical army has suffered heavy losses. If you need, I can lend my army to you for the time being."

"Okay, thanks."

Han Xiao nodded, stood up, and looked around at all the Beyond Grade As present. A cold tint flashed in his eyes as he said with a sharp and penetrative tone, "Let's get moving. See if they can make it back to the Central Galaxy!"

The tables had turned.

The hunters had become the hunted.

The time to counterattack had arrived!

Chapter 856: Fakisen's Plan

As hyperdrive streams of light dashed across the dark cosmic space, the traces left by the Arcane Church fleet in retreat awoke the dynasty's surveillance buoys one after another, not hiding their movements even a little bit.

Inside the Glorious Sun Grade main ship, the five Beyond Grade As including Sagman and Psyker gathered and looked at the fleet commander, Rogue, whose eyes never shifted away from the star map.

"Planet Lighthouse is at the edge of the Dawn Star Cluster and very close to the desolate universe belt. If we continue to retreat at full speed, we will get out of this security perimeter very soon," Rogue said with a deep voice.

The transmission of energy and light took time; given the sheer size of the universe, plenty of remote detection methods had delays. Transmitting real-time information through quantum communication technology was one of the more common methods used. However, the universe was way too large. There was no way the dynasty would be able to deploy surveillance buoys in every corner of the cosmic space. The security perimeter usually spread out from the stronghold planet as its center with diminishing density of surveillance buoys as the distance increased.

At this time, the Arcane Church had already escaped to the exterior security perimeter of Planet Lighthouse and was entering deep into the desolate universe belt. With absolutely no time to spare, clearing out the buoys was meaningless; they would be located in the end anyway. Therefore, Rogue did not mind the fact that their route was exposed to the dynasty. After all, he was not going to go straight to the secret stargate.

The plan was to enter stealth mode in an area with little to no buoys in the desolate universe belt so that they could get rid of the dynasty's direct surveillance. They would then split into hundreds of groups to make detours before heading to the secret stargate.

This way, a large number of the groups would be considered as abandoned. The moment their fleet departed, the location of the secret stargate had shifted. The original secret stargate location was abandoned, but this information was not updated on the star map. The only people who knew about this were the core members such as Rogue and the Beyond Grade As. This was to prevent the other groups from leaking the location of the secret stargate if they were captured by the dynasty.

Of course, these other groups were not completely abandoned; they were smoke screens. When Rogue, the Beyond Grade As, and the core groups successfully escaped, only then would these other groups be told the real location. That way, even if the location of the secret stargate was exposed, the impact would be much smaller. After all, they could destroy the stargate anytime to prevent further damage or even make those groups return from the desolate universe belt—their time was not precious at all.

"Quickly, the risks we're taking increase every minute we spend in the Flickering World," Sagman said.

"If all you can say are useless and meaningless things that everyone knows, you'd better stop speaking. Thanks to you, the risks we're taking now are completely meaningless!" Rogue did not hold back at all. His tone had traces of rage.

He had just reported the battle results to the Bishops, which had earned him a massive scolding. With the thought of his future not being the brightest in mind, he could not help but feel a rage boiling inside him. Hence, he was not in the mood to hold his emotions back toward these Beyond Grade As who had caused this operation to fail.

Getting so bluntly yelled at, Sagman's skin tightened. He thought about it for a second but did not say anything. It was true that the Beyond Grade A battlefield was what had decided the outcome and led to this failure, so he was indeed somewhat to blame.

The other four did not say anything either. They were now all on the same boat fleeing in the dynasty's territory, so no one had time to mind Rogue's disrespect.

Psyker's face looked the worst. Thinking of the fact that his friend, Dylan, was now in the dynasty's hands made his mood extremely horrible. He could not be bothered with anything else.

Seeing that no one spoke, Rogue snorted and said, "The dynasty is definitely dispatching troops to block our escape route. However, you need not worry too much; this is just a fake route. Also, most of the dynasty's fleet nearby went to support Planet Lighthouse, and it will take some time for the more distant strongholds to send out fleets. Therefore, even if we happen to be blocked, we can easily eliminate whoever's on the way. The only thing we need to worry about is the dynasty's Beyond Grade As chasing after us. According to the current situation, Tarrokov will wait for the reinforcements to arrive before making moves. Pity, I almost thought we could lure them in and set up a trap..."

While Rogue analyzed the situation, Sagman and the others were discussing the situation privately through psychic communication.

"Given the size of the fleet, we'll still be just as conspicuous even if we split up. Maybe we should leave the fleet and take mini spaceships. That's stealthier," Taylor said.

"We can consider that, but let's talk about this after the main fleet splits up."

When fleeing, the survivability and stealth of a Beyond Grade A acting alone far exceeded moving together with the fleet. As individuals with great powers who were not affected by the harsh environment of space, if they randomly hid on a desolate planet, no one would be able to find them.

This was especially true for Ninjia and Taylor, who had mastered forbidden spells. Without the enemies' interference, their teleportation spells were among the best abilities for escaping.

Rogue was worried that they might be chased by the dynasty's Beyond Grade As, so he wanted to keep Sagman and the others around. What he did not know was, Sagman and the others were also thinking about using the main fleet as bait to draw the dynasty's attention.

...

In another direction, the Fallen Ark's fleet was also retreating at full speed.

Due to the sudden rupture, EsGod's fleet had cut off contact with the Arcane Church. Without any communication channel, the two of them did not know each other's whereabouts at all and only focused on escaping on their own.

However, EsGod had one advantage. They had forced their way in from the exterior security perimeter, so they had deliberately destroyed quite a number of surveillance buoys on the way. This had caused some areas to be blind spots, which assisted in their escape.

Inside the main ship's command room, Fakisen looked away from the star map and turned to the EsGod doppelganger beside him.

EsGod's main body had already found an enclosed room to undergo evolution, and no one knew how long that would take. Before EsGod started his evolution, he had created some doppelgangers to protect himself and monitor the movement of the fleet.

EsGod was wary of everyone. Even his helpful assistant who had accompanied him for a hundred years, Fakisen was no exception. In times when his main body was the weakest, the only person he really trusted was himself.

"He still doesn't trust me..."

Fakisen's spike-filled tongue licked the blood-red metal mask that covered the upper half of his face, making an annoying scratching noise. Air pumped out from his nose like he was sneering.

Right in front of EsGod's doppelganger, Fakisen lifted his dry brunch-looking four arms. Purple fog flew out from his dark purple skin, forming a sphere in midair.

Then, he summoned a subordinate and gave the orb to him. "Empty an ordinary battleship, remove its energy core and AI system, and leave it as an empty shell. Put this orb inside that spaceship, then abandon it and let it drift around on the path we passed by. The dynasty troops chasing us will discover this spaceship."

The EsGod doppelganger turned to him and said coldly, "What are you trying to do?"

"Hehe..." Fakisen's laughter was eerie. "I'm planning to contact the dynasty..."

Bang!

The moment he said that, the EsGod doppelganger immediately grabbed him by his neck and lifted him up, pressing him against the wall.

"Are you selling me out?"

Although his throat was grabbed by EsGod, Fakisen was not afraid at all. Instead, he laughed even louder. "Hahaha, I'm planning to work together with the dynasty. If they can give us information about the Arcane Church, we can send some of our people to intercept them. They're pawns anyway. We're the closest to the Arcane Church. With our help, the dynasty will be able to drag the Arcane Church back more efficiently."

"There's no need for that," the EsGod doppelganger said coldly.

"No, there definitely is a need. The dynasty surely wants to fight the Arcane Church more than us. There are many Beyond Grade As over there, which makes them much more valuable. If the dynasty can capture them, the Arcane Church will lose close to half of their Beyond Grade As. The dynasty will not give up such an amazing opportunity to cause damage to the Arcane Church. And when the dynasty puts their focus on the Arcane Church, Your Excellency EsGod, the pressure you face will be much smaller. Hehehe."

Fakisen's tone was filled with mockery as he continued, "After fleeing at such a crucial moment, the Arcane Church is definitely going to hold a grudge against us for it. When we return to the Central Galaxy, we're going to face both the Crimson dynasty and the Arcane Church. If we do this, not only will the dynasty be less furious at us, the Arcane Church will be weakened too. This means that the Beyond Grade As you'll have to face will be much fewer. Furthermore, if the Arcane Church do suffer such an enormous loss, they probably won't have chance to come make trouble for us any time soon."

The EsGod doppelganger asked, "How do I know you're not going to sell out my location?"

"Hee, if Your Excellency is not assured, please leave an EsGod doppelganger in that empty spaceship all you like, to monitor the communication between me and the dynasty. If you think I sold out your location... Hehe, I'm right here. You can kill me anytime."

The EsGod doppelganger stayed silent for a while before suddenly saying, "I'll leave a doppelganger behind to negotiate with the dynasty. You don't have to participate in it."

Although this idea Fakisen had was strange and sudden to him, he thought it did indeed make sense. After all, even if the negotiation went south, it would just be a doppelganger getting eliminated.

"Hehe, that'll do too."

As the EsGod doppelganger let Fakisen go, he landed on the ground, rubbed his neck, and called a subordinate over. He broke the fog orb that he had just made apart and absorbed the fog back into his body. Then, he acted as if nothing had happened and continued to observe the star map.

No one could see Fakisen's eyes under the blood-red mask that covered the upper half of his face, and no one knew what he was thinking... Speaking of which, no one actually knew how he saw with his eyes covered.

...

The intense battle at Planet Lighthouse had ended, but this whole thing was far from over. Under Tarrokov's command, the dynasty's fleets started their pursuit of the Arcane Church and the Fallen Ark's fleets.

Before the shock, confusion, and curiosity of the army players who flocked to Bun-Hit-Dog's posts broadcasting about the battlefield's turn of events dissipated, a new mission popped up on everyone's interface.

Before this, the Black Star Army players only knew that Planet Lighthouse was attacked, there were around ten Beyond Grade As fighting, and their army commander Black Star was one of them. As for the identity of the attackers, the cause of this incident, or anything else, they had no idea at all.

This mission, however, explained all this and brought even more shock to the players.

_____________________

The Crimson dynasty Order: All Out Pursuit

Mission Introduction: In order to obtain the Evolution Cube and cause conflicts, the Arcane Church worked together with the Fallen Ark and attacked the dynasty's outpost in the Flickering World. There were seven enemy Beyond Grade As. However, with the help of the dynasty's ally Black Star, Milizaus, Beyoni, and the friend invited by Black Star, Austin, we successfully defeated the enemies! Currently, these two fleets are now fleeing in the Flickering World. All forces are hereby dispatched to pursue the enemies and uphold the dynasty's dignity—Crimson Dynasty Exploration Army Chief Commander, Tarrokov.

Mission Requirements: Chase after the Arcane Church and the Fallen Ark's fleets, find out their whereabouts, and eliminate their men to the best of your ability.

Rewards will be given after the mission ends depending on your performance.

_____________________

Knowing what had happened, the Shattered Star Ring page on the forums exploded.

"The Arcane Church attacked the Crimson Dynasty? Are the Universal Civilizations going to start a war with each other‽"

"No wonder as many as eleven Beyond Grade As appeared in one huge fight. That's the reason behind it. Is the Army Commander okay? Is he still alive?"

"Their target is the army commander's Evolution Cube, so this was actually caused by the army commander, huh?"

"Damn, targeted by a Universal Civilization yet managed to force them away, awesome!"

"The Black Star Army is the Crimson dynasty's ally. Does that mean that the army is now also the Arcane Church's enemy?"

"I've got a feeling that something huge is going to happen!"

This time, Bun-Hit-Dog snatched up the first-hand information. Under his post, countless players came to comment. Dozens of new comments were appearing every second, which made him extremely excited...

Following Black Star was indeed the right choice. There was explosive news every now and then!

After the initial shock, many players were thrilled. After experiencing three versions, they had discovered some patterns—the things happening in Galaxy were connected, and they influenced each other. This was an extremely orderly system. One could actually use logic to predict some of the possible incidents that might happen in the future through the intelligence and news of the various areas.

This incident involved the three largest civilizations, so it was not a small matter by any means. If the two sides went at each other, the storyline would definitely be huge.

Some people speculated that this attack might have been an early sign of a future main storyline.

Or it might even be the main storyline of the next version.

It was not impossible.

As this kind of speculation spread on the forums, some people made different speculations saying that this might be connected to what would happen during the version update period and would only appear in the next version in the form of a background introduction. Many also agreed with this.

Due to Han Xiao's past actions, the Chinese players in the Shattered Star Ring had developed a habit of guessing the large-scale storyline of the versions. The Australians and Russians from the Constellation Corridor joined in on the discussion, too, mixing into this atmosphere filled with excitement.

While all kinds of speculations circulated the forums, the Black Star Army were not just occupied with arguing on the forums but also took part in the pursuit.

Although most people were too far away and could not make any contributions, the army players were used to participating in large-scale Faction Missions together as a whole. Furthermore, this mission did not have a failure condition, so they would probably receive the minimum reward as long as they made an effort to chase after the enemies.

The Flickering World was still in a state of information lockdown; its network was not fully connected with the known universe yet. Other than the ones involved in the matter, the other forces in the outside world still did not know what had happened in the Flickering World.

The players were the first group of outsiders that knew about these secret pieces of information. This time, the forums displayed its unique information advantage—while the outside world did not have a clue about this matter, almost all the players knew about what had happened on Planet Lighthouse!

The forces of the three civilizations were spread across the entire explored universe. Their influence was incomparable. No matter which Star Field the players were in, they could all feel the intense and uptight atmosphere. They all looked forward to seeing what kind of tremendous impact this incident would cause after the outside world knew about it!

...

On the other side, Tarrokov's main fleet took off from Planet Lighthouse to chase after the Arcane Church. The five Beyond Grade As—Han Xiao, Milizaus, Beyoni, Heber, and Ravenlaude—were working together on this very rare occasion.

Not long after departure, the high-level official who was responsible for the dynasty's logistics contacted Han Xiao upon Urranrell's request, giving him more than enough face by asking him personally about what Ultimate Knowledges he wanted.

Chapter 857: Apostle Weapon and Ultimate Knowledge

"Alright, we will send these two knowledges to you as soon as possible. Remember to receive it." The Logistics officer then hung up.

Han Xiao left the quantum network and played with the black handgun in his hands while waiting for the arrival of the knowledge.

The handgun in his hands looked like a backward firearm, but it actually made use of dark energy with a mini energy furnace within it. It was mainly sold to the players as a long-ranged weapon but was no more than a toy gun to Han Xiao. It was pretty useless and was mainly made into such an appearance for old times' sake.

As his strength grew greater, Han Xiao's memories of the time when he was weak grew deeper. The many scenes of him fighting back on Planet Aquamarine flashed through his head. He was already a powerful character in the universe and had come a long way from the time when he found it difficult to kill even an ordinary warrior. He now had the ability to even destroy planets, and the number of things capable of killing him was decreasing.

"It has already been more than twenty years..." Han Xiao had a complicated expression on his face.

Psionic Prime stood beside Han Xiao and asked, "Master, what are you thinking about?"

"I only taught about the past." Han Xiao then turned around to look at Psionic Prime.

"I realized that you are becoming more and more curious."

Psionic Prime nodded his metal head. "Although I can obtain knowledge from the web, the emotions of a living being are boundless, and I am only able to understand some things after experiencing it personally. Thus, I enjoy communicating."

"This is a good thing. I'll need you to help me manage a Mechanical Life civilization in the future. You are the first Mechanical Life that I created, and if nothing goes wrong, you will be the leader in the future. As the leader of a civilization, you must learn to understand others and understand the thoughts of other Mechanical Lives."

Han Xiao then paused for a moment, and a helpless look could be seen on his face. "Enjoying communication is a good thing, but you should change your habits when talking on the web..."

Han Xiao used his Virtual Technology skills to keep a record of the Mechanical Life's web data. He realized that many Mechanical Lives including Psionic Prime enjoyed having side accounts to chat with the citizens of the various civilizations.

It would not matter if it was just a normal conversation, but most of the Mechanical Lives would have a few hundred or thousand accounts to chat with others at the same time with the contents of the conversation being extremely explosive. The most common one would be having dirty talk by mimicking the opposite gender.

In his eyes, the majority of the Mechanical Lives were like problematic children. They were like sponges absorbing the evil and kindness of numerous living beings, forming various different personalities.

Sizing Psionic Prime up, Han Xiao thought for a moment before saying, "Stand in front of me."

Psionic Prime obeyed obediently.

Han Xiao sat on the sofa, and a bluish gold Mechanical Force appeared on his palm.

"You are my first child, and after a long period of observation, I am satisfied in your potential. Are you willing to become my Apostle Weapon and obtain even greater strength?"

"I am willing to accept everything of yours, master." Psionic Prime knelt before him.

"Then accept this bestowment. Also, do not call me master in the future..."

Han Xiao's lips curled up slightly.

"Call me Lord."

The next moment, the special Mechanical Force in his palms, which contained the 'Power of Lord's Dominance', entered Psionic Prime's body. This was the skill of the Lord Mechanic, [Apostle Life Creation].

Hum!

Psionic Prime's energy furnace began surging and bolts of bluish-gold Mechanical Force extended out from within the mechanical body as though the bolts of electricity were alive.

The magnetic field that contained a strange aura enveloped Psionic Prime's body, and the mechanical structures and parts within Psionic Prime's body began to change. The surrounding alloy began to shake as though they were about to be sucked into Psionic Prime's body.

Han Xiao then stretched out his arms and sent a large number of nanoparticles toward Psionic Prime. These nanoparticles revolved around Psionic Prime like a star ring. The revolution gradually picked up speed, and the nanoparticles transformed into a metal sea that entered Psionic Prime's body to provide raw materials for the upgrade.

Han Xiao then sat down on the couch by the side and played with the dark energy handgun while admiring the scene before him. The special effects of [Apostle Life Creation] were much more dazzling than [Emperor's Gift].

There was a limited number of slots for his Apostle Weapons, a mere ten or so.

After a while, Psionic Prime's transformation had finally ended, and his appearance had transformed greatly.

Psionic Prime was even taller than before, about four meters tall. He had many new components, and his armor had many complicated but beautiful engravings on it.

With a round crown like metal on his head, Psionic Prime held onto a long, staff-like mechanical spear in his hands.

"How do you feel?" Han Xiao asked with a smile.

"I thank the Lord for your bestowment. I can feel my new strength," Psionic Prime said with a deep voice and held up the spear in his hands. Psionic energy then gushed out from his energy furnace, and he burst forth with energy.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and suddenly lifted his handgun, opening fire at Psionic Prime.

Boom boom boom!

A couple of dark energy laser beams struck Psionic Prime but were blocked by a layer of psionic energy. At the same time, the battle notification was triggered.

Han Xiao then looked at Psionic Prime's attributes, which were displayed on the interface, and nodded with satisfaction.

Psionic Prime was currently at level 215, and his various attributes were strengthened. He was now at a boss level, and his strength had exceeded all his other Mechanical Lives.

Without Han Xiao's Mechanical Force boost, Psionic Prime still had the strength of a Calamity Grade, and with the boost from his Mechanical Force, Psionic Prime would be able to exchange blows with a Beyond Grade A and would no longer be cannon fodder. His strength was similar to EsGod's doppelganger.

The spear in Psionic Prime's hand was a special Apostle Weapon from [Apostle Life Creation] and was called 'Psionic Prime Spear'. It could also split into a floating state and even enlarge or shrink. It had many different forms and could even be transformed into a psionic energy form. It could be used for both long- and close-range battle, and both a Mechanical Pugilist and Cannon Master was able to use it. The level of the weapon was above 200, and it was of the silver orange grade. The strength of the weapon would be increased when being used by Psionic Prime.

Apart from this, Psionic Prime also obtained a special 'Apostle Characteristic' and 'Apostle Authority'. His Apostle Characteristics were 'Stable' and 'Leader', which could strengthen the Mechanical Life around him during battle. His Apostle Authorities were 'Psionic Control' and 'Battle Boost', which gave him better control over psionic energy and higher combat power.

A satisfied smile could be seen on Han Xiao's face.

The strength of an Apostle Weapon was extremely impressive, but it was a pity that [Apostle Life Creation] had a long cooldown of a month. It meant that he would only be able to create twelve Apostle Weapons in a year. Of course, because of his talents like [Machinery Emperor] and [Elementary Grade Mechanical Sense], he could create more than twelve Apostle Weapons.

"Familiarize yourself with your new energy, my new Apostle," Han Xiao said with joy.

"I will not let the Lord down." Psionic Prime said.

Beep beep.

Han Xiao's communicator rang at this moment; the Crimson Dynasty had finally sent the two Ultimate Knowledges over.

Han Xiao spent twelve thousand Contribution Points to choose two Ultimate Knowledge.

Armed Branch: [Endless Material Science]

Control Branch: [Virtual Creator]

One of them belonged to his Virtual Mechanic branch, and he only needed eight Potential Points. The other was an important knowledge to Mechanics, and the Mechanic from any branch would try to learn it.

Resources and energy had always been the two largest bottlenecks to a Mechanic's technological skills, and the Armed Branch had a material-related knowledge at all levels. This allowed a Mechanic to combine more powerful materials and increase the basic attributes of a Mechanic. This was a core knowledge of the Mechanic Class.

Learning these two knowledges required thirty-two Potential Points and Han Xiao had thirty-three Potential Points on him.

Han Xiao smiled and immediately learned the two knowledge.

Learning...

Successfully learned! You have learned [Endless Material Science]!

Learning...

Successfully learned! You have learned [Virtual Creator]!

You have received the talent [Material Pioneer]!

[Material Pioneer]: The probability of success for merging new materials is increased, and the abilities obtained from special materials have been increased. For example, the self-recovery ability of machines when using memory alloy will be increased.

You have received talent [Virtual Lord]!

[Virtual Lord]: Your various Virtual Technology skills have been strengthened greatly. The total bonus is 2.5. When you enter the quantum network vision, your consciousness can jump to different quantum network nodes and increase your range greatly. You can let Virtual Life Forms submit to you. You have mastered all the various Virtual Technology skills, and the quantum network is your fortress.

You have acquired [Ultimate Material Refinement]!

You have acquired [Endless Material Combination]!

[Endless Material Combination]: You can combine the specialties of any materials and attempt to create new material recipes. The higher the grade of the material and the more complicated the recipe, the lower the success rate. The basic success rate is determined by INT and Machinery Affinity. When you craft a new recipe, the strength of the new material will be increased.

You have acquired [Virtual Life Evolution]!

[Virtual Life Evolution]: You can transform an AI into a Virtual Life Form. A Virtual Life Form has more powerful infiltrative and defensive abilities.

You have acquired [Virtual Soul]!

[Virtual Soul]: You soul can transform into a Virtual Life Form and live within the quantum network. Total level, INT, and Virtual Technology skills will determine the strength after transformation in the quantum network. This effect can be cancelled.

When you use your Mechanical Force to connect to a target, you can temporarily virtualize your target's soul and pull it into the quantum network. Success rate is determined by total level, INT, MYS, and LUK. If successful, the target won't be able to control their body temporarily, and attacking the target in the quantum network will cause mental damage.

Cooldown: 15 min.

Han Xiao looked through the notifications and nodded with satisfaction.

"The effects of these talents are extremely powerful. Endless Material Science allowed me to improve the quality of my machines and create new materials. Virtual knowledge allowed me to have new battle tactics."

With the two Ultimate Knowledge in his hands, Han Xiao was extremely satisfied. He did not make use of his remaining six thousand Contribution Points to exchange for new knowledge but kept them for the Political Asset effect.

Just when he was about to go to the battle room to test Psionic Prime's new strength, his communicator rang. Tarrokov was calling him, revealing some information which truly baffled him.

Han Xiao replied with an odd expression.

"You're saying that EsGod wants to work with the dynasty temporarily and send some manpower to help us stop the Arcane Church?"

"That's right. Our forces that chased after the Fallen Ark troops captured an empty battleship with EsGod's doppelganger inside. He didn't fight back and allowed himself to be captured, saying that he wanted to talk to us."

Tarrokov was truly surprised.

Han Xiao frowned and felt that this matter was truly suspicious. There was no need for EsGod to do this. EsGod was extremely mobile, and he was not one to bother about his subordinates. Thus, he would be able to escape even without the help of the dynasty. Furthermore, the dynasty's main target was not him. Why would EsGod bother making such an unnecessary move to anger the Arcane Church? Could it be that he thought that he would be able to make the dynasty happy by doing so?

After thinking for a moment, Han Xiao asked, "Chief commander, what are you planning to do?"

"Er... EsGod wants information about the Arcane Church's coordinates, and it won't really matter if we give it to him. The Arcane Church's fleet will leave our security perimeter very soon, and we will lose track of them very quickly. This piece of news isn't secret, and it won't matter who we tell.

"Even if EsGod isn't truly sincere, we wouldn't suffer any losses. But if he really wants to let Sagman and the others be his scapegoat, we will definitely earn big. As for him working together with the Arcane Church to ambush us, we can always settle the score in the future."

"Then let us go according to your plan."

Although Han Xiao felt that EsGod's decision was extremely strange, Tarrokov was the commander. Since Han Xiao could not think of a problem, he would not interfere in Tarrokov's decision.

Right at this moment, Tarrokov said, "There is something else. EsGod's doppelganger would like to meet you."

"Meet me? Alright. Since the dynasty fleet that is giving chase to EsGod doesn't have any Beyond Grade As, I will split out a portion of my mechanical army to meet him and also monitor his doppelganger in the process."

Han Xiao was certain that EsGod probably wanted to 'thank' him for the evolution energy.

After pausing for a while, he continued.

"As for the Arcane Church fleet... even if they leave the security perimeter, I have some means to locate them..."

As a Virtual Mechanic, how can he not leave something behind for the Arcane Church fleet during the battle. Although the firewall of the Arcane Church fleet was strong, he still had the ability to leave a little something behind.

Han Xiao's eyes gleamed.

Choosing to learn the [Virtual Creator] knowledge at this moment was to chase after them!

Chapter 858: Ames' Actions

After giving chase for a while, the star map showed that the Arcane Church fleet had left the security perimeter and begun to split up. Tarrokov had temporarily lost contact with the Arcane Church fleet. Because of his previous conversation with Han Xiao, he invited Han Xiao to the main flagship so that Han Xiao could lock onto the locations of the enemy vessels through his Virtual Technology.

Han Xiao walked through the corridors of the main flagship, straight to the command room, with Hila and the others following behind him.

All of the dynasty's commanders who he met along the way gave him a respectful salute. Han Xiao's achievements in this battle had earned him the respect of all the participants in the battle. It could be said that their lives had been saved by Black Star, and they were naturally grateful to him.

Han Xiao responded with a smile and turned around to see Hila frowning. He then looked down at her neck only to see a bandage on her neck, which extended down her collarbone. He then asked with concern, "Are your injuries alright?"

Hila shook her head. "Such light injuries will recover in no time at all. You do not need to worry."

After the battle, she did not allow Aurora to waste her life force to treat them and chose to recover naturally.

"Does it still hurt?"

"A little bit. The painkillers aren't too effective." Hila frowned. Although she had a stubborn personality, there was no need to act tough for such a small matter.

"Then I need to congratulate you for being alive." Han Xiao chuckled.

Their group then arrived at the command room, where Tarrokov was waiting for them. Upon seeing Han Xiao's arrival, he immediately came forward to welcome him. He then pointed at a location on the star map and said, "This is the last position where the Arcane Church was seen. We have currently lost track of them. Black Star, we shall rely on you."

Han Xiao nodded and closed his eyes to enter the quantum network viewpoint.

In the darkness, nodes began to light up in the quantum network with some near and others far. An endless stream of information was being transmitted by the nodes, and an illusory wave of information floated toward him.

The star map appeared in the quantum network in the form of nodes, and Han Xiao could easily zoom in or out. In the quantum network, distance was completely negligible since he could jump from node to node easily. The improvement from [Virtual Creator] strengthened him in all aspects and greatly increased the range of his abilities.

The quantum network viewpoint seems more detailed than before.

Han Xiao immersed himself in this new feeling for a while before getting to work. He then slowly connected to the nodes to feel the subtle traces that the Arcane Church had left behind in the quantum network.

His brain rapidly processed a large amount of information, and Han Xiao opened his eyes abruptly.

Pa!

A few hundred red dots suddenly lit up on the star map before them. These were the Arcane Church battleships that had concealed themselves.

The locations of all the divisions were marked, and nothing could hide from him!

Tarrokov was overjoyed. "Good job!"

"Haha, I didn't do much." Han Xiao backed out from the quantum network viewpoint and chuckled.

If it was before he learned [Virtual Creator], the traces of his infiltration would probably have alerted the Arcane Church's artificial intelligence, and they would have cleared it up.

But after learning the Ultimate Knowledge of the Virtual Mechanic class, he had received a huge upgrade and could easily create a backdoor into the Arcane Church's system without being detected. This was why he had chosen to learn [Virtual Creator].

Tarrokov stroked his chin and said, "Now that we have their coordinates, the enemy's movements will be transparent to us, and we don't need to worry about losing them. Hmm, the enemy has split up their forces, and a portion of them are probably going to be sacrificed. If this is the case, it is very likely that these pawns being sacrificed have fake information about the location of the stargates and wish to distract us. The true location of the stargate should be in the fleet that contains those Beyond Grade As. Black Star, are you able to lock onto the enemy commander and Beyond Grade As' positions? I suspect that they are not on the main flagship."

"I can, but I need to infiltrate the enemy's surveillance equipment. The risk of being exposed will be increased, and we may lose their locations. Are you sure you want to take the risk?" Han Xiao replied. The security of a Universal Civilization naturally should not be underestimated.

After thinking for a while, Tarrokov shook his head. "We should continue to maintain our current state. As long as we have their coordinates, we can try to capture their entire fleet in one fell swoop. Give EsGod a portion of the intelligence first."

Han Xiao nodded and did not say another word. His consciousness then entered his mechanical army. The mechanical army that he had sent out was almost going to come into contact with EsGod's doppelganger.

...

A small fleet was currently approaching the meeting point together with an empty spaceship. They had been waiting for a long while, and beams of light suddenly appeared from the darkness of space and stopped before them.

Both fleets came into contact with each other and verified their identities. The Black Star Army then approached the empty spaceship.

A large number of dynasty soldiers were currently pointing their weapons at the exit of the spaceship, waiting for the Beyond Grade A envoy to take over from them.

For a bunch of ordinary soldiers to monitor EsGod's doppelganger, even if EsGod did not fight back, they would still have an immense sense of pressure. It was as though they were facing a beast that could kill them at any moment. Thankfully, their helpers had finally arrived.

Whoosh!

The hatch to the spaceship opened, and Psionic Prime walked in with his spear. Behind him was a group of Mechanical Lives and a large number of mechanical soldiers.

Psionic Prime then looked down at the dynasty's soldiers and said, "I am the first Apostle of Lord Black Star, Psionic Prime. I am here to take over the mission from all of you and shall watch over EsGod's doppelganger."

"We shall hand him over to you." The group of soldiers heaved a sigh of relief and hurriedly handed over the mission before leaving the empty spaceship hastily.

Psionic Prime then brought his troops along to the empty spaceship. EsGod's doppelganger was currently present.

Behind him, Silver Flash looked at the gigantic Psionic Prime and said angrily, "The Lord is too biased. Why does he get to be the first Apostle Weapon?"

"Stop complaining. Psionic Prime is the first child, so this can't be helped," a Mechanical Life Protector called 'Gold Sovereign' said. He belonged to the first batch of Mechanical Life and had a cold personality.

In front of them was a beastman-type mechanical soldier called 'Mad Sky Hunter'. He turned around and said, "The Lord has his own considerations, and we only have to give our absolute loyalty. Since the Lord bestowed Psionic Prime with such strength, it means that there is a limited number of Apostle Weapon slots. Perhaps only a small portion of us will be able to transform into Apostle Weapons."

Psionic Prime listened to the discussion behind him without saying a word and arrived at their destination in the spaceship.

The energy core in this empty spaceship had already been removed, and the spaceship was currently short on power. EsGod's doppelganger was leaning on the couch, and he faced Psionic Prime's mechanical army.

"Black Star, you're here," EsGod's doppelganger said with a smile.

"I am Psionic Prime. The Lord does not want to meet you now. You can just let me know what you want to tell him."

EsGod's doppelganger sized Psionic Prime up and said with a teasing tone, "Apostle Weapon? Black Star didn't have such an ability the last time we fought. It seems like he received a great reward from the current battle. Alright, I do not have any interest in talking to you. Get Black Star out to see me."

Psionic Prime then held his spear up and pretended that he did not hear anything.

Upon seeing that, EsGod raised his arm out, and his arm stretched out like rubber, sending out a punch that was too fast to follow with the naked eye!

Clank!

His fists were imbued with Esper energy and crashed onto Psionic Prime's spear, generating a small shockwave.

Without saying anything, Psionic Prime channeled his energy into his spear, and the spear entered its released mode.

A psionic energy wave then shot out from the spear!

Swoosh!

EsGod's doppelganger had a stunning speed, and he avoided the attack nimbly. However, the couch that he was sitting on was sliced in two, and the entire wall of the spaceship was also sliced cleanly in two.

The mechanical troops and EsGod's doppelganger thus drifted into space and faced each other in a standoff. The dynasty's spaceships by the side immediately aimed their cannons at EsGod's doppelganger.

Psionic Prime stood at the very front, and a surge of Mechanical Force descended on his body from afar. Psionic Prime's body exploded forth with a blinding light. The other mechanical troops did not receive the boost from the Mechanical Force and retreated under Psionic Prime's orders.

EsGod's doppelganger looked at the surge of Mechanical Force and knew that Han Xiao was definitely paying attention to the situation. He knew what Han Xiao's intention was and could not help but sneer.

Han Xiao wanted him to fight the Apostle Weapon to test the strength of the weapon.

"Humph, on account of the fact that you allowed me to evolve, I shall play with your Apostle Weapon for a while."

The next moment, EsGod's doppelganger made his move, and his arms stretched out toward Psionic Prime like a cannonball. He launched ferocious attacks, leaving behind a series of afterimages.

This doppelganger did not have any powerful Esper Abilities and only had a few abilities to strengthen and modify the physique. However, this EsGod doppelganger still had the strength of a Beyond Grade A and the ability to suppress all Calamity Grades.

Psionic Prime then brandished his spear to fight EsGod, and both their figures weaved around in space.

Psionic Prime and EsGod's doppelganger were evenly matched with each other in the head-on confrontation!

Psionic Prime's spear was imbued with blue psionic energy, and EsGod was like a lump of clay, capable of changing his form to avoid various different attacks. At the same time, EsGod's attacks were also avoided by Psionic Prime by splitting his body up and transforming into various mobile floating guards.

The mechanical troops watching by the side could not help but be surprised.

They were originally no more than cannon fodder in the face of a Beyond Grade A, but Psionic Prime had the strength to fight a Beyond Grade A head on.

"Is this the strength of an Apostle Weapon?"

Silver Flash and all the other Mechanical Life earnestly yearned for such strength.

Both parties clashed time and time again, and both of their figures retreated together.

At this moment, the Mechanical Force on Psionic Prime dissipated, indicating that it was the end of their spar.

EsGod's doppelganger then stopped fighting after noticing that since he was there to talk.

All of them returned to a Black Star Army spaceship that was by the side. EsGod sat down, and Han Xiao's long distance projection appeared before him.

Upon seeing that, EsGod's doppelganger said with a smile, "Black Star, it is all thanks to you that I've been able to evolve this time."

Han Xiao then snorted. "You wanted to see me just to say something like this?"

"Of course not." EsGod's doppelganger waved his hands and chuckled. "I wanted to ask you if you managed to come up with any results after researching that set of wormhole data."

This fellow indeed chose to expose the data on purpose so that he could borrow my connections to help him research the data... Han Xiao's eyes narrowed.

However, EsGod still thought that he was the only one who knew about the existence of the World Tree Civilization and felt that he had an upper hand in intelligence.

Up until now, EsGod still thought that Han Xiao only researched the wormhole data to be careful but did not know that Han Xiao was also aware of the World Tree Civilization's existence.

Han Xiao naturally would not destroy EsGod's illusion as this was the only way to prevent EsGod from being wary.

"Long story short. These are the coordinates that the dynasty wants me to pass to you." Han Xiao then got Phillip to show a portion of the data. "If you really want to help the dynasty stop the Arcane Church, the dynasty may reconsider how they should deal with you."

EsGod's doppelganger did not bother responding and started to view the intelligence report.

Upon seeing that, Han Xiao said, "However, I cannot understand why you suddenly chose to work with the dynasty. Angering the Arcane Church has no benefits to you."

"You don't need to worry about this." EsGod did not even bother raising his head.

Han Xiao stroked his chin and fell into thought.

He had always felt that this was not EsGod's intention but he was fooled by someone else.

Although EsGod would be able to curry favor with the dynasty by doing so, Han Xiao felt that his intention was to make use of this opportunity to increase the Arcane Church's losses. It was as though his targets were Sagman and the other Beyond Grade As.

"If they manage to succeed, who will benefit the most? The Crimson Dynasty? The Federation of Light? Or maybe those Super Star Cluster Civilizations?"

Han Xiao let out a deep sigh.

...

After the Arcane Church fleet split up to escape, Rogue, Sagman, and the others changed their spaceships and abandoned the main flagship. They then disguised themselves as a small fleet and were currently making their way to the true position of the secret stargate.

Rogue felt that such a method would be able to confuse the dynasty's forces, but the following event had shocked him.

A portion of their escaping fleet suffered from an ambush. However, the ones ambushing them were not just the dynasty's fleet but also the Fallen Ark fleet!

"Is EsGod mad? Why is he attacking us‽"

Rogue panted heavily with an ashen expression and bloodshot eyes.

"That darn EsGod actually arrived at an agreement with the dynasty. This fellow really wants us to help restrain the dynasty for him!"

Sagman was also extremely frustrated. It was one thing for EsGod to go back on his word, but he had even gone a step further to attack them. Although he did not have any expectations in EsGod, he could not help but be enraged by EsGod's actions.

Psyker then looked at the star map and suddenly said, "The situation is strange. They are accurately ambushing our divisions. Is it because that division was unlucky to run into the dynasty's defensive line, or has the dynasty grasped our coordinates?"

Everyone's expression changed greatly the moment these words were said.

Psyker gritted his teeth. "Black Star is a Virtual Mechanic, so he may have done something."

Mercer also gritted his teeth and thought to himself, What kind of bullsh*t Mechanic is he?

Upon hearing that, Rogue immediately activated the automatic artificial intelligence scan on the spaceship, but there were no traces of Han Xiao's infiltration.

"Black Star's infiltration can't be detected..." Sagman felt his head ache. He was extremely knowledgeable, and he knew that a Virtual Mechanic capable of bypassing a Universal Civilization's firewall was not easy to deal with.

Although none of them were certain that Han Xiao had managed to lock onto their positions, they decided to prepare for the worst-case scenario.

"The dynasty's encirclement isn't complete yet, so this is our only chance to escape," Rogue said. "Inform our forces to split up again. I want to see a million divisions. Also, cut off half of the fleet's quantum network connection!"

He wanted to seize the opportunity before the encirclement was formed to use even more divisions to confuse the dynasty. Forming a million divisions meant that each division would only have a few battleships, and it would be impossible for them to fight back. This was akin to sacrificing even more people.

Cutting off half of the fleet's quantum network connection meant that these divisions would become deaf and blind. It would be impossible for them to communicate with the other fleets, so they could only escape according to the star map. The only advantage of doing so was that they would be able to prevent their locations from being spotted. Rogue was prepared to cut off his own quantum network connection, and it was akin to giving up command.

Because of Han Xiao's methods, Rogue had no choice but to make such a decision. It was akin to abandoning everyone in exchange for their survival.

Ninjia looked at him coldly and said, "Sir, you will definitely have to face court martial if you do so."

"Hahaha..." Rogue laughed. "After the failure of this mission, what kind of a future will I have?

"If not for Black Star turning the tables on all of you, would I have failed?

"Do I hate all of you? Of course I do!

"But all of you are still the high-level combatants of the Arcane Church.

"These soldiers and troops can be easily drafted and hired again, but all of you are different. It is impossible to easily replicate the existence of a Beyond Grade A, and you still have the Universal Treasure Ten Thousand Deity Scepter in your hands...

"My top priority is to cover your escape. Your lives are more important than any of ours!

"When I was in command school, my lecturer told me that I shouldn't be a commander if I can't be merciless. Having perfection in all aspects is an impossible dream, so we have to make sacrifices in order to complete our objective. Everything that isn't important can be abandoned...

"I have already thought things through! Who cares about the court martial? My only mission is to protect the strength of the Arcane Church!"

Rogue panted heavily after saying such a 'moving' speech.

Sagman and the others all narrowed their eyes.

As Beyond Grade As, they would not be easily taken in by the words of others, and Rogue's intention was not able to escape their eyes.

The five of them looked at each other before looking at Rogue.

"Then let's go according to your plan," Sagman said slowly.

...

Above Planet Aquamarine, Floating Dragon Island had a lot more facilities a few months ago. There were plenty of spaceships flying in and out, and it was extremely prosperous.

In order to set up their main camp, Floating Dragon no longer allowed scavengers and galactic pirates to land on the island and chased away all the gray organizations on the island. Of course, there was a portion who did not dare approach the stronghold of the Black Star Army and took the initiative to escape.

The organizations entering Floating Dragon were mainly proper financial groups, and under Floating Dragon's influence, Planet Aquamarine also gained support from quite a few financial groups.

In Floating Dragon Palace, Ames was currently seated on her throne.

Ames looked down at the representatives who had come to visit, and her face remained completely expressionless; no one was able to tell what she was thinking. In truth, however, she was just daydreaming.

Sigh, all these troublesome matters will be taken care of by Jenny anyway.

Ames' mind had already drifted elsewhere.

I wonder how Hila and Aurora are doing. Tsk, Black Star is truly annoying. You took both my students away and don't even send some news back.

Beep beep.

At that moment, her communicator, which was floating nearby, rang. Ames then grabbed it with her force field and was a little surprised upon seeing who the caller was.

Curious, Ames picked up the call and Austin's figure appeared. "Austin? Didn't this fellow go and search for materials? Why have you called me?"

Austin smiled and said, "Ames, I have a piece of information that may be of use to you."

Ames raised her brows. "Interesting. When did you start selling information? Isn't that Black Star's hobby?"

Austin smiled profoundly and informed Ames about the battle at Planet Lighthouse.

Ames was seated lazily at the start, but she began to gradually sit up straight with unstable force field energy floating around beside her, bringing about a huge pressure to the financial group representatives below.

"... that's about everything." Austin finished his description and added, "I am only informing you about this because you are Black Star's ally. Just as I expected, you aren't aware of this matter, and Black Star hid it from you. Haha, I think he doesn't want you to be dragged into this storm."

"Stop nagging. I know what you mean. Humph, in any case, thanks for the information."

Ames hung up and shut her eyes as though she was in deep thought.

Aesop, who was by the side, had heard the conversation and shook his head. "The prophecy was real. Thankfully, I reminded Black Star. If not, he might not have been able to escape this time. Black Star hid this matter from you because he doesn't want you to be involved in the matters of the Universal Civilizations. However, Austin intentionally informed you about this because he wants to muddy the waters. Ah, he is truly a little brat who wants the world to fall into chaos."

Upon hearing that, Ames opened her eyes and said, "I am his ally, not his subordinate. What rights does he have to stop me from participating?"

Aesop had a knowing look on his face. He then shook his head and asked, "What do you plan to do?"

"Contact the Crimson Dynasty envoy Zoel. The Crimson Dynasty is probably going to mobilize their forces in the Shattered Star Ring to attack the Arcane Church's forces and stargate..."

Ames then stood up.

"Black Star, Psyker, Heber, and Austin, everyone is in the Flickering World...

"Thus, I am the only Beyond Grade A in the Shattered Star Ring now!

"I can go wherever I like!"

Chapter 859: Return Gift!

More and more dynasty fleets were being gathered, and the desolate universe belt outside of the Dawn Star Cluster was starting to be locked down. The encirclement was forming, and the gaps for the Arcane Church fleet were slowly closing.

With the aid of Han Xiao's coordinates, the dynasty managed to capture even more battleships. After Rogue ordered for a million divisions to be formed, these divisions no longer had the ability to break through after being discovered by the dynasty and could only be wiped out or captured.

Not too long later, tens of thousands of battleships fell into the hands of the dynasty, and the Arcane Church members on board the battleships could only become captives.

However, Rogue's method had indeed slowed down the dynasty's speed greatly.

If they wanted to hide something, the best method was not to lock it up in a safe but to hide it within a sea of bait. This was the situation that the dynasty was facing.

In the main flagship, Tarrokov was having a virtual meeting with Han Xiao and the others to analyze the situation.

"According to the statements of the captives, the enemy commander Rogue adopted the method of abandoning their forces to confuse us. Furthermore, half of their battleships have disconnected from the network and escaped from our surveillance. They are now lone armies trying to escape in the dark. We have managed to capture the Glorious Sun Grade flagship but were unable to find Rogue and the others. They should be hiding within the fleet that's cut off from the network."

Han Xiao stroked his chin and said, "It seems like they noticed my infiltration and chose to cut off their tails to escape. Heh, this commander is somewhat capable."

"Black Star, do you have any ideas?"

"As long as those troops connect to the quantum network for even an instant, their locations will be exposed." Han Xiao shrugged his shoulders.

When he left behind the infiltration software, he had not learned [Virtual Creator] yet and was restricted by the firewall. If he had his current standard back then, it would not be as simple as infiltrating their system. He would have been able to bypass their defenses and use a virus to control the artificial intelligence of the enemy's battleship. Even if the enemy cut off connection from the network, he would have been able to force the enemy's artificial intelligence to reactivate it.

"I can try to tell their fortunes," Ravenlaude said. "However, the Arcane Church has two Mages, and they have definitely set up a force field to block their destiny lines and prevent others from spying on them."

"Just give it a try since it doesn't require money." Han Xiao raised his brows.

Ravenlaude snorted, and a purple light appeared within his palms. A light blue crystal appeared in his palm with a gray cloud within it.

The crystal then floated in front of him, and Ravenlaude tapped his forehead. Indigo light then flashed in the crystal, and an image gradually appeared in the gray cloud.

Everyone then stretched their necks to take a look, and Ninjia's face appeared within the crystal. He then looked at Ravenlaude as though he had noticed something.

Ka-cha!

The next moment, the crystal, which was not cheap, split in two.

"It was blocked indeed," Ravenlaude said with resignation.

Everyone then looked at him as if him being a disappointment was expected.

Ravenlaude had thick skin and even asked if he could claim his losses.

Tarrokov decided to ignore him temporarily.

"The enemy has chosen to split up their forces with every division being much smaller than before," Heber said with a deep voice. "Rogue's fleet is probably the only one capable of breaking through our obstruction. The moment a Beyond Grade A takes action, they will be discovered by our people. However, we have not had any such reports, which means that they have not met our troops."

"They are truly lucky." Beyoni snorted.

Eh? Luck... Han Xiao then blinked, and an idea came to his head. He then turned around to look at Feidin with a burning gaze.

"Feidin, if I asked you to choose, which direction do you think Rogue would escape in? You are pretty lucky, and your guess may be right."

Feidin did not know whether to laugh or cry.

"Black Star, it is one thing for you to tease me usually, but how can you do so in front of outsiders? You shouldn't joke about this, right?"

"What are you talking about? I am not joking at all," Han Xiao said seriously. "You can also see that we are facing a huge problem that cannot be solved. Why don't you give it a try? Who knows what will happen?"

Seeing Han Xiao's insistence, Feidin could only helplessly point at a few spots on the star map casually.

"Hey, don't blame me if I am wrong."

Han Xiao chuckled and said, "Chief commander, why don't you search the few directions that he pointed out? We may really be able to find Rogue."

"This is too childish!" Aurora could not help commenting.

However, she looked up and realized that Tarrokov and the other Beyond Grade As had calm expressions on their faces as though they did not find it strange.

"I see," Tarrokov said. "Relying on instincts isn't a bad choice right now."

Milizaus and the others nodded in agreement.

They were all experts with a great deal of experience and believed in intuition as well.

Luck was a part of strength!

Rogue's fleet only had ten or so small spaceships, and after cutting themselves off from the network, they had lost contact with the other divisions. They did not know how many of their divisions had been captured and could only choose to escape.

"We aren't too far from the secret stargate, and we haven't met with any dynasty fleets," Rogue said, looking at the star map. "As long as we go past the barricade set up by the dynasty, we will be able to arrive at the stargate."

"Looks like our luck isn't bad," Taylor said.

"It isn't entirely luck," Rogue replied. "We intentionally misled the dynasty's fleet about our direction, and thus, the lockdown in this direction is thinner."

Sagman nodded slowly and replied, "According to our current speed, we will be able to..."

Whoo!

Before he could finish, the alarm suddenly went off.

"Alert! Radar scan detected. Our disguise has been seen through. Please prepare for battle!"

Everyone nodded and saw a dynasty fleet approaching them from the radar.

"Dammit!" Rogue slammed the control panel.

Their concealment mode could hide their location, but the enemy radar would still be able to pick them up at close proximity. A dynasty fleet that was in detection mode had just gone past them and thus detected their presence.

Rogue then turned around and shouted at Sagman and the others, "The enemy has fifty battleships. Please get rid of them quickly!"

Although the battleships of the Arcane Church were slightly faster, the Crimson Dynasty's technological skills also belonged to the Universal Civilization grade and would not be thrown off so easily.

If they tried to continue their escape, the surrounding dynasty fleets would also detect their location. Therefore, they had no choice but to wipe out this fleet that had spotted them.

Sagman and the others nodded solemnly.

Aided by the five Beyond Grade As, Rogue's fleet easily wiped out their enemy but also revealed the existence of Sagman and the others.

"The dynasty already knows that we are in this direction and will definitely attempt to prevent us from escaping. We must escape before the enemy Beyond Grade As arrive..." Rogue clenched his fists tightly.

Because their location had been exposed, Rogue's fleet had to endure many layers of restrictions and could no longer attempt to escape stealthily. They could only forge a bloody path out and were extremely pathetic.

They originally wanted to speed up but ended up being slowed down by the layers of battleships.

Tarrokov, Han Xiao, and the others received news and immediately changed direction to give chase.

The distance between both parties was decreasing as they approached the stargate.

This time, Rogue and the others were charging straight toward the location of the secret stargate, and the dynasty's fleet had finally discovered the secret stargate. Thus, an intense battle broke out with the Arcane Church fleet that was stationed at the stargate.

Rogue and the others eventually managed to arrive at the stargate by relying on the strength of the five Beyond Grade As.

The Arcane Church fleet was currently engaged in an intense battle with the dynasty fleet, and reinforcements were coming from the other side of the stargate endlessly.

From afar, Rogue and the others witnessed the battle. Hope of their escape was right before their eyes, and they could not help but grow excited.

Rogue connected to the quantum network again and contacted the fleet stationed by the stargate. Following which, they then charged straight into the rear of the dynasty's fleet and joined the battle to kill their way to the stargate.

However, Tarrokov led the main fleet and arrived at this moment. Han Xiao and the others immediately spotted Sagman's group of five, who were trying to use their strength to break through the dynasty's formation.

"Do it!"

Without any hesitation, Han Xiao's group of five left the spaceship and charged straight toward Sagman.

Rogue was the first to notice this, and his face turned ashen.

The Beyond Grade As still had a chance to escape into the stargate with their strength, but he had no way of escaping!

He had even abandoned his fleet mercilessly, but he still was not able to escape‽

The powerful energy reaction attracted the attention of Sagman and the others, and their expressions changed greatly.

"They caught up!"

"We cannot be tied down by them!"

Sagman's group of five did not even dare turn around to fight back and sped up toward the stargate. They only wanted to arrive at the stargate before Han Xiao and the others could catch up to them.

They knew that it would be impossible for them to escape from the Flickering World once they were tied down by experts of the same level.

Five brilliant rays of lights were escaping with five chasing behind them.

"Attack the stargate!"

All those who had long-range attacks in Han Xiao's party began opening fire at the stargate.

Various Beyond Grade A attacks bombarded the stargate, and cracks appeared on the protective shield covering the planet. It would not last for long.

Sagman and the others gritted their teeth and took the initiative to block the long-range attacks. They would rather get injured to reduce the damage of the stargate and borrow the strength of the attack to speed up their escape.

It was now the Arcane Church group's turn to protect the stargate, and they were in an extremely pathetic state.

The mechanical army caused the greatest damage, and Mercer was the most pathetic. He was not like the others and did not have any long-range energy shields. He could only use his own body to endure the attacks, and his speed was gradually slowing down.

Sagman and the two Mages were the fastest and charged straight into the stargate first. Psyker followed close behind them, and he used his psychic energy to receive a wave of attacks from the mechanical army, spitting out blood as he entered the stargate.

Four of them escaped through the stargate, and only Mercer was left on the battlefield. Han Xiao and the others finally caught up when he was not too far away from the stargate.

Heber charged forward and held onto Mercer. They then tangled with each other, and Mercer's flying trajectory was thrown off course by Heber's intervention. He smashed into the weakened protective shield and crashed into a corner of the stargate.

Han Xiao then waved his hands, and a portion of his mechanical army charged into the stargate as scouts.

The next moment, he lost contact with the mechanical army, and it was destroyed.

The whirlpool in the stargate then disappeared, and it was shut from the other side.

Upon seeing that, Milizaus snorted. "The four who escaped destroyed the other end of the stargate. Humph, it seems like they have abandoned Mercer."

"At least we caught one," Ravenlaude said with a smirk.

Everyone then turned around to look at Mercer. He was currently surrounded in all directions and had no way to escape.

Heber was currently locked in a fierce battle with the crazed Mercer.

Upon noticing their gazes, Heber said with a deep voice, "This is my prey. Don't intervene."

Since it was impossible for Mercer to escape, they did not mind watching a one-on-one fight to observe both of their strengths.

Han Xiao then cheered, "How energetic, Little Ty-Ty."

"Stop calling me that!"

Heber decided to just ignore Han Xiao and focus his attention on dealing with Mercer.

After finally getting a chance to capture a Beyond Grade A, he would not give it up.

The stargate had already been destroyed, and the enemy did not have any way out. This battle was already as good as over.

At this moment, Tarrokov joined in the conversation and announced with a satisfied look, "Four escaped with one left behind. Rogue has also been captured, and our results aren't too bad. Even if Sagman's group of four can escape from the Flickering World, they will still have to face another wave of attacks."

Escaping from the Flickering World did not mean that they would be safe.

The Crimson Dynasty arranged for troops to block them in the Shattered Star Ring. The Black Star Army, Bloodshed Land, Klent, and all the other allies of the dynasty had also made their move, not to mention the restless Federation of Light.

Their life of escaping had not come to an end, and they would still have to go through the vast Shattered Star Ring.

Upon hearing that, Han Xiao said, "I just infiltrated the database of the stargate and obtained coordinates of the stargate on the other side."

Tarrokov's eyes lit up.

"This way, we will be able to uproot this secret stargate for good, and it will be much easier for us to lock onto their location. Black Star, good job!"

Han Xiao smiled and turned around to look at the battle between Heber and Mercer.

Capturing Mercer was only a matter of time.

Heaving a sigh of relief, a cold light flashed past Han Xiao's eyes.

This was the second Beyond Grade A captive that they had caught!

Would the Arcane Church be satisfied with his return gift?

At the same time, in some part of the desolate universe belt was the exit of the Arcane Church's secret stargate.

Sagman's group of four looked at the stargate that had been destroyed by them and fell silent.

"Mercer... wasn't able to escape..."

Sagman gritted his teeth so hard to the point his teeth almost cracked.

If they had succeeded with their mission and gotten rid of Milizaus, Beyoni, and Black Star, the dynasty would only have had three Beyond Grade As left, and they would have been able to escape easily.

But now...

They had lost the entire battle because of a moment of carelessness!

"We can't stop here," Ninjia said. "Black Star will definitely be able to find this location. Hurry up and leave."

Sagman then snapped back to his senses and said with a dark expression, "Let's go. We must take the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter back."

It had been a long time since they were reduced to such a pathetic state!

Chapter 860: Invitation and Announcement

The remaining soldiers of the Arcane Church were all captured by the dynasty.

The stubborn Mercer and Heber were locked in an intense battle with their fists raining down on each other and Pugilist flames shooting out in all directions like the sparks from the clash of weapons.

A Beyond Grade A Pugilist had grasped the true essence of speed and strength, and their movements were like lightning, which came with numerous afterimages behind them. Milizaus and the others rarely fought in close range, and they admired the battle from the side.

Both of them fought until they were tired and riddled with injuries all over. Heber's situation was slightly better, and he held onto Mercer tightly, bringing him onto the spaceship.

Bang!

Mercer's dense body was thrown onto the ground, and the half unconscious Mercer could not get up again.

Heber then took a deep breath to stabilize his surging blood. He then pointed at Mercer, who was by his feet, and said, "I took care of him."

Clapping could then be heard in the room, and Tarrokov gave him a round of applause with a polite smile on his face.

With Black Star one-shotting Dylan during their most desperate moment right before this, none of them thought highly of Heber defeating an opponent who was already defeated before this in a carefully engineered one-on-one fight. In fact, they all felt that it was truly too slow. However, none of them dared say it, afraid that they would offend Heber.

Han Xiao was different, and he was not afraid of Heber. With his drink in his hand, he said while sucking on the straw, "How slow, Little Ty-Ty. Why did you take so long?"

The Pugilists had spent quite some time fighting each other, and the battlefield had already been cleared up. The spectators had already gone to find some drinks and snacks while watching the battle between the two Pugilists.

"Humph." Heber could not be bothered with him.

No matter what, the achievement of defeating Mercer belonged to him, and no one would remember the details of how it happened. They would only know that he defeated another Beyond Grade A, and having the title was sufficient.

Tarrokov then got everyone to come over and said, "Now that Heber is here, let me repeat myself again. I have already informed Her Excellency Urranrell about the battle results, and Her Excellency is extremely satisfied with our results. The Arcane Church fleet has been wiped out, and the dynasty has two Beyond Grade As in their hands.

"With such chips in our hands, the dynasty will have the upper hand, and Her Excellency will announce this matter to the universe and inform all the large and small organizations about the Arcane Church's actions and also the price that they had to pay."

The battle in the Flickering World did not last too long, and the dynasty was still locking down news about it. The outside world was clueless about it, but announcing it to the entire world was only a matter of time.

If the Arcane Church managed to escape safely after the ambush, the dynasty's prestige would be heavily hit. However, things were different now, and not only was the Arcane Church's fleet completely wiped out, two of the six Beyond Grade As of the Arcane Church had been captured. The dynasty's prestige had gone up another level, and the upper echelons were extremely satisfied with the actions of Han Xiao and the others.

The dynasty would not miss such an opportunity to promote their own Beyond Grade As. Han Xiao would be the main focus of the promotion, and the dynasty was prepared to spread news about how he single-handedly turned the situation around.

Increasing the prestige of their allies was akin to increasing the dynasty's prestige. This was a win-win situation.

When they were watching Mercer and the Tyrant have a wrestling match, Tarrokov had already informed Han Xiao about the matter. As such, Han Xiao only nodded slightly to indicate that he acknowledged those words.

The chief commander then said, "On the other side, there are still four Beyond Grade As who escaped into the Shattered Star Ring, and the dynasty will chase after them. However, the situation in the Shattered Star Ring is different from the Flickering World. The dynasty hopes that all of you will temporarily head to the Shattered Star Ring to hold the fort so that you will be able to respond quickly."

The Flickering World was currently the dynasty's territory, and the other organizations did not have any foundation in this place. Thus, the dynasty was able to cast a large net to chase the enemy down without any interference.

However, the situation in the Shattered Star Ring was different, and the various organizations had complicated relationships. The Arcane Church also had various spies in the Shattered Star Ring, and the four Beyond Grade As no longer only had a single escape route. They could easily choose to split up and disguise themselves as ordinary galactic residents.

Furthermore, with the sheer size of a Star Field, searching for the enemy was akin to finding a needle in a haystack.

Of course, as the ones being hunted, Sagman and the others would face danger at every turn, and they would be experiencing much more pressure.

Because the enemy opened the gap with the stargate, the dynasty's Beyond Grade As were unable to continue giving chase and could only choose to hold down the fort in the Shattered Star Ring. After all, the enemy would definitely try to hide themselves, and they would only be able to fight back after discovering the enemy's tracks. If not, they would just be wasting their time.

Han Xiao then smiled and said, "The Shattered Star Ring is the Black Star Army's main camp, so I sincerely welcome all of you to be guests in the Black Star Army. All of your food and accommodation shall be taken care of by me during this period."

Heber immediately said after hearing that, "The Shattered Star Ring is also my territory. The Black Star Army has only been around for a few years, and there is nothing fantastic about them. All of you can come to my Bloodshed Land instead."

Everyone present was a Beyond Grade A Super and had incredible influence. As locals, both Han Xiao and Heber wanted to pull them into their own territory as guests and increase their prestige.

Milizaus then chuckled. "Since Black Star has invited me, I shall go over to his place."

Beyoni also nodded, "Alright, you promised to host me back when we were in the Central Galaxy. Let's make use of this opportunity."

They had spent one month with Han Xiao on Planet Lighthouse and also fought together in a desperate battle a while ago. They were naturally much closer to each other.

"Black Star, I shall also go over to your place," Maximiler, who only had his projection around, said. "We can make use of this opportunity to have an exchange in Mechanic skills."

"Sounds good." Han Xiao agreed.

Maximiler was a Mechanic and would naturally be more interested in someone of his own Class rather than a muscular man.

Everyone ignored Heber's invitation, and Heber felt a little embarrassed. He then turned around to look at the remaining Ravenlaude.

Ravenlaude's mouth cramped up, and he said helplessly, "Then... I shall go to Bloodshed Land."

Since everyone was going to the Black Star Army, he also wanted to join in the fun and see if he could find an opportunity to borrow the Evolution Cube. However, he felt his head ache upon seeing Heber stare at him and could only go against his own wishes.

Heber's expression became slightly better. At least not everyone had ignored him.

He then looked at the three people beside Han Xiao and felt a little defeated.

He had held the Tyrant Party in the Shattered Star Ring for many years and felt that his network was pretty large. However, the experts of the same level in the other Star Fields did not think too highly of him, and he felt that he lost out to Han Xiao in this respect.

Tarrokov then coughed and interrupted the conversation.

"Because of the increased difficulty in searching for the enemy, the dynasty has decided to cut off the enemy's path of retreat and ambush the Arcane Church's stargate stationed in the Shattered Star Ring.

"The Shattered Star Ring envoy Zoel is already mobilizing our forces, and he will launch an attack after the dynasty makes an announcement regarding this matter."

"It seems like we won't be able to arrive in time for this." Han Xiao nodded. "Neither party has any Beyond Grade As to help. Can the dynasty deal with the Arcane Church's forces?"

"You're wrong. We have a Beyond Grade A combatant." Han Xiao was stunned for a moment. "Could it be that the dynasty invited Beyond Grade A allies from the other Star Fields? Wouldn't it take too much time? The Arcane Church will also be able to send out Beyond Grade A combatants if this is the case."

"No, our Beyond Grade A combatant is a local in the Shattered Star Ring."

"Local? Heber and I are in the Flickering World. Austin is still rushing back and won't be able to make it in time. There's no need to talk about Psyker..."

As he said that, Han Xiao suddenly realized something, and his face darkened.

"Did you guys seek help from Ames by using my name‽"

"Black Star, don't misunderstand us. We didn't do that. The Dragon Emperor took the initiative to approach Zoel and requested to participate in the operation," Tarrokov said. "I only found out recently, and Zoel has already agreed to it. With all of you absent, she is the only Beyond Grade A in the Shattered Star Ring and will be able to aid us greatly."

"How did she find out about the matters over here?"

"This... I don't know about that." Tarrokov shook his head.

Han Xiao frowned and walked to the side to contact Ames.

Ames' figure floated up on his communicator, and she sized Han Xiao up upon seeing him before saying with a smile, "Eh, the busy man is finally willing to call me."

Han Xiao did not bother beating about the bush and asked, "Let me ask you, did you contact the dynasty to enter this storm?"

"Why? Do you have an issue?" Ames smirked.

Han Xiao nodded and said, "You shouldn't have. This isn't a good thing for you."

"How long have you known me?" Ames asked with a calm voice. "To me, there are only things that I wish to do and those that I don't wish to do. You are my ally, and since you were ambushed, what kind of ally would I be if I don't help? Humph, you still tried to hide the matter from me. If not for Austin informing me about the matter, I wouldn't have known that you encountered such danger in the Flickering World."

So, it was that darn old man Austin... Han Xiao then said helplessly, "It isn't that I am hiding the matter from you. I just haven't told you yet. I don't need to inform you at the very first moment, right?"

Ames snorted. "... I really wish to beat you up sometimes. It is a pity that you are much stronger than before, and I'm not confident that I can beat the current you."

Han Xiao stroked his chin and said helplessly, "Don't change the topic. The dynasty will be able to attack the stargate even if you don't participate. There's no need for you to do so. You are not a member of the dynasty and do not have the dynasty's protections. Your situation will be tough if you anger the Arcane Church."

"Really? What about Austin? You don't seem to think about him," Ames said with a mocking tone.

"Is that even the same?" Han Xiao shook his head. "Austin owed me a favor, but you don't. Instead, I am the one who owes you a favor. Besides, both of us are allies, and I have to think on your behalf."

"Tsk, it turns out that you still know how to speak like a human." Ames teased him a little before getting serious. "Alright, you don't need to continue. You should know that even Aesop wouldn't be able to convince me otherwise if I make a decision."

"Alright then..."

Han Xiao was a little helpless but also touched. When he was weak, Ames had also stood up for him like this. Now that they were already on the same level, she still chose to do so, and those memories surfaced in his head.

"Then take care of yourself."

After hanging up, Han Xiao contacted Zoel.

Zoel's face appeared, and he said with a friendly expression, "Haha, Your Excellency Black Star. It has been quite some time. I have heard about your merits in the Flickering World. Good job!"

Zoel was the one who had introduced Han Xiao to join the dynasty. Now that Han Xiao had rendered merits to the dynasty, he would also receive some reward and was in a good mood.

"Zoel, I have something to ask of you..." Han Xiao then said his request.

"It's nothing much. Don't worry, I will inform the garrison commander to prevent the Dragon Emperor from fighting at the most dangerous location."

"Alright, I will return to the Shattered Star Ring soon, and we can have a gathering at the headquarters of the Black Star Army. Milizaus, Beyoni, and Maximiler will also be around."

"They are all bigshots." Zoel's eyes lit up. With his current position, he would only be able to meet the Beyond Grade As in the Shattered Star Ring, and there was no chance for him to meet the Beyond Grade As of the other Star Fields. This was a good opportunity for him to get to know them.

After ending the call, Han Xiao returned to Tarrokov's side and used the Spacetime Amber to seal the struggling Mercer with the aid of the others.

Following that, the fleet changed directions and headed toward the stargate located in the Dawn Star Cluster. It would take them a few days to return to the Shattered Star Ring.

Han Xiao had originally thought that he would have to remain in the Flickering World, but never had he thought that he would be able to return to his main camp because of this interlude.

In truth, his physical location did not matter as the Black Star Army would continue their exploration of the Flickering World.

Opening the forums to take a look, the player's [The Crimson Dynasty Order: All Out Pursuit] had not ended yet. There were still many Arcane Church troops scattered all around and also plenty of Fallen Ark troops that had not escaped.

Compared to Sagman's group of four, Han Xiao would rather deal with EsGod. However, the dynasty's attention was currently on the Arcane Church.

Without aid from his teammates, Han Xiao was not confident about killing EsGod.

I can only wait for the Crimson Dynasty to announce this matter to the universe and carry out a large scale counterattack before trying to persuade them about my previous suggestion, Han Xiao thought to himself. The Political Asset should have some influence on this, right?

The day after catching Mercer, the dynasty called for a press conference, and Ruler Urranrell personally revealed the entire incident to the universe.

Countless galactic media groups broadcast the press conference, and the scene of the press conference spread throughout every Star Field.

Regardless of whether it was a variety channel or family channel, every channel showed the press conference of the dynasty.

The captains of various spaceships, customers of bars, travelers in transit stations, and many others all had their eyes glued to the press conference.

Many galactic residents were listening to the Crimson Dynasty's announcement at the same time.

The galactic residents only knew that the Flickering World was a new Star Field that was currently being explored and did not know anything else. However, a battle between eleven Beyond Grade As had actually broken out in this unexplored Star Field with the Arcane Church and the Crimson Dynasty fighting each other head on! Both Universal Civilizations also simultaneously announced that they were entering war time alert!

This announcement was like the explosion of a psionic bomb!

Chapter 861: Changes and Spies

A Universal Civilization that wanted to make use of public opinion as their weapon had sufficient rights to borrow the galactic media groups to spread their voice. The influence of a Universal Civilization covered the various Star Fields, and their influence could not be matched by the Star Cluster civilizations, which were restricted to their own region.

Ruler Urranrell then described the entire process in detail before releasing an official document that recorded the entire event in detail to the public.

The document emphasized how the Arcane Church was blinded by their greed for the Evolution Cube and ignored the fact that the Flickering World was under the control of the dynasty. They had even worked together with the infamous Fallen Ark and ambushed the dynasty's troops, which caused massive losses to the dynasty. The dynasty strongly criticized such an action and reserved the right to pursue the matter. They announced that they were going to stop all activities with the Arcane Church and enter war-time alert.

The dynasty's announcement was extremely solemn and strict, making the galactic residents feel that the dynasty had suffered astronomical loss. But after viewing the document and understanding the exact process of the matter, they were shocked to realize that the dynasty did not suffer too much of a loss but managed to repel the enemy instead. They had even captured two of the enemy's Beyond Grade As in the Flickering World.

Black Star's contributions were greatly emphasized within the document, and his battle results were being promoted. The dynasty wanted to help Han Xiao raise his prestige and deal a heavy blow to the Arcane Church. The Arcane Church was the background for Black Star's contributions, and Black Star was obtaining his prestige by standing on top of the Arcane Church. The greater the spread of this incident, the heavier the blow dealt to the Arcane Church.

News of Black Star capturing Dylan created a huge commotion after spreading out. Han Xiao was a new Beyond Grade A who had created a sensation just a while back, and most of the galactic residents were somewhat familiar with him.

Who would have thought that in less than a year, the newly ascended Black Star would be able to capture an expert of the same level as him?

Killing or capturing a Beyond Grade A alive had significant meaning in the universe. The Beyond Grade A level was already the peak, and if an individual was capable of subduing this peak, their fame would be propelled up to the next level.

Han Xiao had previously fought Psyker and Heber, and the result of the battle was only a draw. Although it could be considered a Beyond Grade A incident, it was not too shocking.

But this time, he had personally defeated a combatant at his level, and it could be said that Han Xiao's status in the universe had stabilized after this battle.

The document also pointed out that Heber had captured a Beyond Grade A Super, but before Black Star's merits, it seemed extremely ordinary. After all, the galactic residents were able to understand the difference. One managed to capture the enemy while being at the absolute disadvantage while the other fought the enemy in a one-on-one battle when the enemy was surrounded. The two events could not be compared.

Apart from the shock of the event, many were worried about the influence of this matter. If the Crimson Dynasty and Arcane Church broke out into open war, the situation in the galaxy would become tense again.

For the past ten years, the Crimson Dynasty and the Federation of Light had been at a standoff. Now that the Federation of Light had become low profile, the Arcane Church decided to walk up the stage.

Ever since the Flickering World was discovered, the galaxy had been unstable.

Regardless of how slow witted the galactic residents were, they were able to see that the three Universal Civilizations were having conflicts around this new Star Field.

...

After the dynasty made their announcement, the various Super Star Cluster and Star Cluster Civilizations immediately activated their intelligence net to gather information.

Black Star had become the focus of all these organizations, and many organizations became wary of him.

The Beyond Grade A allies of the three Universal Civilizations had always been the target for research of the various organizations. However, Han Xiao was different from the other Beyond Grade As that had joined for a few decades. He had joined the dynasty less than a year prior, and information was limited. However, many organizations had no choice but to adjust his threat to the level of the three pillars of the dynasty and label him as a target to pay close attention to.

The Arcane Church then revealed the various methods that Han Xiao had displayed in the battle through their various hidden intelligence agencies, and all the organizations now knew that Black Star had two Universal Treasures in his hands. There was no need to talk about the Evolution Cube since it was the reason for the battle.

However, the other Universal Treasure was actually able to block the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter and seal a Beyond Grade A. With such methods up his sleeves, Black Star had a special strategic position and could not be considered an ordinary Beyond Grade A combatant.

There were naturally those with greed as well. The Arcane Church intentionally revealed such information so that many organizations would eye the Universal Treasure in Han Xiao's hands. They had indeed succeeded, but the other organizations did not dare to take any reckless actions since even the Arcane Church had failed.

Black Star's battle merits were a true deterrent to many organizations.

...

A few days later, the dynasty began their counterattack, and Arcane Church's stargate located in the Shattered Star Ring suffered from an ambush. An intense battle broke out, and it was said that the energy reactions of the battle could be felt from a Star Zone away.

After Sagman's ambush failed, the Arcane Church had guessed that the Crimson Dynasty would attempt to destroy their stargate located in the Shattered Star Ring. Thus, they had already begun mobilizing their reinforcements and had even mobilized other Beyond Grade A combatants.

However, in order to secretly send out six Beyond Grade As, the Arcane Church had gotten their other Beyond Grade As to attract the attention of the public in various locations. As such, it would require some time to mobilize them, and the dynasty managed to seize that window.

Ames was the only Beyond Grade A present in the Shattered Star Ring, and she participated in the attack before the Arcane Church's reinforcements could arrive. Her Force Field was a sharp weapon in galactic warfare and could easily disrupt and penetrate the formation of the army stationed at the stargate. Furthermore, she was also able to use her Force Field to destroy the stargate and cut off the enemy's route of retreat.

Following which, the dynasty began monitoring all the public stargates and sent out their spies to monitor the Arcane Church's movements.

However, as a Universal Civilization, the Arcane Church had many other ways to deal with that.

...

Old Medal Bar was located in the seventh junkyard of some galactic transit station in the Shattered Star Ring. Although it seemed like a public bar that was a little tattered on the surface, it was actually the gathering point of a black-market merchant with the nickname of 'Night Bat'.

There was no absolute order in the universe, and there would always be shadows when light existed. The galactic black market was the biggest shadow in the galactic society.

There would always be needs when there were people, and there would always be smugglers when there were needs. Every region in the universe had their own black markets. Some were businesses that the government chose to look away from, and others were gray regions that were not controlled by any civilizations.

In the black markets of the Shattered Star Ring, Night Bat was not a bigshot. On the contrary, he was an unknown character who mainly collected scrap. He made use of such a disguise to smuggle some military machines.

There was no need for him to behave sneakily. Almost all the locals knew that Old Medal Bar was his black market gathering point, but because of its small size and the items being sold being relatively safe, no organization paid close attention to him. In this galactic transit station, there were hundreds of such black merchants.

Today, a freight captain arrived at the Old Medal Bar, and this captain had been working together with Night Bat for a long time. He would sell some scraps to Night Bat with some smuggled goods hidden within the scraps. Night Bat personally invited him to the underground chamber under his bar to be a guest today.

Only Night Bat and this freight captain were left in the office.

The freight captain then lit a cigarette and blew out a mouthful of smoke. He took out a sheet of paper and pushed it toward Night Bat.

"This is the list of scraps."

"Thanks."

Night Bat was a skinny man with a fawning smile on his face. Everyone would think that he was a crafty merchant upon seeing his face.

"The goods have been delivered. I'll make a move now." The freight captain stood up.

"Aren't you going to have some fun? I heard that Red Widow on Gray Shed Street has some new mixed-blood elves..."

"Mixed blood elves... forget it. Have you heard? The Crimson Dynasty and Arcane Church have begun fighting in the Shattered Star Ring. The situation in the outside world is far too unstable. I will return home after this trip and wait for them to finish their battle before coming out to do business."

The freight captain seemed a little tempted but decided otherwise and left the room.

Night Bat followed behind him and called for his subordinates to shift the scraps on the cargo ship.

With everyone being busy, no one would notice subtle changes. No one noticed that Night Bat had suddenly grown a few centimeters taller with his body shape changing slightly. One of the workers of the freight captain had also experienced such a subtle change.

After half a day, the goods were finally unloaded, and the cargo ship left the planet.

The cargo ship was set to autopilot, and the captain received news of iron eating bugs being spotted in the warehouse.

This was an extremely common bug that would destroy the internal structure of a spaceship. It had to be cleaned up immediately the moment it was spotted.

The captain went to the warehouse, and more than thirty workers had flamethrowers in their hands to burn the ten or so centimeters bugs into ashes.

"Captain, we have already stabilized the situation and are checking the damage. Some goods show signs of being bitten," a worker reported.

Upon hearing that, the freight captain became anxious. All the goods in the warehouse were his customers' orders, and he would have to pay for them if they were damaged.

He was only an ordinary individual in the universe and was not able to afford such goods.

"Bring me to take a look!"

They entered the depths of the warehouse.

Right at that moment, the worker suddenly took out a silenced handgun and aimed it at the captain's head.

"You..." The captain was shocked.

The worker then opened fire decisively

Pap pap pap!

Three bullets shot through the skull of the freight captain. This was definitely a fatal injury to an ordinary individual.

The freight captain landed on the ground with blood flowing out from his body.

This worker wiped his face and took off a mask-like item to reveal Night Bat's appearance.

Night Bat had a cold expression on his face without any trace of his 'cunning merchant' aura.

He took out the access card and communicator from the captain's body and carried the captain's body back to the region where they had been burning bugs.

When Night Bat walked out from the darkness, the situation was already completely different. Only five of the thirty plus workers were left, and they all had silenced handguns in their hands. There were more than twenty corpses on the ground, and they had all been shot dead.

They looked toward Night Bat and greeted him. "Captain."

They were all spies trained by the Arcane Church. Night Bat had disguised himself as a black market merchant for many years to manage an insignificant smuggling business. A portion of his team had been disguised as workers and worked for this freight captain.

After smuggling for so many years, they had secretly gathered sufficient parts to build a new stargate. These workers had secretly loaded up the stargate equipment onto these spaceships when they were unloading the goods previously.

After remaining hidden for such a long time, they had always been waiting for their organization to summon them. The Arcane Church activated these spies at such a moment, and their mission was to obtain an insignificant looking spaceship and meet up with the Beyond Grade As to help them escape with the stargate equipment.

Night Bat's team was not the only one with such a mission; similar scenes were playing out all around the Shattered Star Ring.

These usually insignificant characters had begun to take action.

Beyond Grade A was the peak of individual strength, but no one would be able to call themselves the protagonist of the universe. The universe was far too big, and every character had their own role to play. Even an insignificant individual could influence the bigger picture.

Chapter 862: A Devastating Number

The dynasty's Beyond Grade As returned to the Shattered Star Ring from the Flickering World through the stargate located in the Dawn Star Cluster. After another period of flying, Han Xiao returned to the Colton Star Cluster together with Milizaus and the others.

During the period that they were travelling, the Crimson Dynasty and Arcane Church were in a confrontation in the Central Galaxy, and the situation was extremely tense.

On the Shattered Star Ring's side, the dynasty's forces located at the borders of the Flickering World had thoroughly investigated the secret stargate exit coordinates provided by Han Xiao, but it was already empty.

When they heard this news along the way, everyone knew that the following job belonged mainly to the intelligence personnel, and they would not be able to do much.

In the spaceship, Han Xiao, Milizaus' avatar, Beyoni, and Maximiler were gathered together, looking out at the Black Star Army headquarters outside the window.

Gigantic battleships were taking off and landing on the gigantic planetary grade fortress, and metal buildings loomed everywhere.

The officers present at headquarters had also received news of their arrival and came forward to receive them.

As the hatch opened, Han Xiao and the others disembarked from the spaceship and were greeted with a sea of people. The warriors of the army were lined up neatly and gave a salute in unison.

"Army Commander!"

Upon seeing that, Han Xiao was stunned for a moment and slightly confused.

Why did they arrange for such a grand ceremony? While it was a spectacular scene, he did not remember giving such an order.

In front of the soldiers, Sylvia pushed Lagi forward.

As the vice commander, Lagi had no choice but to step forward. He then cleared his throat and said with a less monotonous voice, "Cough cough, we welcome the Army Commander's return."

Han Xiao's face contorted slightly, and he asked, "What are you guys doing? It has only been a few months since we last met each other. Why bother with such a solemn ceremony?"

"Sylvia said that the entire universe now knows that you have defeated a Beyond Grade A head on, and we can make use of this opportunity to foster the cohesiveness within the army," Herlous said softly.

There was another reason that he did not mention. Sylvia knew that Han Xiao was inviting the allies of the dynasty over as guests and thus created such a scene to build up Han Xiao's image.

Of course, Lagi felt that this was completely pointless but couldn't convince Sylvia otherwise.

Han Xiao did not really like such a display and did not feel that it was necessary for the army to boost his image. However, he would not nitpick something so small. Since he had given his subordinates authority, he would allow them to have their own thoughts. He then instructed, "Arrange a room for these three Excellencies."

"It has already been arranged," Sylvia said.

Right at this moment, Lagi sighed. "I heard that Austin joined in the battle, and this resulted in huge losses for the Forbidden Sorcerers. Is this true?"

"Yes." Han Xiao nodded.

"Sigh, another few familiar faces have disappeared. Thankfully, I switched sides..." Lagi shook his head weakly. "However, it is meaningless to talk about this. In a few more years, all our bodies will rot, and we will become..."

"Alright, I know that we will all become dust. You can keep quiet now," Han Xiao interrupted.

After stopping Lagi from embarrassing himself, Han Xiao turned around to look at Milizaus and the others.

"I have some matters to handle. You guys can go and rest. You can inform my men if you have any needs. I will go and find you guys later."

"Okay."

Milizaus' group of three had no issues with that. Since they were in the territory of another, they would listen to Black Star's arrangements.

Watching the three enter the headquarters, Han Xiao walked toward his office to meet all his officers and asked them about the recent situation.

The army was already on track, and together with him having sufficient prestige, no one in the Shattered Star Ring would dare provoke them.

Furthermore, the galactic pirates and scavengers had begun avoiding the territories of the Black Star Army, which improved the security of many regions.

It was time for the logistics report, and Reynold gave his report calmly. After listening to his report, Han Xiao did not ask about the matters of the army but about Nero's studies.

"He is extremely talented, and his learning speed is extremely fast. He finished reading all the theory books that I gave him."

He was probably forced to read them by you, right?

Han Xiao's mouth contorted slightly, and he asked, "Where is he?"

"Right outside." Reynold then brought Nero in.

After not meeting him for a while, Nero had already grown up. He now had thick eyebags around his eyes and looked extremely sleepy.

Nero was no longer as energetic as before, and he greeted Han Xiao weakly.

"Hello godfather."

"You..."

Seeing his pathetic appearance, Han Xiao felt a tinge of pity.

Reynold, you are truly a demon! Look at how you tortured this kid.

It seemed like he must hide Nero well from the players. If not, those darn players might end up triggering an 'assassinate Reynold' type mission.

Shaking his head, Han Xiao got Nero to stand in front of him. He then pricked Nero slightly to activate the battle notification and viewed Nero's attributes.

Wait a moment, this...

Looking at the interface, a look of surprise could be seen on Han Xiao's face.

In Nero's talent section, a new talent that had not been there before appeared. It was [Middle Grade Mechanical Sense]!

My guess was correct! Nero has an Advanced Luck Glow and has the right to obtain a Molding Talent. He can even learn a talent like Mechanical Sense!

Although it was only [Middle Grade Mechanical Sense] at the moment, he had a chance of learning Reynold's [Perfect Mechanical Sense] if he continued!

There was finally a new point to break through to Reynold, and Han Xiao was truly excited!

Thinking about that, Han Xiao stroked Nero's head and said with concern, "Your appearance looks extremely poor. Are you too tired from studying?"

Nero then glanced at Reynold, and his body trembled slightly. "No... not tired at all..."

"Don't need to be afraid. You can just tell the truth with me around."

Looking at Han Xiao's compassionate eyes, Nero felt a sense of courage welling up in his heart. He then began to openly complain about Reynold's crimes.

"Godfather, he doesn't even treat me as a human. The sheer amount of homework that he gives isn't even meant for a human! I have less than three hours of sleep every day, and it is interfering with my development. I... I am still a kid!"

Han Xiao then looked at Reynold and snorted. "Is this the truth?"

"Since the Army Commander handed Nero over to me, I will not let you down," Reynold said with a strict appearance. "I will definitely groom him to become a great Mechanic!"

"Sigh, I know that your intentions are good, but you must pay attention to your method." Han Xiao shook his head.

Upon hearing that, a glimmer could be seen in Nero's eyes, and he felt a trace of hope in his heart.

Godfather is speaking on my behalf!

Does this mean that my hellish life will end today‽

His body trembled with excitement, and he was like a man dying from thirst in the desert who saw an oasis.

At this moment, Nero suddenly felt as though a sacred halo could be seen on Han Xiao's body.

Han Xiao took out a bottle filled with dragon's blood. This was Milizaus' blood that he had gathered from the battlefield. He then said to Reynold, "Give this dragon blood to Emerald Grass and get her to research a body strengthening medicine."

The next moment, Han Xiao turned around and looked at Nero with a smile.

"Reynold didn't think things through. How can you learn properly without a strong body? Medicine developed from dragon's blood will be able to replenish your energy, and your development won't be affected no matter how late you sleep. Don't worry and follow Reynold. You must learn properly."

Nero's smile froze in place, and his eyes widened.

In his eyes, the sacred glow on Han Xiao's body seemed to have become a demonic aura, and his godfather's smile was like a demon's grin.

Tears welled up in his eyes and were about to burst forth.

Nero cried his heart and lungs out.

Godfather is also a demon!

Wuwuwu... father, mother, I don't want to live in space anymore. I want to return home!

As Reynold heard that, his eyes lit up, and he nodded with praise.

You are indeed the Army Commander that I respect. You are also a demon.

Han Xiao then got Sylvia to comfort Nero. It was a pity that Rossellin had gone to become a revolutionary. If not, she would have been able to easily fix this mental damage.

Following which, he then used a blank Character Summon Card on Reynold to replenish the number of times he can use Perfect Mechanical Sense. The blank Character Summon Card was slightly different to the previous reward, and he only had a single chance to use it.

Who knew how long it would take for Nero to learn the [Perfect Mechanical Sense]? Han Xiao had always kept his guard up ever since the Planet Lighthouse battle and was worried that the Arcane Church might become desperate. As such, he had to keep a trump card prepared.

After settling his internal affairs, Han Xiao went to find Milizaus and the others and led them on a tour of his headquarters. He also contacted Tarrokov to discuss the dynasty's pursuit mission.

The dynasty's forces present in the desolate universe belt near the Shattered Star Ring were smaller than their forces in the Flickering World. Together with the fact that the enemy had made use of a secret stargate, the dynasty was not able to set up a defensive line in time. By making use of that small opening, Sagman's group had successfully avoided the dynasty's surveillance and escaped into the Shattered Star Ring.

"According to the spatial fluctuations left behind, we believe that Sagman's group of four have decided to split up. This has increased the difficulty of our search." Tarrokov's projection floated beside them and walked together.

"It will be akin to a drop of water entering the ocean when they enter the Shattered Star Ring. It will be incredibly difficult to find them," Beyoni said.

"That's right. Her Excellency also thinks so." Tarrokov nodded. "According to reliable intelligence, the Arcane Church has activated many of their spies in the Shattered Star Ring to save these four Beyond Grade As. Every Universal Civilization has many spies located in the various Star Fields disguised as workers from various occupations, and it is incredibly difficult to see through them. It is an important source of information, and it will be much easier for Sagman and the others to escape with their help."

"Hidden spies... If we can get a list of the spies, we will be able to track them." Han Xiao stroked his chin.

"That's impossible." Tarrokov shook his head. "Such a list will be stored in the main database of the Universal Civilization and protected by a Beyond Grade A Virtual Mechanic. The firewall will be extremely powerful, and it will be impossible to infiltrate them."

"Will those spies contact the higher ups?"

"The spies of a Universal Civilization will report directly to the intelligence agency, and a single encrypted command can allow them to willingly remain hidden for ten years. They do not have any higher ups."

"I see. Then forget it." Han Xiao shook his head and decided to forget about this matter.

Tarrokov then said, "Although it is incredibly difficult to capture them, we cannot give up halfway. We may have some unexpected rewards as well and uproot some of the Arcane Church's spies. We can attempt to completely wipe out all the hidden pieces that the Arcane Church has in the Shattered Star Ring! If they want to plant new spies, it will take them a few decades for sure."

"Hmm, this is fine as well. Rather than attempt to chase after four extremely nimble Beyond Grade As, we might as well uproot the Arcane Church's spies," Maximiler said.

Capturing two Beyond Grade A captives was already a satisfactory battle result.

They were worried that the Arcane Church might truly become desperate after losing even more Beyond Grade As and end up in a large-scale assassination attempt toward each other's Beyond Grade As.

There was an example of such an incident. During the exploration era a thousand years earlier, there was a historical incident called the Saint Menason Incident.

At that time, the leaders from the three Universal Civilizations were not the present ones, and an important Beyond Grade A called 'Saint Menason' from the Federation of Light was ambushed by two Beyond Grade As from the dynasty. Their target was to snatch the Universal Treasure in Saint Menason's hands. However, the Federation of Light called even more Beyond Grade A combatants to counter-ambush the two Beyond Grade As and snatch the Universal Treasure back.

The two dead Beyond Grade As had many friends, and a huge chain reaction was created.

Because of this, the Federation of Light and the Crimson Dynasty began to push the blame onto each other politically.

Nine months later, the dynasty's Beyond Grade As worked together and washed the organizations that belonged to three Beyond Grade As from the Federation of Light with blood. They also got rid of two of the Federation of Light's Beyond Grade As, and only one managed to escape. During this period, the biological brother of an Arcane Church Beyond Grade A also died in the battle because he was a guest at the ambush site.

Because of this, the Arcane Church was dragged into the matter, and another series of assassinations unfolded, which led to the opening of the curtains behind the 'Tragedy of the Pinnacles' event. The three Universal Civilizations began to assassinate each other's Beyond Grade As, and more and more people died. In the eyes of a civilization, a Beyond Grade A combatant was a strategic weapon, and they would not allow other Beyond Grade As to live if their own had died. As such, the conflict between the civilizations grew deeper and deeper.

During the 'Tragedy of the Pinnacles' incident, the three Universal Civilizations sacrificed many Beyond Grade A Supers, and the turning point of the incident was what the civilizations called the Saint Menason Incident. There was actually a mastermind behind the scene, and it was a Super Star Cluster civilization at that time. The three Universal Civilizations then claimed that they found solid evidence to believe that these Super Star Cluster civilizations were fanning the flames from behind the scenes and wanted to make them lose some Beyond Grade As.

Following which, the three Universal Civilizations then wiped out all the Beyond Grade As of that Super Star Cluster civilization and their allies before the entire incident came to an end.

At that time, around half of the Beyond Grade As in the known universe were killed. A few neutral Beyond Grade As were unable to avoid the matter and were forced to join the three Universal Civilizations.

As for whether the mastermind behind the matter was truly the Super Star Cluster civilization, only the three Universal Civilizations knew. In any case, that was how it was written in history.

Although their Beyond Grade As were dead, the civilization was still around. While the three Universal Civilizations were much more peaceful in the Galaxy Calendar era, the majority did not wish to see history repeat itself. After that incident, the number of Beyond Grade As being sacrificed was reduced greatly.

"Don't worry, even if we can't catch Sagman and the others, there is a target that won't be able to escape," Tarrokov said with a smile.

"Psyker right?" Han Xiao also smiled.

The Star Pupil Holy Race was in the Shattered Star Ring, and it was impossible for Psyker to escape. Even if the dynasty adhered to the Peace Treaty and did not attack the Star Pupil Holy Race, it would be impossible for Psyker not to return forever.

If he had killed Han Xiao successfully and snatched the Evolution Cube back, Psyker would have had the protection of the Arcane Church and would not have been in such a passive state.

For now, however, Psyker was truly in a pathetic state.

Han Xiao only had a single thought toward Psyker's current situation.

There's no hope. Let's move house.